<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<search>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>It&#39;s true that if you&#39;re in a bad mood, you will become &quot;ugly&quot;! 7 Skin Conditions Affected by Emotions</title>
    <link href="/Its-true-that-if-youre-in-a-bad-mood-you-will-become-ugly-7-Skin-Conditions-Affected-by-Emotions/"/>
    <url>/Its-true-that-if-youre-in-a-bad-mood-you-will-become-ugly-7-Skin-Conditions-Affected-by-Emotions/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>You may have discovered that when you are in a bad mood, your complexion will become dark yellow and rough, and your whole person’s state is not right.</p><p>A large number of scientific studies have found that 70% of people will digest bad emotions in a way that damages their physical health, and “skin” is an outlet for emotions such as anger, fear, and sadness.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203071.webp"></p><p>A good mood will make the skin radiant, and a bad mood will reduce the appearance of the skin by affecting the skin.</p><p><strong>Skin condition is linked to mood</strong></p><p>Human emotional behavior and hormone secretion are governed by the hypothalamus. The hypothalamus communicates with the cerebral cortex and the pituitary gland and other nervous tissues. It is the center that regulates nerves, humor, and the endocrine.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203072.gif"></p><p>When people are happy, the secretion of the neuroregulatory substance acetylcholine in the brain increases, the blood is smooth, the subcutaneous blood vessels dilate, and the blood flow to the skin. Look radiant, radiant, and full of energy.</p><p>If you are depressed and anxious for a long time, excessive melanin synthesis by epithelial cells will be deposited on the skin surface, making the skin dull and dull, and even the formation of chloasma.</p><p>Depressed mood can also lead to neurasthenia, insomnia, affecting the blood supply of the skin, making the face haggard and dark circles under the eyes.</p><p>Skin allergies are also affected by mood changes. When the mood changes suddenly, the nerve endings will release a large amount of acetylcholine, and acetylcholine can directly act on the blood vessels of the skin, causing vasodilation, prompting the release of histamine, and then causing allergic reactions.</p><p><strong>7 skin diseases implicated in bad moods</strong></p><p>Long-term mental stress often makes it difficult to breathe, and 7 skin diseases are particularly susceptible to bad moods.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203073.gif"></p><p><strong>Acne</strong></p><p>Mental stress will promote the secretion of adrenal cortex hormones and male hormones, induce acne, and also increase the secretion of neuropeptides at the site of skin lesions, aggravating the inflammatory response.</p><p><strong>Alopecia areata</strong></p><p>People who are anxious, impatient or pessimistic, and emotionally sensitive area prone to alopecia areata. The psychological state of the patients with alopecia areata is the basis of the disease. With the improvement of the state of mind, the symptoms of most patients will also improve.</p><p><strong>Atopic dermatitis (eczema)</strong></p><p>Studies have shown that nearly 67% of patients have more stressful life events before and during the disease. Stress, insomnia, fatigue, mood changes, and other factors can induce or aggravate eczema.</p><p>In addition to following doctor’s orders, patients should also pay attention to their mental health and avoid excessive stress.</p><p><strong>Neurodermatitis</strong></p><p>Neurodermatitis, also known as lichen simplex chronicus, is a lichen-like degeneration of the skin caused by repeated scratching, accompanied by severe or paroxysmal itching.</p><p>In addition to medication, patients may consider psychiatric or behavioral therapy to interrupt the vicious cycle of “itch-scratch-itch”.</p><p><strong>Psoriasis</strong></p><p>Psoriasis, commonly known as psoriasis, is a chronic, recurrent, inflammatory, systemic disease. It is also a typical physical and mental skin disease, and mental stress is one of the factors that trigger and aggravate the disease.</p><p>Although psoriasis cannot be cured, it can be alleviated, controlled, or even stopped by standard treatment. During the treatment, the patient should maintain a good mood and receive psychotherapy if necessary.</p><p><strong>Vitiligo</strong></p><p>Vitiligo is a localized or generalized depigmented spot caused by the destruction of melanocytes or a disorder of melanin synthesis.</p><p>Several clinical observations have found that psychological stress such as stress, anxiety, and depression are closely related to vitiligo. Anxiety and depression can aggravate the disease, and if the disease persists, it will in turn increase the negative emotions of patients.</p><p><strong>Systemic lupus erythematosus</strong></p><p>Systemic lupus erythematosus is an autoimmune disease that invades multiple systems. In mild cases, it only affects the skin, and in severe cases, it affects multiple organs and is even life-threatening.</p><p>Emotional stimulation is one of the predisposing factors for lupus erythematosus. Clinical findings showed that most patients had significant depression in childhood, or had an obvious interpersonal crisis before the onset.</p><p><em><strong>Prevention advise from a dermatologist</strong></em></p><p>Long-term mental stress will cause problems in sweat gland secretion, skin microvascular relaxation, and hair nutrition. To avoid the impact of skin diseases, it is necessary to resolve negative emotions in time in life, and dermatologists give preventive advice on this.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203074.gif"></p><p><strong>Improve unhealthy living habits</strong></p><p>In life, pay attention to a balanced diet, regular work and rest, ensure adequate sleep, and avoid staying up late for a long time, overwork, etc.</p><p><strong>Increase outdoor sports</strong></p><p>Go outdoors often, breathe fresh air, enhance physical fitness, pay attention to psychological adjustment, and resolve negative emotions in time.</p><p><strong>Pay attention to indoor hygiene</strong></p><p>During the virus epidemic season, it is also necessary to pay attention to frequent indoor ventilation to promote air circulation, frequent cleaning of the environment, and frequent drying of clothes and bedding.</p><p><strong>Virus rash patients pay attention to isolation and disinfection</strong></p><p>Patients with viral rash at home (mainly manifested by rash and fever all over the body) should be isolated in time, take antiviral drugs reasonably, and disinfect the items and rooms they use.</p><p>Experts remind that in addition to physical pain, many patients feel inferior because of their appearance damage or strange vision, and fall into a vicious circle of mutual influence between a bad mood and skin disease.</p><p>After skin problems, everyone must go to a regular hospital for treatment as soon as possible.</p>]]></content>
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>How can short videos be addictive? Scientists &#39;scan&#39; the brain and found...</title>
    <link href="/How-can-short-videos-be-addictive-Scientists-scan-the-brain-and-found/"/>
    <url>/How-can-short-videos-be-addictive-Scientists-scan-the-brain-and-found/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>If you ask what is the favorite pastime of contemporary people, it is estimated that many people will say: watching videos. On the way to work, while eating, lying in bed before going to bed… Short videos are more and more deeply involved in our lives.</p><p>How much time do you spend watching short videos every day?</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203051.gif"></p><p>What is your brain doing when you watch short videos?</p><p>People who often watch short videos will have a feeling that after watching one video one by one, inertia will gradually form, and if you want to keep scrolling down, you can’t stop at all.</p><p>Have you ever wondered what happened to our brain at this time?</p><p>NeuroImage published a study from Zhejiang University in China that used a functional MRI to reveal the brain while watching short videos.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203052.webp"></p><p>The researchers invited subjects to watch normally recommended videos for new users and personalized recommended videos for old users and found that some components of the brain’s default mode network were more active when watching personalized recommended videos, specifically including bilateral Superior and middle temporal gyrus, temporal pole, ventral posterior cingulate cortex, medial prefrontal cortex, and angular gyrus.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203053.webp"></p><p>In addition, the ventral tegmental area of the midbrain and other discrete brain areas such as the lateral prefrontal lobe, the anterior thalamus, and the cerebellum, which are related to the reward system, also showed higher activation states. And the coupling of regions of the brain’s default mode network to visual and auditory pathways has also been enhanced, which may lead to greater video addiction by up-regulating attention and higher-level perception.</p><p>The default mode network is mainly composed of the medial prefrontal cortex, the posterior cingulate cortex, and the angular gyrus, and is a large neural network spanning the entire brain.</p><p>Decreased activity in the default mode network is the brain’s most visible signal when it comes to paying attention.</p><p>The default mode network becomes very active when people have nothing to do and think about.</p><p><strong>Which nerve does the short video tease?</strong></p><p>Adam Alter, Ph.D. of Psychology at Princeton University, in his book “Can’t Stop: How to Get Rid of Behavioral Addiction in the Age of Swiping” lists six elements of behavioral addiction: tempting goals, irresistible and unpredictable positive feedback, A sense of incremental improvement, increasingly difficult tasks, unresolved tensions that need to be resolved, strong social connections.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203054.gif"></p><p><strong>Irresistible and unpredictable positive feedback</strong></p><p>When you open the short video software, there is almost no operation required, and the software will scroll to show you interesting and interesting short videos of more than ten seconds.</p><p>The background of the short video software can analyze everyone’s preferences based on big data, and make targeted pushes, so that people can’t help but wonder what the next one will be after watching one.</p><p>These surprises and surprises will prompt the brain to continuously secrete the “happy hormone” dopamine, which makes people feel joy and can’t help repeating a behavior.</p><p><strong>Unresolved tension that needs to be resolved</strong></p><p>Most of the short videos are only 15 seconds long and are accompanied by a climax of the music, which means that each short video must quickly show the main point of the story of the development, and it is incomplete, giving a feeling of unfinished business.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203055.gif"></p><p>It is this kind of expectation of “unfinished” and “is there still” that will provoke the nerves of users, making people want to watch more and longer.</p><p><strong>Have immediate goals</strong></p><p>Short videos are mostly short, light-hearted, and can be watched quickly without much effort, which is very attractive in itself, and for people who take a long time in real life to feel that “one thing is done” is attractive. especially powerful.</p><p><strong>Create difficult tasks</strong></p><p>The short video software will also release some new, difficult, and interesting tasks from time to time for everyone to challenge.</p><p><strong>Strong social connections</strong></p><p>Many times we can see similar experiences to ourselves in videos and comment areas, hear the words that come into our hearts, and find things that we can empathize with… These are very important to loneliness, incomprehension, self-doubt, or being malicious and attacked. It’s a very safe “habitat” for people who are not alone, and it makes people feel like they’re not alone.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203056.gif"></p><p><strong>How to watch short videos in moderation</strong></p><p>Nothing is absolutely good or bad, and the same is true for short videos:</p><p>A short video is a tool that allows people to contact more new things in a short period, and the transmission of any information in life needs this kind of short and smooth way.</p><p>For example, an advertisement introducing a product, an advanced technology that needs to be promoted and popularized to everyone, teaching everyone a small life skill in a short way, or leading everyone to appreciate the beauty of a tourist destination, etc.</p><p>On the one hand, a short video liberates the viewer’s nature and relieves pressure; on the other hand, it adds happiness and fun and makes life no longer dull.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203057.gif"></p><p>Modern people are busy with work, and free time has become very precious, and short video is a very typical pastime and information sharing using fragmented time.</p><p>This kind of dissemination seems to improve efficiency, but in fact, the information obtained in a short period is not systematic, and because the video is short, it does not require people to concentrate for a long time, making it difficult for people to form effective memory.</p><p>Once we get used to this way of getting information, the attention span becomes shorter and shorter.</p><p>A short video is just a tool and platform. We can become its masters to improve ourselves and enrich our lives, instead of being led by tools.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203058.gif"></p><p>When watching short videos, it is recommended to do:</p><p><strong>Control time</strong></p><p>Watching for a few hours is not only a waste of time, but also affects your eyesight. You must also pay attention to your priorities in life, and don’t miss the important things in reality by watching short videos.</p><p><strong>Classified treatment</strong></p><p>For some practical information that can increase your knowledge or make use of it, you can refer to it, but choose to ignore some vulgar and sensational content to avoid adverse effects.</p><p>For people who are not so addicted and just regret spending a lot of time watching videos, improving self-control is the key. Scheduling a regular viewing time, setting a good time, asking a friend to supervise interruptions, and putting your phone away before bed can all help to “break the brakes.”</p>]]></content>
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Banana is the most radioactive fruit, why do I recommend you to eat more?</title>
    <link href="/Banana-is-the-most-radioactive-fruit-why-do-I-recommend-you-to-eat-more/"/>
    <url>/Banana-is-the-most-radioactive-fruit-why-do-I-recommend-you-to-eat-more/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Banana, sweet and soft, is a fruit suitable for all ages. After eating bananas for so many years, did you know that they actually have radiation?</p><p>German physicist Derek Muller once experimented on how much radiation is around us. Experiments found that eating a banana will receive 0.1μSv of radiation.</p><p>Since bananas have radiation, can we still eat them with confidence? You can’t just eat it, I also advise you to eat more.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203035.gif"></p><p><strong>Eating bananas, will radiation accumulate in the body?</strong></p><p>The radiation of bananas is related to the element potassium. The potassium content of bananas is abundant in the fruit, and the content of potassium-40 is relatively high. Therefore, bananas have also become the most radiant variety of fruits.</p><p>As the most radioactive food in the fruit world, the radiation dose of bananas is actually very small. Eating 80,000 bananas is equivalent to taking a chest CT.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203031.webp"></p><p>An hour near the Chernobyl nuclear power plant is equivalent to eating 50 bananas</p><p>After we eat a banana, the potassium content in the body will increase by 0.4%, but this is only temporary. Our metabolism controls the amount of potassium in the body, and excess potassium is excreted by the kidneys.</p><p>That is, the radiation produced by bananas does not accumulate in the body.</p><p><em><strong>8 hidden benefits of bananas</strong></em></p><p>Bananas are a good source of vitamins and minerals. The data shows that every 100 grams of bananas contain 60 micrograms of carotene, as well as B vitamins such as thiamine, riboflavin, and niacin, as well as vitamin C.</p><p>Along with being delicious, bananas have many health benefits:</p><ol><li><strong>Protect blood vessels</strong></li></ol><p>Bananas are rich in potassium (256 mg of potassium per 100 grams, 0.8 mg of sodium), which can inhibit the rise of blood pressure and damage to blood vessels caused by sodium. Therefore, people with high blood pressure and heart disease should eat bananas.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203032.gif"></p><ol start="2"><li><strong>Get rid of fatigue</strong></li></ol><p>Bananas are high-potassium foods and rich in magnesium. Modern medicine has confirmed that potassium can maintain normal blood pressure and heartbeat, prevent blood pressure from rising and muscle spasms, while magnesium has the effect of eliminating fatigue.</p><p>In addition, the sugar in bananas can be quickly converted into glucose, which is immediately absorbed by the body and is a fast source of energy, so eating a banana after exhaustion can replenish physical strength.</p><ol start="3"><li><strong>Improve brain power</strong></li></ol><p>A British study of 200 students found that eating bananas and other fruits high in potassium can help improve students’ concentration, learning efficiency, and performance.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203033.gif"></p><ol start="4"><li><strong>Improve skin</strong></li></ol><p>For people with bad skin, it is recommended to eat bananas with yellowed skin. Bananas of this color are ripe and contain more vitamin B2 and vitamin B6, which have a better effect on preventing and treating skin problems.</p><ol start="5"><li><strong>Suppress gastric ulcer</strong></li></ol><p>Bananas have a soft texture and help relieve gastrointestinal disturbances. Bananas can also neutralize excess stomach acid and protect the gastric mucosa.</p><p>Ripe bananas often have black spots or brownish skin on the skin. Studies have shown that this brown-skinned banana contains phospholipids, which are rare in fruits, and has the effect of inhibiting gastric ulcers.</p><ol start="6"><li><strong>Reduce eye disease</strong></li></ol><p>Bananas are rich in carotenoids, which can be converted into vitamin A by the human liver, which is especially beneficial for eye health.</p><p>A study published in the American Journal of Agricultural and Food Chemistry found that eating a banana a day can improve eye health, reduce eye diseases, and reduce the risk of blindness.</p><ol start="7"><li><strong>Good for bone growth</strong></li></ol><p>Calcium, phosphorus, and magnesium in bananas are beneficial to bone growth, and also contain essential trace elements such as zinc, selenium, and copper.</p><ol start="8"><li><strong>Regulate emotions</strong></li></ol><p>The tryptophan contained in bananas can be converted into serotonin, which is an inhibitory neurotransmitter that promotes peace of mind, reduces pessimism and depression, and even reduces pain.</p><p>Bananas are delicious and nutritious, but they are not suitable for everyone.</p><p>The potassium content in bananas is high, and people with acute and chronic nephritis and renal insufficiency should not eat more. The glycemic index of bananas is 52, which is a low-glycemic index food, so diabetics can eat bananas in small amounts, but pay attention to reducing the intake of staple foods.</p><p>In this way, the bananas are not easy to grow spots and turn black</p><p>What causes banana skins to turn black is a gas called ethylene. As bananas ripen, more and more ethylene is released. So, by controlling the ethylene around the banana, you can control how quickly it ripens. Specifically, you can do this:</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203034.gif"></p><p><strong>Wrap banana rhizomes</strong></p><p>Most of the ethylene gas comes from the rhizomes of bananas, and wrapping the rhizomes of bananas can slow down the ripening process of bananas and prolong the preservation time.</p><p>If you want to keep bananas fresh for a week, take the whole banana apart and wrap the roots of each banana tightly with plastic wrap.</p><p><strong>Store at room temperature 13°C</strong></p><p>Experiments show that 13°C is the best storage temperature for bananas. At this temperature, bananas will ripen more slowly.</p><p><strong>Hang up bananas</strong></p><p>Hanging bananas with good ventilation allows the ethylene produced to travel with the wind, thereby slowing the aging of the bananas. In some supermarkets, you can see racks dedicated to hanging bananas. </p>]]></content>
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>This intestinal bacteria is on the &quot;carcinogenic&quot; blacklist! People with frequent diarrhea should be careful</title>
    <link href="/This-intestinal-bacteria-is-on-the-carcinogenic-blacklist-People-with-frequent-diarrhea-should-be-careful/"/>
    <url>/This-intestinal-bacteria-is-on-the-carcinogenic-blacklist-People-with-frequent-diarrhea-should-be-careful/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Intestinal flora is the general term for the microbiota that resides in the human gut, which is related to the immune system, endocrine system, and other metabolic pathways of the human body.</p><p>If the balance of flora is destroyed, the health status of the human body will also change, and constipation, diarrhea, enteritis, etc. may occur, which may even affect life expectancy.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203021.gif"></p><p><strong>This gut bacteria is on the ‘carcinogenic’ blacklist</strong></p><p>In a recent study published in the prestigious journal Cancer Discovery, researchers used enteropathogenic Escherichia coli and enterohemorrhagic Escherichia coli to assess the ability of adherent pathogens to induce bowel cancer.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203022.webp"></p><p>They found that adherent pathogens in the gut can connect to intestinal epithelial cells through their type 3 secretion system (T3SS) and inject genotoxins to damage the DNA in the host intestinal epithelial cells, leading to cell carcinogenesis and colon cancer.</p><p>In 2020, the international authoritative journal “Nature” published an important study on colorectal cancer, and scientists put forward evidence that infection with specific intestinal bacteria can cause cancer mutations.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203023.webp"></p><p>Escherichia coli are mainly epiphytes in the intestines of humans or animals, and most of them will not cause harm to the body, but can inhibit the reproduction of intestinal pathogens and other pathogens.</p><p>Some pathogenic Escherichia coli can cause diarrhea, hemorrhagic colitis, and other symptoms; and diarrhea, alternating constipation, defecation habits and changes in stool characteristics are important indicators for early detection of colorectal cancer</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203024.gif"></p><p>Therefore, when diarrhea occurs, don’t attribute it to excessive consumption of cold drinks, food deterioration, and other reasons. If you generalize, some diseases will become “fish that slip through the net”.</p><p><strong>For the following 5 kinds of diarrhea, it is recommended to seek medical attention</strong></p><ol><li><p>Acute diarrhea, accompanied by frequent vomiting, fever, severe abdominal pain, or accompanied by dizziness, palpitation, dry mouth, oliguria, and other symptoms of dehydration.</p></li><li><p>Acute diarrhea, no relief within 48 hours.</p></li><li><p>Diarrhea with bloody mucus or melena.</p></li><li><p>Patients with chronic diarrhea, but also with a history of colorectal polyps or cholecystectomy, or a family history of colorectal cancer need to be vigilant.</p></li><li><p>Patients with long-term constipation in the past have recently had changes in bowel habits or traits, and diarrhea.</p></li></ol><p><strong>5 types of Escherichia coli can cause disease</strong></p><p>Coliform is an indicator of food hygiene, including Escherichia coli, Citrobacter, Klebsiella aerogenes, and Clorox. Coliforms detected in food do not necessarily cause harm. However, the presence of pathogenic E. coli bacteria in the coliform flora can lead to foodborne illness.</p><p>There were three outbreaks of Escherichia coli in the United States in 1991, 1993, and 1996.</p><p>In 2014, there were more than 400 patients in the E. coli poisoning incident in Japan.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203025.gif"></p><p><strong>Pathogenic Escherichia coli are generally divided into 5 categories</strong></p><p>Enteropathogenic Escherichia coli: Water or egg drop soup in infants and young children.</p><p>Enterotoxigenic Escherichia coli: Most of them have no obvious abdominal pain, and discharge watery stools more than ten times a day.</p><p>Enteroinvasive Escherichia coli: Fever, abdominal pain, diarrhea, mucus, and blood in the stool.</p><p>Enterohemorrhagic Escherichia coli: early watery stools, later bloody stools.</p><p>Enteroaggregative Escherichia coli: associated with intractable diarrhea in children.</p><p>Children, the elderly, pregnant women, and those with weakened immunity are at high risk of pathogenic E. coli infection. Although most patients can recover in a short time, the harm of some pathogenic Escherichia coli should not be underestimated.</p><p>For example, the main pathogenic strain O157:H7 in Enterohemorrhagic Escherichia coli has strong acid resistance and can resist the digestive effect of gastric acid, and it is easy for people to be poisoned when eaten.</p><p>It not only produces Shiga toxin (causing dysentery symptoms), but also attaches to the intestinal wall, causing damage to the intestinal mucosa, causing bloody diarrhea and hemolysis characterized by acute renal failure, hemolytic anemia, and thrombocytopenia Sexual uremia.</p><p><em><strong>5 points to prevent pathogenic bacteria</strong></em></p><p>Escherichia coli poisoning is a typical “disease from the mouth”. Following the five key points of food safety recommended by the World Health Organization can effectively prevent foodborne diseases such as Escherichia coli food poisoning.</p><ol><li><strong>Keep your hands clean</strong></li></ol><p>Wash hands frequently, keep kitchen utensils clean; keep animals away from food.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203026.gif"></p><ol start="2"><li><strong>Raw and cooked food separation</strong></li></ol><p>Raw and cooked food are separated, and special kitchen utensils are used for handling raw food.</p><ol start="3"><li><strong>Fully cooked food</strong></li></ol><p>The meat, poultry, and seafood are thoroughly cooked, and the soup is boiled; cooked food should be thoroughly reheated.</p><ol start="4"><li><strong>Keep food at a safe temperature</strong></li></ol><p>Cooked and perishable foods are cooled promptly; refrigerators do not store foods for long; frozen foods are not thawed at room temperature.</p><ol start="5"><li><strong>Use safe water and raw materials</strong></li></ol><p>Choose a reputable business place to buy food; wash fruits and vegetables; do not eat spoiled food.</p>]]></content>
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Men in this age group should control their weight the most</title>
    <link href="/Men-in-this-age-group-should-control-their-weight-the-most/"/>
    <url>/Men-in-this-age-group-should-control-their-weight-the-most/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Some people’s obsession with the figure is that if they weigh more than 100, they are fat; some people are fearless and let themselves become “balloons”.</p><p>According to the World Health Organization, at least two out of every five adults in the world are overweight or obese.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203061.gif"></p><p><strong>Men in this age group are the fattest</strong></p><p>In 2021, a research team led by the Chinese Center for Disease Control and Prevention will publish data on BMI and obesity in urban and rural areas in China from 2004 to 2018 in The Lancet.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203062.webp"></p><p>Data for this study were derived from six nationally representative health surveys completed by the China Chronic Disease and Risk Factor Surveillance Project between 2004 and 2018. A total of 645,223 people aged 18-69 were included in this analysis. The results show that:</p><p>Chinese people are getting fatter</p><p>The normalized mean BMI of Chinese adults increased from 22.7 kg&#x2F;m² in 2004 to 24.4 kg&#x2F;m² in 2018, mainly driven by weight gain rather than height change.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203063.gif"></p><p><strong>Where does fat grow most harmful to the body?</strong></p><p>When the human body stores subcutaneous fat, it also stores visceral fat.</p><p>A certain amount of visceral fat is necessary for the human body to support, stabilize and protect the internal organs.</p><p>However, when there is excess nutrition in the body, fat will continue to accumulate in the internal organs, which will lead to cardiovascular and cerebrovascular diseases such as hyperlipidemia, hypertension, diabetes, arteriosclerosis, heart disease, and metabolic syndrome.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203064.gif"></p><p>Visceral fat mainly exists in the abdominal cavity, such as the liver, pancreas, stomach, intestines, and other organs around and inside, and its obvious manifestation is abdominal obesity.</p><p><strong>Is your visceral fat excess?</strong></p><p>The easiest way to determine whether your visceral fat exceeds the standard is to calculate the ratio of waist circumference to hip circumference.</p><p>Test 1: Use a tape measure to measure the waist-to-hip ratio (waist-to-hip ratio &#x3D; waist circumference ÷ hip circumference).</p><p>Method: Stand upright, inhale gently, and measure the waist circumference above the navel and the most protruding hip circumference with a tape measure.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203065.webp"></p><p>If the waist-to-hip ratio is greater than 0.9 for men and greater than 0.8 for women, it indicates a high-risk group with excess visceral fat, and the second step test needs to be performed immediately.</p><p>Test 2: Test the subcutaneous fat on the waist and abdomen.</p><p>Method: Try pinching around the belly button. If you can easily pinch up 2 cm, it means that the accumulation of subcutaneous fat;</p><p><strong>How to lose weight if you are already fat?</strong></p><p>Regarding weight loss, the World Health Organization’s recommendation is to lose 0.5 to 1 kilogram per week and 1 to 3 kilograms per month. This “uniform” weight-loss method has little damage to the body and is not easy to rebound.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203066.gif"></p><p>Weight loss is about fat loss, and fat is also a whole body. It can only be reduced in proportion to the whole body. Partial fat loss is unscientific. Only a combination of diet, aerobic, and strength training will slowly lose weight throughout the body. The specific methods are as follows:</p><ol><li><strong>Eat less high-sugar and high-fat foods</strong></li></ol><p>In terms of diet, control the intake of carbohydrates and fats, and eat less polished rice, noodles, and sweets.</p><p>Low-quality carbohydrates (that is, foods with a high glycemic index) may be less healthy than most dietary fats.</p><p>The most conducive to weight control staple food: oats, brown rice, quinoa, buckwheat, etc. These whole grains have a strong sense of satiety and are cooked with rice in a 1:3 ratio, which is great for weight control.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203067.gif"></p><p>Eat more fiber, eat more whole grains, vegetables, fruits, beans, etc., and increase high-quality protein, such as fish, chicken, eggs, milk, and soy products.</p><ol start="2"><li><strong>Eat three meals regularly</strong></li></ol><p>People who often skip dinner will lead to weight gain.</p><p>The reason is that fasting at night may lead to retaliatory eating at breakfast and lunch the next day, and the intake of calories exceeds the standard, which is not conducive to weight control. So if you want to lose weight, eating regularly is the key.</p><ol start="3"><li><strong>Do more aerobic exercise</strong></li></ol><p>People with a good physique can do moderate-intensity exercises, such as brisk walking, jogging, cycling, and Tai Chi. Fitness experts can participate in sports such as running, fast mountain climbing, stair climbing, and tennis.</p><p>The best exercise intensity is more than 60% of your maximum heart rate (maximum heart rate is 220 minus your age). The exercise time for each exercise should be at least 20 minutes, and 40 to 60 minutes is recommended.</p><ol start="4"><li><strong>High-intensity interval training</strong></li></ol><p>High-intensity interval training is a combination of high-intensity exercise, low-intensity relaxation, and rest. For example, use a faster pace or climb for 3 minutes, then walk slowly on flat terrain for 2 minutes, repeating 6 times in 30 minutes.</p><p>In this way, the stimulation to the body is small, so that the human body is in a more stable and comfortable exercise state, thereby increasing the speed of fat burning.</p><ol start="5"><li><strong>Guaranteed 7-9 hours of sleep</strong></li></ol><p>People who slept 7 to 9 hours per night had a 28% to 35% lower risk of abdominal obesity than those who slept less than 5 hours per night.</p><p>The last thing to note is: weight loss needs to be gradual. If you lose weight too quickly, it may cause problems such as weakness, hair loss, depression, and arrhythmia.</p>]]></content>
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>The most &quot;powerful&quot; muscle in the cheek, everyone should practice</title>
    <link href="/The-most-powerful-muscle-in-the-cheek-everyone-should-practice/"/>
    <url>/The-most-powerful-muscle-in-the-cheek-everyone-should-practice/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>As we age, many people find their faces become larger and more square.</p><p>This phenomenon is a plus when it happens to cats, but if it happens to people…</p><p>In fact, it has something to do with a muscle in the cheek.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203011.webp"></p><p><strong>Masseter muscle, the most powerful masticatory muscle in the human body</strong></p><p>When we say that people “Chubby Cheeks”, we often mean that the sides of the chin have become fatter, or the chin itself has changed. One of the common types is the masseter-type Chubby Cheeks.</p><p> <img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203012.webp"></p><p>The masseter muscle is the most powerful masticatory muscle in the human body and is the main performer of the bite action. Under the innervation of the trigeminal nerve, when the masseter muscle contracts, the mandible is pulled upward, and the upper and lower teeth are clenched to crush hard food.</p><p>The muscle fibers of the masseter muscle are relatively thick and have a certain facial support function. The appearance of the middle and lower part of the face will be affected by it.</p><p>Many people feel that their faces have become larger, squared, and “Chubby Cheeks”, and it may be that their masseter muscles have become “stronger”.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203013.gif"></p><p>The largest of the muscle groups attached to the jawbone is the masseter muscle, also known as the masseter muscle.</p><p>The mandible is the bone that supports the jaw. It connects with the temporal bones on both sides to form the temporomandibular joint, where our teeth grow.</p><p>If you want to judge whether your masseter muscles have become “strong”, you can test yourself according to the following methods:</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203014.gif"></p><p>If you’re not gaining weight and you can feel a raised, tight muscle when you bite your back teeth, you’re more likely to have a masseter hypertrophy.</p><p><strong>Masseter muscles are strong, people can live longer</strong></p><p>The masseter muscle is one of the most critical muscles in the human body, and regular exercise can help delay aging and prolong life.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203015.gif"></p><p>Recently, in a study published in the “Annals of Anatomy”, researchers at the University of Basel in Switzerland found that there is a third layer of muscle tissue in the masseter muscle, known as the “masseter coronoid muscle”.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203016.webp"></p><p>This new layer of muscle may help stabilize the jaw by elevating and contracting the coronoid process, the only part of the masseter muscle that pulls the jaw back and is essential for chewing.</p><p>The masseter muscle is key to longevity, stronger masseter muscle, younger brain. Some people can bite hard fruits when they are young, but as they get older, they can’t even eat some glutenous things, which also affects their nutritional intake and mood.</p><p>In 2017, a study in the American Journal of Geriatrics pointed out that the strength of chewing can also predict the risk of Alzheimer’s disease. The stronger the brain, the younger the brain, and the lower the risk.</p><p><strong>Bad habits can “injure” the masseter muscles</strong></p><p>The so-called “use it and lose it”, many wrong usages will lead to “injury” of the masseter muscle.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203017.gif"></p><p><strong>Bad chewing habits</strong></p><p>People who usually like to bite hard objects, chew for a long time, and have a lot of times will have a stronger masseter muscle, which will lead to a wider jaw. In severe cases, it can cause dysfunction of the jaw joint.</p><p>Unilateral chewing will make the burden on one side heavier, while the masseter muscle on the other side cannot be functionally stimulated, and unilateral masseter muscle hypertrophy may occur, and the corresponding joints will be heavily stressed and damaged.</p><p><strong>Nerve problems</strong></p><p>Trigeminal nerve problems, trauma, mental stress, cold stimulation, night grinding, etc. may damage the masseter muscle, resulting in masseter muscle disorders, such as fascia pain, muscle spasm, etc.</p><p><strong>Aging</strong></p><p>People’s masseter muscle thickness increases by around 2mm during puberty and stops growing naturally after age 20 (women) and 22 (men).</p><p>With age, collagen is lost, muscle elastic fibers are aged and broken, the strength and support of masseter muscles will be relatively weakened, and facial relaxation or sagging may occur, and chewing ability will decrease.</p><p><strong>Masseter weakness</strong></p><p>When the masseter muscle is weak, it can be manifested as being tired from chewing, not chewing, and unable to eat hard food, etc., and the risk of malnutrition, aspiration, difficulty swallowing, and slurred speech is greatly increased.</p><p><em><strong>3 ways to train chewing power</strong></em></p><p>The strength of the masseter muscle is often referred to as masticatory power, and masticatory power weakens with age. Experts recommend the following three ways to exercise the masseter muscle.</p><p><strong>Bulging cheeks</strong></p><p>To train chewing force, you can use the method of “Bulging cheeks”, that is, let the cheeks move back and forth like a mouthwash, and do it 30 times quickly, which can stimulate the muscles of the cheeks and increase the chewing force.</p><p><strong>Pull battle</strong></p><p>Use your big molars to bite one end of tough food such as gummy candy and shredded squid, and gently pull the other end with your hand to feel the force of the masseter muscle.</p><p><strong>Practice knocking teeth</strong></p><p>When tapping the teeth, tap lightly first, the upper and lower teeth collide gently, and the speed is slightly faster; then bite and tap, the upper and lower teeth are like biting something, but the speed is slightly slower, and do it three or four times a day.</p><p><em><strong>What should I do if I don’t want the masseter muscle to become “strong”?</strong></em></p><p>For the sake of beauty, some people hope to reduce the masseter muscle to achieve the purpose of a thin face. Some opt for medical treatment, such as surgery to remove part of the muscle fibers or a “face-lift” (local injection of botulinum toxin).</p><p>Reminder: If you choose to inject face-lifting needles in irregular institutions, it is likely to cause the facial expression to be stiff after surgery, so that the masseter muscle loses part of its normal function and affects chewing function.</p><p>It can be achieved through some daily habits: reducing chewing, not eating too much hard food (nuts), etc. After a long time, the masseter muscle will naturally atrophy.</p>]]></content>
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>The more you lick your lips, the drier your lips become! Dermatologist&#39;s Essentials for Lip Moisture</title>
    <link href="/The-more-you-lick-your-lips-the-drier-your-lips-become-Dermatologists-Essentials-for-Lip-Moisture/"/>
    <url>/The-more-you-lick-your-lips-the-drier-your-lips-become-Dermatologists-Essentials-for-Lip-Moisture/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>For chapped lips, do not apply lip balm directly</p><p>Compared with other parts of the body, the lips are a thin layer of mucosal tissue, without sweat glands and sebaceous glands, and cannot secrete sweat and oil, so they are easily affected by the external environment.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202281.gif"></p><p>When the weather is dry, the lips are prone to dryness and peeling. When the lips appear erythema, dryness, scaling, chapped, edema, itching, or even burning, they may be suffering from cheilitis.</p><p>At this time, lip balm comes in handy.</p><p><strong>Clean your lips before applying lip balm</strong></p><p>Eat and drink water during the day, even if you apply lip balm, it will fall off, so it is recommended to apply it at night. Apply a lip balm before bed to moisturize overnight until the next morning, and your lips won’t be less prone to dryness.</p><p><strong>If it is dry and cracked, apply water first, then apply lip balm</strong></p><p>When the lips are already chapped, applying lipstick directly may not be effective, it is best to apply it with water first.</p><p>If there is chapped bleeding, it is best to pour cool pure water on a cotton pad and apply it on the lips to effectively stop the bleeding.</p><p>If it is only dry and there is no chapped bleeding, it is recommended to apply a damp and hot towel on the lips, which can effectively soften the lips, allow the lips to fully absorb moisture, and then apply lip balm to lock in the moisture.</p><p><strong>Choose lip balms and avoid those with these ingredients</strong></p><p>To prevent lip problems, avoid licking or biting your lips on weekdays. Although this can temporarily moisten your mouth, it will evaporate the moisture of the lips and aggravate dryness. When molting occurs, do not tear it with your hands, otherwise, it will aggravate the inflammation.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202282.gif"></p><p>When choosing a lip balm, be sure to read the ingredient list carefully. Some products contain chemical ingredients that can irritate the lips; choose a lip balm product with little irritation, good moisturizing effect, and reliable ingredients.</p><p><strong>Salicylic acid, phenol</strong></p><p>Lipsticks that contain exfoliating ingredients such as salicylic acid and phenol should be purchased and used with caution. Salicylic acid works primarily by softening the cuticle, then peeling it off, quickly letting the dead skin on the lips leave.</p><p>The skin on our lips is extraordinarily thin, it is only about one-third as thick as the nearby skin. Regular use of lip balm containing salicylic acid can make lips thinner and more prone to chapped lips.</p><p><strong>Mineral oil, mineral wax, or microcrystalline wax</strong></p><p>These ingredients seal in especially well, like wrapping a layer of plastic wrap around your mouth. When they wrap around your lips, the lips will feel very wet and slack off. Over time, dependence will reduce the moisturizing ability of the lips.</p><p><strong>Camphor or menthol</strong></p><p>These ingredients will cool your mouth. Camphor is toxic to a certain extent and should not be applied to the mouth; while menthol will accelerate the evaporation of water.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202283.gif"></p><p><strong>Recommended ingredients:</strong></p><p>Moisturizing + Repairing Skin Barrier Selection contains these ingredients: Sodium Hyaluronate, Ceramide, Squalane;</p><p>The water lock contains these ingredients: castor oil, jojoba oil, petroleum jelly.</p><p><strong>Recommended ingredients for severely chapped lips:</strong></p><p>The chapped lips are particularly serious and even dry to the point of peeling. The lip balm you choose should preferably contain allantoin, glycyrrhizic acid, vitamin E, and, other special ingredients that can be anti-inflammatory, calm, and repair the lip skin.</p><p><em><strong>3 things every day to keep your lips away from dryness</strong></em></p><p>Loss of water is fast and it is difficult to lock in water. As a “vulnerable group” in the human body, the lips need your careful care.</p><p> <img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202284.gif"></p><p><strong>Strengthen moisturizing</strong></p><p>Drink plenty of water at ordinary times and use a humidifier when necessary to improve the humidity of the environment. The correct choice of lip balm products, pay attention not to use frequently, it is generally recommended to use about 3 times a day.</p><p><strong>Conditioning diet</strong></p><p>Eat more eggs, dried fruits, beans, and fresh vegetables and fruits every day. These foods are rich in vitamin C and vitamin B2, which can nourish the lips.</p><p><strong>Reduce external stimuli</strong></p><p>Try to avoid external stimuli such as wind and sun, and wear a mask when going out to reduce the evaporation of moisture from the lips.</p><p>If the chapped lips are still not relieved after self-care, or even more serious, it is best to go to a regular hospital specialist to avoid delaying the treatment time.</p><p><em><strong>Tip: Lipstick should be applied vertically</strong></em></p><p>This is because the lines on the lips are vertical, but when people apply lipstick, they almost always apply it horizontally, which makes it difficult for the active ingredients to fully penetrate and nourish the lip lines, and even aggravate wrinkles, making it easier to dry and crack.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202285.webp"></p><p>If you already have small cracks under your lip lines, it is easy to tear these small holes again when applying lipstick horizontally.</p><p>Apply lipstick vertically, in line with the law of lip lines, and the moisturizing effect is longer.</p><p>However, be aware that the skin on the lips is very fragile, so apply the lipstick gently to avoid irritation. When the weather is cold, the paste tends to become hard. It is best not to apply it directly, but to apply it with fingers, cotton swabs, or brushes.</p>]]></content>
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>What kind of tea is considered &quot;strong tea&quot;? These 7 types of people should not drink</title>
    <link href="/What-kind-of-tea-is-considered-strong-tea-These-7-types-of-people-should-not-drink/"/>
    <url>/What-kind-of-tea-is-considered-strong-tea-These-7-types-of-people-should-not-drink/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Tea is one of the most popular beverages and drinking tea has been around for thousands of years.</p><p>Some people like to drink strong tea, thinking that strong tea is rich and rich, and the taste is distinct; some people like light tea, thinking that light tea is fresh and elegant, which can not only quench thirst but also maintain health.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202271.webp"></p><p><strong>What is considered “strong tea”?</strong></p><p>The main functional components in tea are tea polyphenols, caffeine, and theanine. Among them, tea polyphenols make tea astringent, caffeine brings a bitter taste to tea, and theanine makes tea taste fresher.</p><p>At present, there is no uniform definition of strong tea. When there are too many tea leaves, the bitterness of the tea soup will increase, the freshness will be relatively weakened, and the color of the tea soup will become stronger, which is often referred to as strong tea.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202272.gif"></p><p>However, the strength of tea is related to personal taste and feeling, and there is no absolute measure.</p><p>Tea addicts who have been drinking tea for many years have become accustomed to the bitter taste of tea, and the strong tea in the eyes of ordinary people may not be strong for them.</p><p>Those who do not drink tea often or who are used to drinking weak tea will not be able to accept it if it is slightly thicker.</p><p>From a health point of view and taste, strong tea is suitable for tea lovers, and tea of suitable strength is suitable for most people.</p><p>If the tea can be brewed according to the best tea-water ratio of each type of tea, the color and aroma of the tea will be maximized.<br>The standard tea dosage for most famous teas (green tea, black tea, yellow tea, scented tea) is 1 gram of dry tea with 50 ml of water, that is, the ratio of tea to water is 1:50;</p><p>The ratio of tea to water for ordinary bulk tea (green tea, black tea, yellow tea, scented tea) is 1:75.</p><p>The amount of black tea, white tea, and oolong tea should be more. The tea-water ratio of dark tea is 1:50<del>1:30, the tea-water ratio of white tea is 1:25</del>1:20, and the tea-water ratio of oolong tea is 1: 15 or so.</p><p><em><strong>The following categories of people should try to avoid drinking strong tea:</strong></em></p><ol><li><strong>Children and adolescents</strong></li></ol><p>The caffeine in strong tea will excite the central nervous system, shorten the child’s deep sleep time, and may affect the child’s growth and development.</p><ol start="2"><li><strong>Women in special times</strong></li></ol><p>For women who are in the menstrual period, pregnancy, or breastfeeding period, drinking a lot of strong tea for a long time will hinder the absorption of iron and cause iron-deficiency anemia. Excessive intake of caffeine also affects the development of fetuses and infants.</p><ol start="3"><li><strong>Those who are sensitive to caffeine</strong></li></ol><p>Such people should not only avoid strong tea, but also avoid tea as much as possible in the afternoon and evening, so as not to affect sleep.</p><ol start="4"><li><strong>People with poor gastrointestinal function</strong></li></ol><p>Some people will feel uncomfortable in the stomach and intestines after drinking tea. The caffeine in tea can stimulate the gastrointestinal mucosa, promote the secretion of gastric acid, and aggravate the gastrointestinal discomfort.</p><ol start="5"><li><strong>Patients with high uric acid or gout</strong></li></ol><p>Caffeine is a diuretic, and moderate drinking of weak tea in patients with high uric acid can help reduce uric acid. However, if you drink strong tea, caffeine will decompose and produce new uric acid after entering the human body, which will aggravate the disease.</p><ol start="6"><li><strong>Drunk</strong></li></ol><p>Drinking strong tea after being drunk will increase the burden on the heart, and tea will accelerate the excretion of urine, so that the toxic acetaldehyde formed in the body is excreted from the kidneys before being decomposed, irritating the kidneys.</p><ol start="7"><li><strong>Those who take certain drugs</strong></li></ol><p>Tea polyphenols are easy to interact with metal preparations to cause precipitation. When taking metal preparations such as calcium preparations, iron-containing blood supplements or iron-containing preparations, aluminum-containing preparations, cobalt preparations, silver preparations, etc., you should avoid drinking strong tea.</p><p>It is also not recommended to drink strong tea when taking hypnotic, sedative, antitussive drugs and enzyme preparations. Some Chinese herbal medicines, such as ephedra, Uncaria Chinensis, and Coptis Chinensis, should not be mixed with tea, and tea should not be drunk within 1 to 2 hours after taking the medicine.</p><p><strong>4 kinds of common tea have “specialties”</strong></p><p>Green tea, black tea, oolong tea, Pu’er tea… These common teas have different production processes, and each has its own health benefits.</p><p><strong>Green tea</strong></p><p>Polyphenolic compounds, such as catechins, are recognized as key components of green tea that are beneficial to health and have a variety of health care functions, including preventing cancer, improving cardiovascular health, and helping with weight loss.</p><p>Green tea is also the tea with the most types and richest content of vitamins. From the perspective of traditional Chinese medicine, green tea is slightly cold and helps to reduce the fire.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202273.gif"></p><p><strong>Black tea</strong></p><p>Black tea belongs to fully fermented tea. During processing, tea polyphenols are oxidized into theaflavins and thearubigins, and most of the sugars are hydrolyzed into soluble sugars, resulting in the unique aroma and taste of black tea.</p><p>Black tea is rich in theaflavins. A large number of medical studies have shown that drinking black tea can help regulate the content of low-density lipoprotein and high-density lipoprotein in human arteries. Theaflavins can also resist oxidation, prevent chronic inflammation and obesity.</p><p><strong>Oolong tea</strong></p><p>Oolong tea is also known as green tea. In addition to catechins, tea polysaccharides, tea saponins, etc., oolong tea also contains some special functional ingredients.</p><p>For example, some oolong tea varieties are rich in “methylated catechins”, which can help anti-allergy, anti-inflammatory, antioxidant, protect liver cells, and assist in lowering blood pressure.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202274.gif"></p><p><strong>Dark tea</strong></p><p>Dark tea is a post-fermented tea with rich minerals. Under the action of microorganisms, tea will undergo a series of complex chemical reactions to generate some functional components that are beneficial to the human body.</p><p>Pu-erh tea and Fu brick tea are representatives of different types of dark tea in my country, and their active ingredients are different, but they both help reduce lipids.</p><p><strong>Choose tea according to your constitution</strong></p><p>From the perspective of TCM health preservation, each person’s constitution is different, and the nature and taste of each type of tea are also different. According to the constitution and common manifestations in the “Classification and Determination of TCM Constitution”, the types of tea recommended drinking also have their emphasis.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202275.gif"></p><p><strong>Peaceful constitution</strong></p><p>The physique with normal functions is more coordinated, usually ruddy and energetic. You can drink all kinds of tea.</p><p><strong>Qi deficiency constitution</strong></p><p>It is manifested as being easily fatigued and weak, lack of breath and lazy words, or dizziness, and the complexion is a little yellow. It is recommended to drink Pu’er cooked tea, oolong tea, and eat it together with snacks made from soybeans, corn, peas, etc.</p><p><strong>Yang deficiency constitution</strong></p><p>Such people lack yang energy, fear the cold, and dare not eat cold food. People with this constitution can choose black tea, dark tea, and heavily fermented oolong tea (rock tea) to drink tea. Green tea, yellow tea, and Kuding tea are not recommended.</p><p><strong>Yin deficiency constitution</strong></p><p>Manifested as fever in the hands and feet, easy to dry mouth and throat, dry eyes, dry stool. Such people can drink more green tea, yellow tea, white tea, Kuding tea, lightly fermented oolong tea, less black tea, dark tea, and heavily fermented oolong tea.</p><p><strong>Blood stasis constitution</strong></p><p>It is manifested as dull complexion, dark tongue, or ecchymosis on the edge of the tongue, tongue tip, and tongue, often tingling in the body, and fish scale-like changes in the skin. If your tongue is pale and you are afraid of cold, you can drink black tea. If your tongue is red and your body is hot, you can drink green tea.</p><p><strong>Phlegm-dampness constitution</strong></p><p>Such people are mostly obese, with a plump and soft abdomen, prone to sweating, oily face, phlegm in the throat, and thick tongue coating. You can drink tangerine pucha, black tea, and dry ginger.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202276.gif"></p><p><strong>Hot and humid constitution</strong></p><p>Such people often have dampness and heat inside, the face and nose tip are always shiny, prone to acne on the face, itchy skin, and often bad breath. It is advisable to drink more green tea, yellow tea, white tea, Kuding tea, and less black tea, dark tea, and heavily fermented oolong tea.</p><p><strong>Qi stagnant constitution</strong></p><p>Manifested as thin, sentimental, emotionally fragile, and often feel pain in the breasts and flanks. Try to drink less tea with more caffeine, suitable for drinking hawthorn tea, rose tea, chrysanthemum tea, bergamot tea, tangerine peel tea.</p><p>Generally speaking, you can choose according to the warm and cool bias of tea: Yin and cold constitution, such as people who are often afraid of cold, suitable for drinking warm tea; positive constitution, such as people who are prone to dryness and heat, suitable for drinking cold tea; normal constitution , yin and yang balance, drink tea according to the season</p>]]></content>
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Magnify the tooth 1000 times, so you can see its truest appearance</title>
    <link href="/Magnify-the-tooth-1000-times-so-you-can-see-its-truest-appearance/"/>
    <url>/Magnify-the-tooth-1000-times-so-you-can-see-its-truest-appearance/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>In a sense, the mouth is the dirtiest place in the human body. It is estimated that there are more than 400 species of bacteria in the human mouth.</p><p>Plaque is a bacterial population that attaches to teeth. Using a microscope with a focused electron beam, the scientists magnified the tooth 1,000 times and photographed the tooth and its attached bacteria.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202261.webp"></p><p>Yellow plaque attached to the surface of the blue tooth</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202262.webp"></p><p>Dental plaque in the pink and purple coat</p><p>The staff made the pictures into color, to let people see more clearly the punctate bacteria lurking in the teeth and the plaque formed by the bacteria attached to the teeth.</p><p><strong>The culprit of periodontitis is plaque</strong></p><p>Bacteria in the oral cavity are not alone. They adhere to the surface of the teeth or the mucosal surface of the oral cavity through saliva and other substances to form dental plaque.</p><p>Even freshly cleaned teeth can develop new plaque in minutes. After 12 hours, the plaque will initially mature.</p><p>This plaque may irritate the local gums, causing periodontitis.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202263.gif"></p><p>The process by which normal gums develop into periodontitis</p><p>Dental calculus we often say is actually mineralized dental plaque. The accumulation of calculus will “run” under the gums, causing the gums to recede, eventually causing the teeth to loosen or even fall out.</p><p>Mild periodontitis manifests as red and swollen gums, bleeding from brushing, and bad breath;</p><p>Moderate periodontitis can cause inability to chew, sore gums, receding gums, and exposed tooth roots.</p><p>Severe periodontitis will cause symptoms such as tooth loosening, displacement, pain, inability to chew food, and eventually tooth loss.</p><p><strong>6 signs of plaque buildup</strong></p><p>If brushing is not timely or thorough, plaque can lead to tooth decay and calculus. When there is too much plaque, there are several signs that can appear early, and early identification can prevent oral problems from getting worse.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202264.gif"></p><ol><li><strong>The tooth surface is not smooth</strong></li></ol><p>When plaque builds upon the surface of the teeth, when touched with the tongue, the surface of the teeth will feel rough.</p><p>This often happens in the morning before you brush your teeth, and if it persists throughout the day, it could be a sign that plaque is building up.</p><ol start="2"><li><strong>Bad breath</strong></li></ol><p>Plaque contains bacteria, which produce an unpleasant odor.</p><ol start="3"><li><strong>Yellow teeth</strong></li></ol><p>When plaque “grows” on the teeth, the film can make the teeth appear dull white, or yellow.</p><ol start="4"><li><strong>Red, swollen or bleeding gums</strong></li></ol><p>Too much plaque can irritate the gums, making them swollen and painful, causing gingivitis. Bleeding when brushing your teeth after periodontitis.</p><ol start="5"><li><strong>Tartar buildup</strong></li></ol><p>When plaque is not removed for a long time, it hardens into tartar, calculus, which often appears at the junction of the gums and teeth and looks yellow or brown.</p><ol start="6"><li><strong>Sensitive teeth</strong></li></ol><p>Over time, plaque can cause gums to recede, which can make teeth feel more sensitive. Soreness when inhaling cold air, cold or hot food, or water.</p><p><strong>Brush your teeth after meals to prevent the teeth from being corroded by acid</strong></p><p>Periodontitis is a preventable disease. After eating, the oral environment will become “sour”. 12 minutes after a meal is the peak period of bacterial fermentation of carbohydrates to produce acid.</p><p>■ Studies have shown that the pH of the oral cavity begins to decrease after eating, and it drops to the lowest level in about 12 minutes. After half an hour, most people’s oral pH will return to normal levels.</p><p>■ The oral pH of some people with severe caries activity was lower than the critical value from the beginning; half an hour later, their tooth enamel was still in a demineralized state and was still fragile; after 1 hour, it had not returned to the normal level.</p><p>For most people, brushing your teeth early can interfere with and block this process, reducing the risk of acid erosion. Additionally, brushing your teeth once a day was associated with a 9% lower risk of cardiovascular disease and an 8% lower risk of diabetes.</p><p>Therefore, in addition to brushing in the morning and evening, it is best to brush after every meal. If not available, rinse your mouth with water.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202265.gif"></p><p>There is nothing wrong with brushing your teeth immediately after eating a normal diet. People who are worried about brushing their teeth to damage the enamel should pay more attention to the brushing method and the choice of the toothbrush.</p><p><strong>Ways to get rid of dental plaque</strong></p><p>Plaque may produce acid and decalcify to form dental caries, or secrete toxins against periodontal tissue. Therefore, the most important thing in daily dental care is to remove plaque to prevent dental caries and periodontitis.</p><p><strong>Brush your teeth with the Pasteur method</strong></p><p>When brushing your teeth, stick to the Pasteur brushing method, also known as gingival sulcus sweeping or horizontal fluttering.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202266.gif"></p><p>This cleans the plaque better without damaging the teeth and gums. Brush your teeth within 30 minutes after meals, at least 3 minutes each time, and choose a toothbrush with soft bristles.</p><p><strong>Use mouthwash</strong></p><p>Based on proper brushing, mouthwash can help inhibit plaque growth. If you choose a medical prescription mouthwash, you should first ask your doctor if it can be used for a long time.</p><p><strong>Use dental floss</strong></p><p>Simply brushing your teeth can only remove about 2&#x2F;3 of the plaque, and the rest are hidden between the teeth, under part of the gingival margin, and in the dead corners caused by the misalignment of the teeth, which can easily lead to adjacent surface caries, gingival inflammation and other symptoms.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202267.gif"></p><p><strong>Regular teeth cleaning</strong></p><p>Scaling is the most effective way to remove plaque and tartar. Brushing your teeth every six months to a year can prevent bleeding gums and loose teeth, effectively prevent periodontal disease, and help maintain oral health.</p><p><strong>Use a dental irrigator</strong></p><p>The irrigator can irrigate any part of the mouth through the nozzle, including between the teeth and deep gums where the toothbrush and floss are not easy to reach. It is recommended to rinse for 1-3 minutes after each meal.</p><p><strong>Use a gap brush</strong></p><p>For those with larger gaps, a gap brush can be used. Interstitial brushes are single-bristle brushes designed to remove plaque from larger interdental spaces, as well as aligners, fixed restorations, implants, gap retainers, and other hard-to-reach areas. The size of the gap brushes is different, which can be selected according to personal conditions and cleaning parts.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202268.gif"></p><p>To remove plaque, different groups of people should pay attention to different issues:</p><p>Elderly people with large gaps between their teeth can use more brushes. Middle-aged people are prone to get angry, and their gums are inflamed, swollen, and bleeding. Use a soft-bristled toothbrush. Children who have difficulty brushing their teeth can use an electric toothbrush.</p><p>It should be noted that if you use an electric toothbrush if you have bleeding gums, periodontal disease, or repair teeth, the speed should not be turned to the maximum.</p>]]></content>
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>What&#39;s going on inside your body when you laugh?</title>
    <link href="/Whats-going-on-inside-your-body-when-you-laugh/"/>
    <url>/Whats-going-on-inside-your-body-when-you-laugh/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Laughter is a part of being human from the first few months of life.</p><p>According to statistics, children laugh about 300 times a day on average, and adults laugh an average of 15 to 100 times a day. Women are generally more likely to laugh than men.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202251.gif"></p><p>Laughing produces a sense of happiness. What’s going on inside your body when you grin?</p><p><strong>People who love to laugh extend their life by four years, benefiting the whole body</strong></p><p>A summary of studies by the Spanish Society of Neurology found that people who laugh or smile live four and a half years longer than those who don’t.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202252.gif"></p><p>A good mood can strengthen the immune system, which in turn affects the health of the body. “Pleasant Emotion Therapy” in psychotherapy helps patients have a positive emotional experience.</p><p>When you grin, these changes are happening inside your body:</p><p><strong>Lower stress hormones</strong></p><p>Laughing once reduced levels of the three stress hormones cortisol, epinephrine, and dobachol in the body by 39%, 70%, and 38%, respectively.</p><p><strong>Stimulate serotonin secretion</strong></p><p>Smiling can promote the secretion of the neurotransmitter serotonin in the brain, and serotonin can reduce negative emotions such as irritability, enhance pleasure, and make people feel happy.</p><p><strong>Stimulate the immune system</strong></p><p>Laughter can reduce the level of inflammation in the body and increase the activity of K lymphocytes (a type of immune cells that play a role in fighting viruses, parasites, tumors, etc.). Therefore, laughter helps to strengthen the body’s immune system and protect the body from disease.</p><p><strong>Significantly increased pain threshold</strong></p><p>Laughing can relieve pain because it promotes the production of endorphins in the body. It is a natural pain reliever that enhances our ability to fight pain. When you’re suffering from illness, try to make yourself a little bit happier and maybe less painful.</p><p><strong>Blood circulation is improved</strong></p><p>When a person laughs, the blood flow to the organs increases and the blood circulation improves. In addition, laughter can also dilate blood vessels, increase blood supply to the brain, and lower blood pressure, so it can be called a “natural antihypertensive drug”.</p><p>In contrast to people who don’t like to laugh for a long time, a study by the Yamagata University School of Medicine in Japan found that men, smokers, inactive people, and diabetics are the majority of those who laugh less frequently.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202253.jpg"></p><p>Compared with those who laughed the most, those who laughed least often had a 1.95-fold higher risk of all-cause mortality and a 1.62-fold higher risk of cardiovascular events (stroke, myocardial infarction, angina, etc.).</p><p><em>6 cool science facts about laughter</em></p><p>Have you ever noticed that you feel refreshed every time you laugh out loud? The most common expression of a smile, in addition to making people feel happy, also hides a lot of scientific cold knowledge.</p><ol><li><strong>Laughing is an aerobic exercise</strong></li></ol><p>Laughing activates 53 muscles in the human body, which can exercise body parts such as the abdomen, shoulders, and diaphragm. Laughing for 10 to 15 minutes a day can burn 10 to 40 kcal.</p><p>A study by the University of Navarra in Spain showed that laughing 100 times is equivalent to cycling for 15 minutes.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202254.gif"></p><ol start="2"><li><strong>Laughing more improves concentration</strong></li></ol><p>A study by Kinki University in Japan proved that laughter can increase cerebral blood flow, improve cognitive function in the brain, and improve concentration.</p><p>After watching the video and laughing, people can concentrate more, answer questions faster, and increase blood flow in the frontal lobe related to brain activation by about 2.7 times.</p><ol start="3"><li><strong>Laughter strengthens relationships</strong></li></ol><p>Laughter has a strong social attribute. Early in life, a baby’s laughter is an external sign of happiness and helps strengthen the bond with the caregiver. Later, the laughter evolved into a sign of appreciation. Practicing a smile every day strengthens our social skills.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202255.gif"></p><ol start="4"><li><strong>Laughing more prolongs life than laughing</strong></li></ol><p>A study from the Department of Psychology at the University of Basel in Switzerland found that laughing every now and then throughout the day can help reduce stress and improve mood more than a one-time belly laugh.</p><ol start="5"><li><strong>Even a fake smile reduces stress</strong></li></ol><p>Smiling relieves physical tension and reduces stress hormones in the brain. People tend to frown when stressed, and even a fake smile can have a positive effect on stress relief.</p><ol start="6"><li><strong>Smile has region</strong></li></ol><p>In Strange Things, British psychologist Dr. Richard Wiseman says there is a clear geographic preference for what constitutes “interesting things”.</p><p>Americans usually like to tell jokes that contain a sense of superiority; continental Europeans tend to be light-hearted; British people are most easily amused by word games.</p><p><em><strong>How to make yourself a person who loves to laugh?</strong></em></p><p>A smile brings more than just that moment of happiness. People who laugh for a long time benefit from head to toe. I understand the truth, so how do you make yourself laugh?</p><p><strong>No.1 Spend more time with people who love to laugh</strong></p><p>A smile is contagious. Robert Provine, a professor of psychology at the University of Maryland in the United States, confirmed that just listening to recorded laughter caused subjects to giggle, which is why pre-recorded laughter is used in sitcoms.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202256.gif"></p><p>When laughter is heard, the area of the brain responsible for smiling automatically responds, displaying a smile that comes from the heart. You’re 30 times more likely to laugh when someone is around you than when you’re alone.</p><p><strong>No.2 Practice smiling for 10 minutes a day</strong></p><p>Smile practice is best done regularly several times a day, about 10 minutes each time.</p><p>If you can’t think of anything worth laughing about, you can pretend to be happy, and then gradually expand into a grin, and then you end up laughing.</p><p>A study published in Psychological Reports shows that forcing yourself to laugh (or even just smile) can improve mood. This is because the human brain cannot distinguish between genuine and fake laughter, and thus both achieve corresponding health benefits.</p><p><strong>No.3 Try watching talk shows and cross-talk</strong></p><p>A study by the International Cancer Center in Osaka, Japan found that cancer patients who enjoyed laughing while watching talk shows, stand-up comics, and counterpart comics had significantly improved immune function.</p><p>At the same time, the researchers found in the questionnaire that patients who often watched cross-talk felt their pain symptoms improve, and after enjoying a pleasant laugh, their tension, depression, and anger eased a lot, and their quality of life improved.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202257.gif"></p>]]></content>
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Is your sleep &#39;junk sleep&#39;? It&#39;s said to be worse than insomnia</title>
    <link href="/Is-your-sleep-junk-sleep-Its-said-to-be-worse-than-insomnia/"/>
    <url>/Is-your-sleep-junk-sleep-Its-said-to-be-worse-than-insomnia/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>When you wake up every morning, do you think you have enough sleep? Some people fall asleep when they touch the pillow, but feel groggy and powerless when they wake up… Scientists believe that these “Junk sleep” that “sleep equals no sleep” are even scarier than insomnia. Snoring does not mean good sleep, and sleep violence is also very bad. Oversleeping may lead to high mortality rate… A Japanese research survey shows that people who sleep 7 hours a day can live the longest, and the more sleep they sleep, the mortality rate The higher it is, if people who sleep more than 9 hours a day may have problems with their health. As the foundation of survival, sleep is closely related to our life.</p><p>Over the years, sleep experts from all over the world have been looking for a sleep rule that is truly suitable for human beings. In addition to the “Secret of the Biological Clock” that won the Nobel Prize in Physiology or Medicine before, there are many scientists on the road of sleep research. different discoveries. For example, according to the National Institutes of Health report, people who get 8 hours of sleep per night respond best, and if they get only 6 hours of sleep per night for 2 consecutive weeks, then it is equivalent to being forced to “stay up all night” for two nights. The surprising thing about the study is that people who sleep for 6 hours a night think they have enough sleep, but in fact their physical function and cognition are deteriorating without knowing it. Although they do not feel sleepy, their functional response is actually getting worse and worse. . Too little sleep is not good for your health, nor too much sleep.</p><p>The concept of “garbage sleep”, which was investigated by the British Sleep Commission, has once again aroused heated discussions in the academic circles. “JUNK SLEEP” corresponds to “JUNK FOOD”, which refers to the problem of insufficient sleep time and low sleep quality. Is your sleep like “garbage”? What is the correct sleep time? What are the dangers of sleeping too much? </p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/20202241.jpg"></p><p><strong>Which sleep is “Junk sleep”?</strong></p><ol><li><p>Falling asleep while watching TV, listening to music or playing video games;</p></li><li><p>Force yourself to go to bed and get up in the morning according to the “time point”, and the time “point” is always adjusted;</p></li><li><p>After waking up naturally, thinking of “staying in bed” again, forcing to prolong the sleep time;</p></li><li><p>Do not sleep at night, make up sleep during the day, make up sleep on weekends;</p></li><li><p>High work pressure, need to work overtime at night, fall asleep immediately after high-intensity work, etc.</p></li></ol><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202242.jpg"></p><p>How long should you sleep?</p><p>Sleep has certain health standards in terms of “time”. The British Sleep Association recommends that the best sleep time is 14 to 15 hours for infants aged 1 to 12 months, 12 to 14 hours for children aged 1 to 3 years, and 3 to 6 years old. 10 to 12 hours for children, 10 to 11 hours for children aged 7 to 12, 8 to 9 hours for adolescents aged 12 to 18, 7 to 9 hours for adults aged 18 to 65, and 7 to 8 hours for adults over 65. Sleep “time” is not the more the better, it should be moderate. Numerous studies have shown that excessive sleep increases disease morbidity and mortality, especially in the elderly population.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202243.jpg"></p><p>What are the dangers of sleeping too much?</p><ol><li><strong>Excessive sleep induces diabetes</strong></li></ol><p>The normal sleep time is 6-8 hours, and if it exceeds 9 hours, it becomes too long. Some studies have found that too long sleep can easily induce diabetes. Relevant surveys show that if you sleep more than 8 hours, the risk of diabetes will increase by more than 3 times.</p><ol start="2"><li><strong>People who sleep too long will become stupid</strong></li></ol><p>If you sleep for too long, people will become lazy. At the same time, because the sleep time is too long and the brain rests for too long, the cell activity of the brain will decrease. Because the sleep time is too long, the nerve cells will be inhibited for a long time. Over time, it will affect intelligence, lead to memory decline, and make people more and more stupid.</p><ol start="3"><li><strong>Easier to die</strong></li></ol><p>Relevant data show that people who sleep 7 hours a day have the lowest mortality rate, less than 6 hours will increase the risk of death, and more than 9 hours will also increase the risk of death. And the results of this statistic are not divided between men and women. Therefore, the more sleep is not the better, everything is counterproductive, less is detrimental to health, and more will also endanger life.</p><ol start="4"><li><strong>Weight gain</strong></li></ol><p>Researchers looked at weight and fat gain in Quebec adults over a six-year period. They found that people who slept too little and too long each night gained more weight than those who slept seven or eight hours. During the study period, people who slept 9 to 10 hours per night were 25% more likely to gain 5kg, even with controlled food intake and increased physical activity. Therefore, these results underscore the need to consider sleep duration in weight gain and obesity, the researchers wrote in the study.</p>]]></content>
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Anti-inflammatory diets go viral! What are the anti-inflammatory foods?</title>
    <link href="/Anti-inflammatory-diets-go-viral!-What-are-the-anti-inflammatory-foods/"/>
    <url>/Anti-inflammatory-diets-go-viral!-What-are-the-anti-inflammatory-foods/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Many diseases that plague the human body have a common feature - inflammation.</p><p>Recently, many food bloggers have begun to introduce a magical “anti-inflammatory diet” that claims to enhance the body’s immunity and reduce the risk of inflammatory infections.</p><p>Not only are there “anti-inflammatory diets,” but there are plenty of foods that can exacerbate inflammation. Are these eye-catching claims true?</p><p><em><strong>What is the “inflammation” of an “anti-inflammatory diet”?</strong></em></p><p><strong>The “inflammation” in an anti-inflammatory diet is not the same as the “inflammation” we often talk about caused by viruses or bacteria.</strong></p><p>Inflammation is a defense response of the body’s own immune system to external stimuli. The immune system is like a guard that protects the body. When there is trauma or infection, the immune system will be activated, and the guard will respond quickly, engulfing invading viruses and bacteria or clearing itself. The necrotic tissue, we call this inflammation caused by bacterial or viral invasion as acute inflammation, which comes and goes quickly.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202231.webp"></p><p>The “inflammation” in the anti-inflammatory diet is chronic inflammation, which is the low level of excessive production of various cytokines (interleukin, tumor necrosis factor TNF-α and interferon γ-INF, etc.) under stress or stress. level of chronic inflammation.</p><p>This inflammation can develop gradually over months or years and affect the immune system. At this time, the immune system is in a state of protracted war, always vigilant but tired and irritable, and it is easy to miss the gun.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202232.webp"></p><p><strong>This repeated and sustained immune response often brings harm to the body. Studies have shown that chronic inflammation is associated with many chronic diseases</strong>, such as obesity, type 2 diabetes, cardiovascular disease, chronic respiratory disease, psoriasis, rheumatoid arthritis, cancer Wait.</p><p>A 32-year report involving 210,000 participants published in 2020 by the Department of Nutrition at the Harvard School of Public Health shows that <strong>cardiovascular health is associated with an inflammatory state in the body, and food can exacerbate or improve the inflammatory state in the body.</strong></p><p><em><strong>What does an “anti-inflammatory diet” include?</strong></em></p><p>Since different foods have different effects on inflammation in the body, it is necessary to understand the anti-inflammatory or pro-inflammatory effects of different foods.</p><p>Overall, <strong>red meat, overly processed foods, and foods high in sugar and oil tend to lead to more inflammation in the body.</strong></p><p>Red meat contains a sialic acid molecule, Neu5Gc, which is not found in the human body. It is recognized by the immune system as a foreign invader, causing inflammation. Animal experiments have shown that long-term consumption of large amounts of red meat will increase the risk of cancer in mice.</p><p>Unprocessed foods such as white bread, sugar-sweetened beverages, salad dressings, and processed meat products are generally high in sugar, salt, and fat, and contain a lot of trans fatty acids, which can easily lead to chronic inflammation in the body.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202233.webp"></p><p><strong>Food components that improve chronic inflammation include omega-3 fatty acids, polyphenols, dietary fiber, and natural antioxidants</strong>; these substances can block signaling, inhibit prostate cyclooxygenase expression, downregulate levels of inflammatory mediators, and activate antioxidants. It can also exert an anti-inflammatory effect by adjusting the intestinal flora and producing short-chain fatty acids.</p><p><strong>The biological activity of anti-inflammatory foods has been validated in cell and mouse models, but inconclusive in human studies</strong>. In a review published in Critical Reviews in Food Science and Nutrition in 2021, <strong>the research team selected 88 foods with anti-inflammatory effects from 3,581 studies, including: cranberries, grapes, pomegranates, strawberries, whole grains products, low-fat dairy products, yogurt, sesame seeds, flax seeds, soy foods, turmeric, etc</strong>.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202234.webp"></p><p>Combining the above studies, <strong>the researchers divided foods that may have anti-inflammatory properties into 6 categories</strong>:</p><p><strong>Vegetables</strong>, especially cruciferous vegetables such as kale, cabbage, broccoli, etc.;</p><p><strong>Fruits</strong>, especially berries such as cranberries, strawberries, blueberries, grapes, etc.;</p><p><strong>Foods rich in dietary fiber</strong> such as whole grains, legumes;</p><p><strong>Foods rich in polyphenols and flavonoids</strong> such as green tea, soybeans, etc.;</p><p><strong>Spices</strong> such as turmeric, ginger, cinnamon, nutmeg, sage, and garlic;</p><p><strong>Foods are rich in omega-3 fatty acids</strong> such as salmon, flaxseed oil, algae oil, grapeseed oil, canola oil, nuts, almonds, etc.</p><p><em><strong>Does the “Anti-Inflammatory Diet” Really Work?</strong></em></p><p>Although the Anti-Inflammatory Diet is very fashionable, However, it is not a specific dietary pattern. <strong>The Mediterranean diet, DASH diet (A salt-reduced diet for people with high blood pressure), the Okinawan diet, the traditional Nordic diet, and the traditional Mexican diet are all anti-inflammatory diets.</strong></p><p>These dietary patterns share the same characteristics: <strong>a plant-based diet with an emphasis on fruits and vegetables, whole grains, foods rich in omega-3 fatty acids, lean meats, and spices.</strong></p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202235.webp"></p><p>Although the effect of diet on chronic inflammation has not been clearly quantified, some studies have shown positive effects. A 2016 study found that after one year of anti-inflammatory diet in patients with type 2 diabetes, the inflammatory factor-CRP in their blood was reduced by 37%. produced a suppressive effect.</p><p>These results are exciting, but the human body is very complex. To improve immunity and reduce the occurrence of chronic inflammation, one should not be superstitious about a certain legendary diet. In addition to a balanced diet, it is best to start from four aspects:</p><p><strong>Exercise</strong>: 30 minutes of moderate exercise every day, aerobic exercise is very effective in improving immunity.</p><p><strong>Reduced pressure</strong>: Long-term stress and tension will increase the level of inflammation in the human body. Maintaining an optimistic attitude and good habits is conducive to controlling the level of inflammatory factors in the body. Regular sleep also helps to slow down the accumulation of inflammatory factors.</p><p><strong>Weight contro</strong>l: Obesity can lead to hormonal and immune system disturbances and exacerbate chronic inflammation, so balance diet and exercise to maintain an appropriate weight and BMI.</p><p><strong>Get rid of bad habits and have regular physical examinations</strong>: smoking and drinking are recognized bad habits, which will increase the level of inflammatory cytokines in the blood; carry out regular physical examinations to detect potential risks of the body in time; if you have suffered from gastritis, pharyngitis, hepatitis Other inflammations or autoimmune diseases such as lupus erythematosus, arthritis, etc., require more detailed and scientific lifestyle and eating habits.</p><p>Allergy is also an important cause of chronic inflammation, so for allergic people, eliminating allergens is an important way to resist chronic inflammation.</p>]]></content>
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Obesity causes 35 diseases! Respiratory, nervous, and circulatory systems are all under  Pressure</title>
    <link href="/Obesity-causes-35-diseases-Respiratory-nervous-and-circulatory-systems-are-all-under-Pressure/"/>
    <url>/Obesity-causes-35-diseases-Respiratory-nervous-and-circulatory-systems-are-all-under-Pressure/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The number on the scale is a barometer of many people’s daily mood; it not only affects people’s emotions but also determines their health.</p><p>A meta-study published recently in the journal Biomedical Centre-Pharmaceuticals in the UK found that excess obesity is associated with an increased risk of 35 diseases.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202221.gif"></p><p><em><strong>Obesity causes 35 diseases</strong></em></p><p>A meta-study of 56 chronic diseases published in the journal Biomedical Center-Medicine found:</p><p>Obesity and type 2 diabetes, 14 circulatory diseases, asthma, chronic obstructive pulmonary disease, 5 digestive diseases, 3 musculoskeletal diseases, multiple sclerosis, and 6 digestive system cancers, uterine cancer, kidney cancer associated with an increased risk of bladder cancer for a total of 35 diseases.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202222.webp"></p><p><strong>Diabetes</strong></p><p>Genetically predicted high BMI [body mass index, BMI&#x3D;weight in kilograms&#x2F;height squared in meters] was associated with an increased risk of type 1 diabetes; higher BMI in adulthood was associated with an increased risk of type 2 diabetes.</p><p><strong>Circulatory system disease</strong></p><p>The risk of aortic stenosis was most strongly associated with high BMI, followed by heart failure and hypertension.</p><p>Obesity can increase the risk of type 2 diabetes and heart disease by increasing fasting blood sugar, triglyceride levels, and promoting systemic inflammation, the researchers said.</p><p><strong>Respiratory diseases</strong></p><p>The study found that the mortality of asthma and chronic obstructive pulmonary disease was related to BMI.</p><p><strong>Digestive system diseases</strong></p><p>A higher BMI increases the risk of several diseases, including gallstones, gastroesophageal reflux, Crohn’s disease, and nonalcoholic fatty liver disease. Of these, the nonalcoholic fatty liver disease had the strongest association.</p><p><strong>Musculoskeletal disorders</strong></p><p>Risks of gout, osteoarthritis and rheumatoid arthritis were associated with higher BMI.</p><p><strong>Nervous system disease</strong></p><p>The risk of multiple sclerosis also increased with increasing BMI, but no association was found between Alzheimer’s disease, amyotrophic lateral sclerosis (ALS), and BMI.</p><p><strong>Tumor</strong></p><p>Higher BMI is associated with cancers of the digestive system (including esophageal, gastric, colorectal, pancreatic, liver, and gallbladder&#x2F;biliary tract cancers), uterine cancer (including endometrial, cervical), ovarian, kidney, It was associated with an increased risk of bladder cancer, but was associated with a reduced risk of breast and prostate cancer.</p><p>The researchers say that the association of excess obesity with chronic disease cannot be ignored, and from now on, a sustained reduction in the prevalence of overweight&#x2F;obesity should be a major public health goal.</p><p><em><strong>Obesity can be divided into 4 grades</strong></em></p><p>If the human body is compared to a heavy truck, the danger of being overweight is the same as overloading a truck. The more overweight, the more serious the damage and the shorter the service life.</p><p>For example, when a truck with a nuclear load of 5 tons is overloaded by 3 to 5 tons, it seems to still be able to drive normally, but in fact it has done great damage; if it is overloaded by 10 tons, the truck may face the risk of being scrapped at any time.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202223.gif"></p><p>To scientifically prevent and control obesity, you can refer to the following weight management models. The normal range for BMI is 18.5 to 23.9, 24 to 27.9 for overweight, and over 28 for obesity.</p><p><strong>Phase 0</strong></p><p>Overweight without associated disease or its pre-existing conditions (eg, hyperuricemia, prediabetes, hyperlipidemia, fatty liver).</p><p>Being overweight is a health warning line, and it is necessary to conduct lifestyle interventions promptly, such as changing habits such as overeating and drinking, always eating late-night snacks, and eating too much oil and too salty, and at the same time increasing the amount of exercise.</p><p><strong>Phase 1</strong></p><p>Overweight, with associated pre-morbidity; or obesity, without or with associated pre-morbidity.</p><p>At this stage, professional doctors are required to intervene, prescribing exercise prescriptions, formulating diet plans, etc., and patients need to strictly implement lifestyle interventions.</p><p><strong>Phase 2</strong></p><p>Overweight or obese with associated mild to moderate disease.</p><p>In this stage, in addition to the treatment of diseases and strict implementation of lifestyle interventions, scientific weight loss is also required. Weight loss drugs can be used under the guidance of doctors, or small weight loss surgery can be performed.</p><p><strong>Phase 3</strong></p><p>Obesity with associated severe disease.</p><p>This stage will seriously threaten health or longevity. If the weight does not improve within 3 to 6 months based on strict implementation of lifestyle intervention and weight loss drug treatment, weight loss surgery may be required.</p><p><strong>Weight loss advice for obese people</strong></p><p>How to avoid weight loss mistakes and manage weight scientifically and effectively? Experts from various countries have given specific suggestions.</p><p><strong>Prioritize cardio</strong></p><p>The European Society for the Study of Obesity recommends a detailed exercise training regimen, and the following are exercise recommendations summarized by multidisciplinary experts from institutions including the Sorbonne University in France, Maastricht University in the Netherlands, Padova University in Italy, and the University of Leeds in the United Kingdom.</p><p>It is recommended to prioritize 150-200 minutes of at least moderate-intensity aerobic exercise per week, or high-intensity interval training (need to assess cardiovascular risk).</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202224.gif"></p><p>Aerobic exercise and high-intensity interval training have similar weight-loss and fat-loss effects in overweight or obese individuals, as long as the energy expended are similar. Using these two methods, the average weight loss is expected to be around 2 to 3 kg.</p><p>High-intensity interval training (HIIT) raises your heart rate and burns more calories in a short amount of time. In layman’s terms, it is a combination of aerobic and anaerobic exercise that is interspersed with low-intensity exercise or a short rest between high-intensity exercise.</p><p>For example, the alternation of running 100 meters fast and jogging 100 meters, but paying attention step by step, gradually adapting to the training, and then appropriately adding more training movements until all training is completed.</p><p>To maintain the weight after weight loss, it is recommended to do 200-300 minutes of moderate-intensity aerobic exercise every week.</p><p><strong>Control fat intake</strong></p><p>It is recommended that obese people choose olive oil and tea oil for cooking, and control it at 20-25 grams per day.</p><p>When going out to eat, choose light dishes, try not to order dishes with a lot of oil, such as boiled fish and fresh food; get rid of the habit of overeating, and eat fewer snacks with a lot of “oil”, such as shortbread bread, puffs Wait.</p><p><strong>Protect the Achilles tendon</strong></p><p>Big data shows that because of their heavier weight, the Achilles tendon bears a higher force on the Achilles tendon during exercise than the general population and is more prone to injury.</p><p>Fully warm up before exercise, avoid vigorous and fatiguing exercise, and exercise more muscles, all of which will help prevent Achilles tendon injury.</p><p>Finally, for obese people, the World Health Organization’s recommendation is: “even speed” to lose weight.</p><p>Don’t worry, lose 0.5-1 kg per week and 1-3 kg per month. This method does little damage to the body and is not easy to rebound.</p>]]></content>
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Every time you listen, speak, read, and write, you are &quot;massaging&quot; your brain</title>
    <link href="/Every-time-you-listen-speak-read-and-write-you-are-massaging-your-brain/"/>
    <url>/Every-time-you-listen-speak-read-and-write-you-are-massaging-your-brain/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>You can’t speak fluently, your ears don’t work well, you can’t name things when you see things… When did you realize that you were suddenly “old”?</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202211.gif"></p><p>In the book “Changing Minds: How Aging Affects Language and How Language Affects Aging”, University of Memphis psychology professors Roger Cruz and Dr. Richard Roberts mentioned that aging is a two-way process, time plays a decisive role, but human intervention is Also important.</p><p>Through the learning and use of language, people can influence the cognitive aging process, promote brain health, and even prolong life and improve the quality of life.</p><p><em><strong>The more language you use, the better your brain becomes</strong></em></p><p>“Language is a very important part of cognitive function.” Cognitive function is a person’s ability to understand the external world, including memory, calculation, execution, attention, language, and orientation (including space, time, and character relationships). ).</p><p><strong>Listening, speaking, reading and writing protect cognitive function</strong></p><p>Clinically, some dementia patients do not have problems with memory, but have language barriers.</p><p>For example, the naming disorder, that is, the patient knows that the cup is used for drinking water, but cannot call the name; and the patient’s language expression is confusing, not fluent, and it is difficult to say a complete sentence. Language training for these patients can play a certain role. improve.</p><p>That is to say, the training of listening, speaking, reading, and writing has a certain protective effect on cognitive function. The famous “Nun Study” in the United States found that an individual’s early language ability may be related to the risk of Alzheimer’s disease.</p><p> <img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202212.webp"></p><p>The nuns participating in the study are playing a competitive scrabble game</p><p>The more developed the language function in the early years, the deeper the depth of thought logic, the better the cognitive function will be maintained in the later years, and the lower the risk of developing Alzheimer’s disease.</p><p><strong>Brains ‘get smaller’ from age 40</strong></p><p>Human brain development generally peaks between the ages of 20 and 40. From the age of 40, the number of nerve cells (neurons) in the brain gradually decreases, which affects memory, coordination, and brain function, and the size of the brain gradually shrinks.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202213.gif"></p><p>From a physiological point of view, people’s memory, reaction ability and executive ability will irreversibly decline with age, <strong>but language ability does not age with the body, on the contrary, the more it is used, the more developed it is.</strong></p><p>Many examples of “late bloomers” show that age does not impair people’s ability to speak, write, and learn new vocabulary, and even the ability to understand, use, and create language develops well in old age.</p><p>For example, Canadian female writer Alice Munro wrote her first novel at the age of 37 and won the Nobel Prize for Literature at the age of 82; British writer Daniel Defoe did not publish her first novel “Lu “Binson Crusoe”; Shandong writer Jiang Shumei began to learn and read at the age of 60, published her first book at the age of 74, and then published 5 works in seven or eight years…</p><p><em><strong>How Listening, Reading, Writing, and Writing Affect Brain Health</strong></em></p><p>Listening, speaking, reading, writing, and reading accompany people throughout their lives, which not only affects people’s cognition and personality, but also affects their brain health.</p><p><strong>Listening: Strengthening Cognitive Resilience</strong></p><p>One of the most obvious signs of physical aging is hearing loss. ENT experts at Johns Hopkins University in the United States have found that people with hearing loss have an accelerated decline of 30% to 40% in hearing and cognitive abilities.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202214.gif"></p><p>Hearing is an important channel for language input to the brain. The reasons for the accelerated impairment of cognitive function due to hearing loss may include:</p><p>Diseases that cause hearing deterioration can also impair cognition; hearing loss reduces stimulation of key areas of the brain, accelerating neurodegeneration; hearing loss affects information acquisition and depletes cognitive reserves.</p><p>A study published in the American Journal of Medicine found that as long as someone listens when speaking, the brain is more cognitively resilient. 4 years.</p><p><em><strong>Speaking: Exercise brain flexibility</strong></em></p><p>Talking is a benign stimulus to the brain and helps keep it alive.</p><p>If a person lives in isolation and no one speaks and communicates, not only will the ability to speak slowly deteriorate, but also loneliness and social isolation will occur, thereby reducing cognitive function.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202215.gif"></p><p>Clinically, some dementia patients also have problems with speaking ability, such as poor expression, difficulty in finding words, and difficulty in naming. Among them, <strong>the difficulty of finding words is a typical cognitive impairment problem</strong>, and suddenly cannot remember familiar things, names, but also proper nouns and object names.</p><p>Studies have shown that when a person reads instructions aloud, they tend to focus better and perform better than those who read them silently. If you need to remember a lot of information, especially in writing, reading aloud is the best way to do it.</p><p><strong>Reading: Boost your brainpower</strong></p><p>When reading, the brain must coordinate numerous perceptual and cognitive functions, including basic visual skills, phonological perception, long-term memory, and working memory.</p><p>When reading, in addition to paying attention to the current information points (story background, characters, details, etc.), you should also connect with the content you read before.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202216.gif"></p><p>There are hundreds of millions of information points in each book, and the brain needs to continuously remember this information and store it, which ultimately enhances memory.</p><p>Brain scans of people with an average age of 76 at the University of California, Berkeley, found that reading at an early age can prevent Alzheimer’s disease.</p><p>According to a study by the Rush University Medical Center in the United States, the elderly who regularly read and read newspapers have a 32% lower risk of mental decline than the general population.</p><p>A large-scale study led by the Yale School of Public Health found that people who read at least 30 minutes a day lived nearly two years longer on average than those who didn’t.</p><p>It should also be reminded that the carrier of this reading is a paper book, not an e-ink product.</p><p><strong>Write: Strengthen memory</strong></p><p>Writing activates the motor, visual and cognitive areas of the brain.</p><p>“Writing not only mobilizes cognition, but also the motor function of the body.” Shen Lu said that writing is the strengthening of memory. In the process of choosing words and sentences, both the mind and the body are well exercised.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202217.gif"></p><p>Gerontologists at Utah State University found that people who kept a diary throughout their lives had a 53 percent lower risk of developing cognitive impairment.</p><p>It should be noted that the four dimensions of language listening, speaking, reading, and writing can operate relatively independently. For example, a stroke patient may lose the ability to read, but not necessarily the ability to understand language and speak, and even continue to write.</p><p>Language ability “uses it and loses it” will also decline in the normal aging process, but maintaining and exercising language ability can optimize cognitive function and fight to age.</p><p><em><strong>5 small things to exercise language function</strong></em></p><p>Like physical exercise, language exercise should also be adhered to, especially for the elderly. Experts recommend starting from the following points.</p><p><strong>Keep listening</strong></p><p>When hearing loss occurs, you should seek medical attention or get hearing aids in time; listen to soothing and familiar music or stories from your youth to awaken pleasant memories.</p><p>Research from institutions such as the University of Toronto confirms that repeated listening to meaningful music produces beneficial brain plasticity in mild cognitive impairment or early Alzheimer’s disease.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202218.gif"></p><p><strong>Actively communicate</strong></p><p>The elderly should communicate more with their family members in their lives. For example, after watching TV and discussing the plot with their family members, they can not only exercise memory, but also enhance their feelings.</p><p>Participate in more social activities, such as speech contests, etc., to exercise language skills; maintain healthy social interactions, and refuse bad social behaviors such as gambling and alcoholism.</p><p><strong>Keep reading</strong></p><p>It is recommended that the elderly read more books and newspapers, at least 3 to 5 days a week, and read at least 30 minutes a day, which can not only help memorize words and knowledge, but also understand the latest information, so as not to be out of touch with society.</p><p>The material to be read should be scientific and slightly challenging, to mobilize the elderly’s thinking or learn new knowledge.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202219.gif"></p><p><strong>Develop the habit of writing</strong></p><p>Cultivate the habit of writing a diary, copying poems or words of interest, not only to exercise writing ability, but also to exercise work and motor functions.</p><p>The elderly can also read the written diary regularly to evoke memories and exercise memory function. Anxiety and depression patients usually write more, which can also reduce the symptoms of emotional tension.</p><p><strong>Try to learn a new language</strong></p><p>A new study from New York University shows that in addition to enhancing cognition, learning a second language can also broaden your horizons and add joy to life.</p><p>Experts remind that the decline in listening, speaking, reading, and writing skills often indicate cognitive dysfunction, and every change in function may be a signal of some diseases:</p><ol><li>The language fluency is decreased, and the language fluency test can be used for self-examination.</li></ol><p>Say the names of fruits, vegetables, or animals as much as possible within 1 minute, 14 with a college degree or above are considered qualified; 12 with a high school degree; 11 with a junior high school degree; and 10 with a primary school degree or below.</p><ol start="2"><li><p>Difficulty finding words, unable to understand other people’s speech, such as watching TV and unable to keep up with the plot.</p></li><li><p>The speech is simple and repeated. After the next sentence is finished, you do not know what the previous sentence is saying.</p></li><li><p>Difficulty in writing or reading, unable to write complex characters, unable to read newspapers.</p></li></ol><p>Once the above situation occurs, you should pay attention to it and see a memory clinic or a cognitive specialist.</p>]]></content>
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Quit smoking gradually VS Quit smoking immediately</title>
    <link href="/Quit-smoking-gradually-VS-Quit-smoking-immediately/"/>
    <url>/Quit-smoking-gradually-VS-Quit-smoking-immediately/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>A single cigarette produces at least 4,000 chemicals from lighting to burning out, 69 of which are identified as carcinogens.</p><p>A study published in The Lancet shows that quitting smoking early can prevent 28 diseases such as myocardial infarction and lung cancer.</p><p>Many smokers are aware of the dangers of smoking and try to quit smoking, but they are often unbearable with various withdrawal reactions and fail repeatedly.</p><p>From a scientific point of view, gradually quit smoking vs abruptly quit smoking, which method has a higher success rate?</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202201.webp"></p><p><em>Gradually quit smoking VS immediate smoking cessation, which one to choose?</em></p><p>Scientists from the Universities of Oxford and Birmingham, UK, conducted a randomized controlled clinical trial to evaluate the smoking cessation effect of “gradual withdrawal” and “immediate withdrawal”.</p><p>The researchers included 697 ex-smokers with established addictions and randomly divided them into two groups:</p><p>The first group is the “immediate smoking-cessation group”, that is, quit smoking directly and completely from the beginning;</p><p>The other group gradually reduced the amount of smoking 2 weeks in advance, reduced it to 1&#x2F;2 of the original smoking amount on the first weekend, reduced it to 1&#x2F;4 of the original smoking amount on the second weekend, and then stopped smoking.</p><p>In addition, both groups of participants received the same behavioral supportive treatment and short-acting nicotine replacement therapy to cope with the uncomfortable symptoms of smoking cessation and improve the success rate.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202202.webp"></p><p>The research team compared the smoking cessation effects of the participants at 4 weeks, 8 weeks, and 6 months after the start of complete smoking cessation.</p><p>The criteria for evaluating the effect of smoking cessation include the quitter’s oral and the exhaled carbon monoxide concentration of the quitter. The results show that:</p><p><strong>At 4 weeks</strong></p><p>39.2% of the people in the “gradual tapering group” quit smoking successfully without relapse; while 49% of the people in the “immediately stop smoking group” quit smoking successfully without relapse.</p><p><strong>At 8 weeks</strong></p><p>The success rate of smoking cessation was 29.2% in the “taper tape group” and 36.6% in the “immediate withdrawal group”.</p><p><strong>At 6 months</strong></p><p>15.1% of the “gradually tapering group” quit smoking successfully without relapse, and 22% of the “immediately stop smoking group” quit smoking successfully without relapse.</p><p>The above three groups of data show that the success rate of smoking cessation in the “immediate smoking-cessation group” is higher than that in the “gradually tapering group”.</p><p>The conclusion is clear: To improve your chances of quitting smoking, it is best to stop smoking from the moment you decide to start quitting.</p><p><strong>Smoking Addiction</strong></p><p><strong>Chronic diseases recognized by WHO</strong></p><p>The famous writer Mark Twain said: “It’s easy to quit smoking. I have quit dozens of times in my life.” A joke is enough to show how difficult it is to quit smoking.</p><p>Nicotine in tobacco is a highly addictive substance, which is an important reason for many “old smokers” to smoke for a long time.</p><p>After nicotine is inhaled into the human body, it will enter the brain center with the blood within 10 seconds, stimulating a sharp and short-term release of dopamine.</p><p>Dopamine’s euphoric effect wears off quickly once nicotine intake is stopped, leaving smokers unable to continue experiencing euphoria and experiencing withdrawal and cravings.</p><p>Therefore, addicts smoke cigarettes every once in a while to maintain nicotine levels in the brain.</p><p>It should be emphasized that smoking addiction (also known as tobacco dependence) is not a behavioral habit, but a chronic disease. The World Health Organization has included it in the International Classification of Diseases, coded as F17.2.</p><p>The study found that the brain structure and function of tobacco-dependent patients will change, manifested as gray and white matter atrophy, abnormal neural activity in the frontal lobe, temporal lobe, and limbic lobe, and significantly reduced functional connectivity of the insula-related brain regions, proving the pathological site of this chronic disease. in the brain.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202203.gif"></p><p>Tobacco dependence is divided into physical dependence and psychological dependence:</p><p>Physical dependence refers to a series of unbearable withdrawal symptoms, including irritability, anxiety, restlessness, headache, inability to concentrate, sleep disturbance, etc., after smokers stop smoking or reduce the amount of smoking.</p><p>Psychological dependence, also known as spiritual dependence, is manifested as a strong subjective desire to smoke.</p><p>Physical dependence and psychological dependence cannot be completely separated, and often coexist, which affects the success rate of smoking cessation.</p><p><strong>“Withdrawal” is the biggest obstacle</strong></p><p>The reason why quitting smoking is particularly difficult is often because of “withdrawal symptoms”.</p><p>In general, withdrawal symptoms are a normal phenomenon in the process of smoking cessation. They usually begin to appear a few hours after smoking cessation, are most intense during the first 14 days of smoking cessation, and gradually decrease until they disappear.</p><p>Therefore, relapse is most likely when you first quit smoking.</p><p>Most withdrawal symptoms last about a month, and there are steps you can take during this period to help you get through the toughest phase.</p><p><em><strong>How to deal with “withdrawal reaction”?</strong></em></p><p>For example, take a deep breath or go for a walk outside when feeling tense or irritable;</p><p>When you can’t concentrate, try to reduce the workload and take a short rest;</p><p>When feeling tired, be sure to get enough sleep and take a proper nap at noon;</p><p>When you always want to eat, choose some fresh vegetables and fruits instead of high-calorie snacks.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/20220204.gif"></p><p>It should be noted that some people still relapse after quitting smoking for several months or even years, generally due to inducing factors, such as high work pressure, sudden accidents at home, social gatherings, etc.</p><p>When encountering such a situation, one must firm up the belief that quitting smoking is to say goodbye to the cigarette completely, not to touch a cigarette again, and not to take a fluke mentality that “it’s okay to take a puff or two”;</p><p>Secondly, to avoid factors that induce smoking, stay away from other smokers, limit alcohol consumption, etc.;</p><p>Smoking can be replaced by some compensatory behaviors, such as drinking water, chewing sugar-free gum, taking a walk, listening to music, etc.</p><p>In this case, the craving for smoking will not last too long, and as long as you stick to it for a few more minutes, it is likely to avoid a relapse.</p><p><strong>Smoking cessation clinics may improve success rates</strong></p><p>Some smokers can rely on perseverance to quit smoking. For tobacco-dependent patients, smoking cessation clinics can help improve the success rate of smoking cessation.</p><p>Doctors will formulate personalized smoking cessation treatment plans according to the methods recommended by clinical smoking cessation guidelines, including smoking cessation advice, smoking cessation drug treatment, and other intervention methods.</p><p>The doctor will also regularly track and follow up on the smoking cessation situation to help solve the problems encountered in the process of smoking cessation.</p><p>Don’t be afraid of smoking cessation drugs. Smoking addiction is a chronic disease and the use of drugs is a very formal approach. There is ample evidence that smoking cessation drugs can relieve withdrawal symptoms and improve the success rate of smoking cessation.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202045.webp"></p><p>Whether it is an “old smoker” or someone who has recently become addicted, some preparations need to be done before quitting smoking to help quit smoking successfully.</p><p><strong>Determine a quit smoking day</strong></p><p>You can choose an important day, such as holidays, birthdays, anniversaries, etc. From this day on, don’t smoke again.</p><p><strong>Create an environment conducive to smoking cessation</strong></p><p>Before quitting smoking, dispose of all smoking-related items around you, including cigarettes, lighters, ashtrays, etc. at home, in the car, in the office, and with you, and try to create a smoke-free environment.</p><p><strong>Review past smoking cessation experiences</strong></p><p>If you have tried to quit smoking before, you can summarize your past experience and find out what helped you quit smoking and what was more likely to lead to relapse.</p><p>Especially for problems or difficulties that may arise in the first few weeks, such as nicotine withdrawal symptoms, and plan ahead.</p><p><strong>Team up to quit smoking or get personal supervision</strong></p><p>Tell family, friends, and colleagues that you have decided to quit smoking, and get their understanding and support. In addition, smokers around you should be encouraged to quit smoking together, at least not in front of you.</p><p><strong>Write a commitment</strong></p><p>It is recommended to sign a smoking cessation commitment letter with yourself, and you can also leave one for your supporters, which will help you get encouragement and supervision from others.</p>]]></content>
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>People with magnesium deficiency have poor anti-cancer ability! How to be an &quot;Mg&quot; eater?</title>
    <link href="/People-with-magnesium-deficiency-have-poor-anti-cancer-ability-How-to-be-an-Mg-eater/"/>
    <url>/People-with-magnesium-deficiency-have-poor-anti-cancer-ability-How-to-be-an-Mg-eater/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Many people think about supplementing calcium, vitamin D, and even iron when supplementing nutrition, but few people think about supplementing magnesium.</p><p>But in fact, magnesium is needed for many activities in the human body: activating muscles and nerves, increasing body energy, digesting protein, carbohydrates, and fats, etc.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202191.webp"></p><p>Magnesium deficiency can cause 21 conditions including anxiety and asthma.</p><p><em><strong>Study finds that magnesium may help immune cells fight cancer</strong></em></p><p>On January 19, 2022, a research team from the University of Basel in Switzerland published a study in the American journal “Cell”, showing that T cells can help immune cells fight cancer in a magnesium-rich environment.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202192.webp"></p><p>The experiment provided mice with cancer cells in a diet deficient in magnesium ions, and found that the cancer cells in the mice spread faster, and then supplemented with a diet containing magnesium ions, and found that the immune capacity of the mice was enhanced.</p><p>Further analysis found that in an environment rich in magnesium ions, magnesium binds to the T cell surface protein LFA-1, thereby increasing the immune capacity of T cells and effectively resisting cancer cells.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202193.webp"></p><p>T cells (blue) form immune synapses through LFA-1 to attack tumor cells (white)</p><p>Experiments show that:</p><p>Low levels of magnesium in serum have poor immunity;</p><p>Tumors locally increased magnesium levels, and T cells enhanced immune responses to cancer cells.</p><p>Using data from an earlier study in cancer patients, the researchers re-analyzed it and found that immunotherapy was less effective in patients with insufficient blood levels of magnesium.</p><p>Therefore, magnesium may be able to act as a “right-hand man” for the human immune system and play a role in promoting cancer treatment.</p><p><em><strong>The body sends these signals when magnesium is deficient</strong></em></p><p>In life, many people will have symptoms such as insomnia, depression, anorexia, and fatigue, which may be due to magnesium deficiency in the body. Magnesium is one of the essential minerals in the human body. When magnesium is deficient, the body will prompt 7 signals:</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202194.gif"></p><p><strong>Difficulty falling asleep</strong></p><p>Magnesium helps to increase levels of a neurotransmitter in the brain called gamma-aminobutyric acid (GABA), which promotes relaxation and sleep, helping to relieve sleep disorders.</p><p><strong>Depression</strong></p><p>Magnesium can improve human hormone regulation and brain serotonin levels, which is beneficial to blood sugar balance. Brain serotonin is essential for maintaining emotional stability, so magnesium deficiency is more prone to depression and anxiety.</p><p><strong>Migraine</strong></p><p>“European Journal of Neuroscience Research” has published research that magnesium can effectively reduce the severity and frequency of migraine symptoms, which is related to magnesium’s ability to regulate hormones and relax muscles.</p><p><strong>Eyelid jump</strong></p><p>One of the most common manifestations of magnesium deficiency is eyelid twitching. This is because magnesium regulates muscle movement, and when magnesium levels in the body are low, muscle spasms and twitching occur in many parts of the body.</p><p><strong>Abnormal heart rhythm</strong></p><p>Magnesium helps maintain a normal heart rhythm. Doctors give magnesium supplements intravenously to reduce atrial fibrillation and arrhythmias because magnesium reduces levels of nutrients such as calcium.</p><p><strong>Always feel tired</strong></p><p>Magnesium is an essential element of the human body’s energy production system, and the human body needs magnesium to generate adenosine triphosphate for energy production.</p><p><strong>Prone to skin problems</strong></p><p>Magnesium reduces inflammation in the body that can lead to skin conditions like acne, eczema, psoriasis, and more. Magnesium also regulates vitamin D levels and maintains healthy skin.</p><p><em><strong>6 types of people are prone to lack of “magnesium”</strong></em></p><p>Insufficient magnesium intake, malabsorption, or increased excretion can lead to magnesium deficiency, causing loss of appetite, nausea, vomiting, fatigue, and weakness.</p><p>With the increase of the deficiency, numbness, tingling, muscle spasm, arrhythmia, etc. may also occur, and even lead to hypocalcemia and hypokalemia. There are 6 types of people who are easy to be recruited:</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202195.gif"></p><p><strong>Calcium supplement population</strong></p><p>After middle age, calcium loss is faster than calcium deposition. The risk of osteoporosis is increased, and many middle-aged and elderly people will supplement calcium, but high calcium will competitively inhibit the absorption of magnesium.</p><p><strong>Unbalanced diet</strong></p><p>Middle-aged people tend to gain weight. People who don’t have time to exercise will lose weight by dieting, and hunger will affect the intake of magnesium. Some middle-aged people don’t like meat, but a high-protein diet will reduce the absorption rate of magnesium.</p><p><strong>Strong tea drinkers</strong></p><p>The caffeine in strong tea contains a diuretic component that increases magnesium loss.</p><p><strong>People with diabetes</strong></p><p>Middle-aged and elderly people are a high-risk group of diabetes. Diabetes increases the excretion of magnesium, and magnesium deficiency, in turn, reduces the working efficiency of insulin, forming a vicious circle.</p><p><strong>People who take certain drugs for a long time</strong></p><p>Some drugs such as bisphosphonates and tetracycline antibiotics can affect the absorption of magnesium, and some diuretics (such as furosemide, hydrochlorothiazide tabletsdiureticic acid) can increase the excretion of magnesium.</p><p><strong>Frequent drinkers</strong></p><p>Alcohol abuse can cause pancreatitis, alcoholic ketoacidosis, etc., and increase the excretion of magnesium. Long-term excessive drinking can easily lead to serious loss of magnesium.</p><p><em><strong>To become a “magnesium” eater should do:</strong></em></p><p><strong>Eat green leafy vegetables</strong></p><p>Leafy greens are the richest in magnesium, followed by whole grains, nuts, meat, and milk.</p><p>However, green leafy vegetables contain oxalic acid, which affects magnesium absorption, and whole grains contain phytic acid, which affects magnesium absorption. It is recommended to blanch the vegetables in boiling water before cooking them; when cooking coarse grains, soak them for a while in advance.</p><p><strong>There is no need to take magnesium supplements if you</strong></p><p>Drinking milk every day, eating meat, and eating more “magnesium” foods can fully meet the body’s magnesium needs, and there is no need to take magnesium supplements.</p><p><strong>Avoid these drinks</strong></p><p>Avoid beverages that cause magnesium loss in the body, such as alcohol, strong tea, coffee, etc., and drink plenty of water.</p><p><strong>A balanced and varied diet</strong></p><p>Usually moderate intake of fruits and vegetables, with staple food thickness. Reduce high-salt, high-fat diets.</p><p>If necessary, magnesium supplements can be taken in moderation under the guidance of a doctor. It is recommended that the calcium and magnesium intake ratio should be maintained at 1:1.</p><p>For children and the elderly, magnesium is more important than calcium; if the kidneys are not functioning well, magnesium supplementation must be evaluated by a doctor.</p>]]></content>
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>3 kinds of &quot;functional&quot; toothpaste that doctors are afraid of! These ingredients may induce enteritis</title>
    <link href="/3-kinds-of-functional-toothpaste-that-doctors-are-afraid-of-New-research-These-ingredients-may-induce-enteritis/"/>
    <url>/3-kinds-of-functional-toothpaste-that-doctors-are-afraid-of-New-research-These-ingredients-may-induce-enteritis/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Anti-moth, whitening, hemostasis, antibacterial, anti-allergic… Many people pay attention to the “function” written on the package when buying toothpaste and rarely look at the specific ingredients.</p><p>Recently, the international academic journal “Nature Communications” published a study: antibacterial agent triclosan (TCS) contained in some toothpaste may cause damage to the human intestine and induce enteritis.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202181.gif"></p><p><em><strong>This ingredient in toothpaste can induce enteritis</strong></em></p><p>The research, carried out by Tsai Zongwei’s team at Hong Kong Baptist University in collaboration with a foreign team, explains how the antibacterial agent triclosan (TCS) triggers intestinal inflammation.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202182.webp"></p><p>Studies have shown that after exposure to TCS, the intestinal toxicity of TCS is stimulated under the action of human gut microbial GUS enzymes, which in turn leads to the appearance of enteritis. By targeting the inhibition of gut microbial GUS enzymes, the harm of TCS to the human gut may be eliminated.</p><p>This study also further confirmed that TCS, a common ingredient in daily necessities, will cause certain harm to the human body, so you must pay more attention when choosing daily necessities.</p><p><em><strong>Dentists are afraid of 3 toothpaste ingredients</strong></em></p><p>According to the British “Daily Mail” report, many toothpaste ingredients are harmful to our health, Dr. Toby Talbert, a dental expert at the Royal College of Surgeons, reminded us to pay attention to these 3 ingredients:</p><p><strong>Descaler: It can easily cause mouth ulcers</strong></p><p>The oral mucosa is one of the most delicate tissues, and sodium lauryl sulfate is the most effective cleaning agent, which can cause irritation or damage the oral mucosa, leading to chronic oral ulcers.</p><p>People with frequent oral ulcers and those with ulcers are best not to use a toothpaste containing sodium lauryl sulfate.</p><p><strong>Whitening agent: easy to damage gums</strong></p><p>Bleaching agents such as hydrogen peroxide are added to many to toothpaste to whiten teeth. However, they can irritate soft tissues, damage the oral mucosa, and damage the gums.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202183.gif"></p><p>The whiteness of teeth is related to enamel and dentin, which is difficult to change with toothpaste. Although bleaching agents can remove some stains on the surface of the teeth, they have little effect on the deep stains that are endogenous to the teeth.</p><p><strong>Abrasives: can damage tooth enamel</strong></p><p>Fine particles are added to many to toothpaste to remove stains from the surface of the teeth, however, some ointments are not abrasive enough and can wear away the enamel, which can lead to sensitive teeth over time.</p><p>It is recommended to purchase toothpaste containing aluminum hydroxide or calcium hydrogen phosphate with fine particles. These abrasives are relatively good and cause less damage to the tooth surface.</p><p><em><strong>“Functional toothpaste” should not be used indiscriminately</strong></em></p><p>Toothpaste is used as a brushing aid. Its basic function is to clean the oral cavity. Generally, commercially available toothpaste can be satisfied after strict testing. The effects of whitening, anti-cavity, desensitization, and hemostasis are all auxiliary and are not enough to directly affect oral health.</p><p><strong>Whitening toothpaste:</strong></p><p>Mainly, some special “friction particles” are added, which can remove the cigarette stains and tea stains deposited on the surface of the teeth, but do not affect deep endogenous stains such as tetracycline teeth and fluorosis teeth.</p><p>If the friction particles are large and hard, long-term use may also cause tooth wear.</p><p>There is also some whitening toothpaste with blue paste, which can only achieve the “visual effect” of temporary whitening through the blue foam.</p><p><strong>Acid-proof toothpaste:</strong></p><p>The principle is to form a protective film on the surface of the tooth, thereby enhancing the disease prevention ability of the periodontal tissue, but it should be stopped after symptoms improve, otherwise it will destroy the microbial ecological balance in the oral cavity.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202184.gif"></p><p><strong>Antibacterial toothpaste:</strong></p><p>Some medicated toothpaste has bactericidal and bacteriostatic ingredients, which can help kill some bacteria in the oral cavity in a short time, but daily use is equivalent to taking a small number of antibiotics for a long time, which is not conducive to the microbalance of oral flora and is prone to drug resistance.</p><p><strong>Anti-sensitive toothpaste:</strong></p><p>Desensitizing ingredients such as fluoride and strontium chloride are added, which can only relieve mild dentin hypersensitivity to a certain extent.</p><p><strong>Fresh breath toothpaste:</strong></p><p>The freshness of the breath comes from brushing your teeth carefully, removing plaque and some harmful bacteria, not the fragrance of the toothpaste itself, so the “scent” of the toothpaste is not so important.</p><p><em><strong>Choose a toothpaste that suits you</strong></em></p><p>The use of toothpaste should vary from person to region and region, and should not be used blindly for a long time.</p><p> <img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202185.gif"></p><p><strong>Mainly depends on the quality of the friction agent</strong></p><p>Small particles should be selected to prevent damage to the tooth. The ones containing aluminum hydroxide and calcium hydrogen phosphate are better, followed by silica, and the particles of calcium carbonate are the largest.</p><p><strong>Change toothpaste</strong></p><p>Using a toothpaste for a long time, the bacteria in the mouth will develop resistance and learn to “resist” the effect of toothpaste to clean the mouth.</p><p><strong>Sharing a toothpaste</strong></p><p>Sharing a toothpaste can easily lead to cross-infection of many oral diseases. If someone in the family catches a cold or suffers from other oral diseases, some viruses and bacteria may remain in the crevices of the toothbrush after brushing.</p><p>The next time you brush your teeth, the toothpaste comes in contact with the toothbrush, potentially transferring the virus to the toothpaste and spreading it to others through the toothpaste.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202186.gif"></p><p><strong>Choose according to an oral condition</strong></p><p>For example, children can choose children’s toothpaste; family members with caries can use fluoride toothpaste; people with periodontitis can choose Chinese herbal toothpaste or toothpaste with anti-inflammatory ingredients.</p><p><strong>Some areas are not suitable for fluoride toothpaste</strong></p><p>Fluoride toothpaste can reduce the chance of cavities, prevent the surface of the teeth from being dissolved, and also make the dissolved teeth stronger. However, in high fluoride areas such as Shanxi, Inner Mongolia, and Hebei, the drinking water contains fluoride, so it is not suitable to use fluoride toothpaste.</p><p>Reminder: toothpaste is not a substitute for medical treatment. If you have oral ulcers, black teeth, toothache, caries, bad breath, etc., you should go to the doctor in time.</p>]]></content>
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Being with someone who makes you feel comfortable is also a regimen</title>
    <link href="/Being-with-someone-who-makes-you-feel-comfortable-is-also-a-regimen/"/>
    <url>/Being-with-someone-who-makes-you-feel-comfortable-is-also-a-regimen/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/Being-with-someone-who-makes-you-feel-comfortable.webp" alt="Being with someone who makes you feel comfortable is also a regimen"></p><p>Everything in the whole world is like a huge symphony. Walking with the big symphony of heaven and earth, walking in a normal and neutral way is the standard of health.</p><p>When you are sick, you are actually kicked out by God.</p><p>Therefore, the disease was called “disorder” in ancient times, and the cause was called “disorder” or “lost power”.</p><p>So what is health? <strong>Health is “normal”</strong>.</p><p>Health does not mean that you are ruddy, full of energy or something, not these things, nor how much muscle strength, how much heartbeat…</p><p>What is “usually”?</p><p><strong>The most important point is to be in a relatively harmonious relationship with oneself, with the society, and with this big world, and to be able to play with the natural rhythm.</strong></p><p>When the weather is hot, everyone else sweats, and you can sweat too; you can walk without getting tired after walking for two hours. But if everyone else is afraid of cold, you still feel hot; if everyone else is sleepy, and you can’t sleep at 3:00 in the middle of the night, in fact, you have already begun to keep up.</p><p>If you think you are healthy, you are already very sick.</p><p>There are several stages of disease in the eyes of traditional Chinese medicine, the first stage is “shen” disease.</p><p>The mind is scattered, the mind is uncertain, and the concentration is not concentrated. This is a kind of.</p><p>Sensitive, easily attracted by the outside world, tempted, emotional, lustful, poor self-control, this is the second type.</p><p>In ordinary life, if you don’t sleep well, wake up easily, you are afraid of noise, the dark, and ghosts, this is a weak spirit.</p><p>The mental illness is serious, the form and spirit are separated, the heart and the mouth are different, the outside and inside are conflicting, you are no longer with yourself, you are not sincere, you can’t even express your emotions, or you can’t express your emotions too much.</p><p>For example, many varieties of shows now belong to “too”, the purpose is to exaggerate and provoke emotional outbursts, create obsessed fans, and easily get confused.</p><p>There is also “not enough”. When you should be happy, you have to suppress it. If you get used to it, you will not be happy anymore.</p><p>Too much, not too much, it’s all abnormal.</p><p>“There is no air at the moment” is also abnormal. I suddenly cried when it was time to be happy. It was originally sad but forced me to be strong. There are many such situations in real life, which is abnormal.</p><p>What is health?</p><p><strong>Health is “normal”, and “neutralization”.</strong></p><p>Therefore, after learning Chinese medicine, you will know that <strong>“I wish you every day is normal</strong>“ is the greatest blessing.</p><p>In the past, my teacher taught me a trick to see a doctor: When Western medicine doesn’t know what it is, and Chinese medicine doesn’t know the cause, and you don’t know how to treat it, what should you do? <strong>Adjust normally.</strong></p><p>Every time a patient comes for a follow-up consultation, he should be asked about his living condition, eat, drink, sleep, and sleep. These are the basic indicators of Chinese medicine treatment.</p><p>eat well? Did you sleep well? Are you moving? Does it pull well? Is it normal to sweat? Especially for chronic diseases, when these basic indicators are adjusted to normal, it means that the vitality is restored, and the qi mechanism becomes normal. At this time, the original vitality of the human body can resolve the disease.</p><p>Any disease is like this.</p><p>Now there is a big misunderstanding: if you have a disease, you must cure it.</p><p>Therefore, the patient or even the entire family will forget the normal life, no exercise, no life, no entertainment, no love, nothing, and only the tension and anxiety are left to fight the disease.</p><p>what is this? Abnormal.</p><p>Your swing is being disturbed or even stopped! In this case, even if you have the resources to find the best doctor in the world, it is useless. For a person to recover, he must enter a real and orderly normal life, in a state of ups and downs and mutual interaction with all things, to slowly heal the disease.</p><p>Therefore, about health preservation and conditioning, the really important thing is to find a state of peace and comfort as much as possible. The same is true for healthy people. To do the right thing at the right time, at the right place, with the right person, in the right way, is health preservation. In Buddhism, it is called “right conduct” and “right action”.</p><p><strong>All diseases are first “SHEN” diseases</strong></p><p>Chinese medicine believes that all diseases are mental diseases first, then qi diseases, then blood diseases, and finally what? <strong>physical disease</strong>.</p><p>Diseases start from the invisible part of life, that is, from the spiritual and information level; in the second stage, to the qi part, the energy pattern and operation law are disordered; in the third stage, to the visible disease level.</p><p>The source of many people’s illnesses is some kind of great trouble, great resentment, or a lot of confusion that they cannot resolve. <strong>Many times, the disease is because they are unwilling to face, clarify, and solve.</strong></p><p>Why do Confucianism, Buddhism, and Taoism attach so much importance to “ashamed”, “introspection”, and “repentance”? First, you have to realize that you are wrong before you can “get away from it”.</p><p><strong>As soon as one’s mind changes, so does his demeanor, and the direction of the life train also changes.</strong></p><p>When a person’s body is seriously ill, the direction of the life train has been wrong for a long time.</p><p>But one thing must be remembered, beliefs have the opportunity to turn back at any time, and once the beliefs change, the demeanor has the opportunity to be corrected at any time.</p><p>Many people are ignorant of their own life, inner state, and physical and mental feelings, but they expect to change a lot by eating a handful of mung beans and a few cordyceps. This is fine for simple and agile chicks and birds, but it is not so easy for people as big and complex as our bodies and minds to rely on it to change. Unless you have a very clean body, a very clear mind, and live a very simple life, a handful of mung beans will not be able to mobilize you, and a packet of soup is not easy to do.</p><p>There is a dialogue in the Yellow Emperor’s Classic of Internal Medicine:</p><p>“The Emperor said: Who is the one who has exhausted the form and blood, but has no merit?”</p><p>The Yellow Emperor asked Qi Bo, when a human body is broken and the blood is drained, it is difficult to cure the disease. Why is this?</p><p>“Qi Bo said: “God does not make it.”</p><p><strong>The patient’s spirit has not played its due role, and the doctor has no way to mobilize it.</strong></p><p>The Yellow Emperor then asked: What is the meaning of God not envoys?</p><p>Qi Bo replied: “Needle stone, Tao is also. If the spirit does not enter, the will will not be cured, so the disease cannot be cured. Now that the spirit has been destroyed, the honor and guard cannot be recovered. What? Weeping guards are removed, so the gods go away and the disease will not heal.”</p><p>Everyone is slowly pondering over this passage, why there are more and more illnesses and more and more incurable diseases, you can find the reasons from here.</p><p><strong>The source of everything lies in the invisible thoughts and spirits, and then there is energy, and then it is transformed into matter.</strong></p><p>All diseases, or the beginning of the world, come from this.</p><p><strong>The real wellness</strong><br><strong>is to feel yourself</strong></p><p>When a person lives with his own feelings, he starts from his heart, the origin is himself, and there is no dislocation.</p><p>What are the problems that are prone to occur in modern people?</p><p>We ask for a thing, a person, or a thing. There are always many lofty development plans, always thinking, thinking very far. Or follow a star and keep it in mind. Keep looking at this or that, or keep talking, keep doing things.</p><p><strong>When we take external things as the origin, we lose our sense of who we are and our surroundings.</strong></p><p>What is this state called in Chinese medicine? It is the “<strong>separation of form and spirit</strong>“.</p><p>What is the state of sitting quietly? It is the “Yellow Emperor’s Classic of Internal Medicine” that “form and spirit are combined”, or “body and mind are one”.</p><p>Now when it comes to nutrition, we need to eat well, an egg in the morning and a meal of meat in the evening, right?</p><p>We all burned stoves when we were young. The size of the fire determines how much firewood you should put in it. The reason is simple, right?</p><p>So why don’t we understand these truths when it comes to eating?</p><p>Your fire is obviously very small and weak, you have no digestion power, the flue is blocked, you have no bowel movement, no sweat, no exercise, you still eat steak and drink milk, it will only increase Fertilizers and blockages, put out the fire.</p><p>These truths do not need to be learned through medical knowledge to understand, they are the most basic common sense in daily life, and should be experienced in life.</p><p>Experience the different feelings of what you eat. Live consciously. If you feel uncomfortable after eating something, even if you don’t realize it until the tenth time, it is the beginning of awareness.</p><p><strong>It is best to be suitable for yourself, not to look for an external unified standard.</strong></p><p>Therefore, in life, you must develop the habit of mindfulness, to feel yourself, observe yourself, and then at least know:</p><ol><li><p>What is comfortable to eat and what is uncomfortable;</p></li><li><p>Who is comfortable with and who is uncomfortable with;</p></li><li><p>Thinking, saying, and doing will make you feel more at ease, or conversely, you will be unable to sleep, tangled and sad.</p></li></ol><p><strong>In life, if you observe yourself all the time, you can adjust yourself all the time. This is the real health preservation.</strong></p><p>Tune your mind and body</p><p>“The Yellow Emperor’s Classic of Internal Medicine” also has a higher requirement for health preservation and spiritual nourishment - “<strong>calm and emptiness</strong>“, which is close to the state of Taoist and Buddhist achievers.</p><p>“Tian” means quiet and peaceful, with a relaxed, slight sweetness.</p><p>The great joy and great sorrow that are common in TV dramas are relatively paranoid, lost, and lost, not an ordinary neutral state.</p><p>If this “tian” is replaced with “sweet”, which means “sweet”, there is a principle in traditional Chinese medicine called “sweetness to slow it down”, which means that all medicines, as long as they are sweet, such as licorice, can make people’s spirits. , The operation of the body, including the way people look at problems and their attitudes is softened and relaxed.</p><p>Many diseases now stem from the lack of “<strong>relief</strong>“.</p><p>For example, neurasthenia, anxiety disorders, bipolar syndrome, etc. are all common in this era. Everyone has fallen into a state of mental and psychological life that is too fast and too urgent.</p><p>If you are in a hurry, the gods will float outside, and the qi will be unstable. If it is tight and chaotic, the physiological functions will also be out of tune.</p><p>What does “light” mean? “I don’t care so much, I can do anything, I can.” So there is a lot of space, this is OK, that is OK; instead of having expectations, clinging to goals, and not wanting to control the situation.</p><p><strong>Ask and think less, and have less promising habits.</strong></p><p>Buddhism often says “purify one’s own mind”, Confucianism says “thinking without evil”, and Taoism says “destruction for the day”.</p><p>For people with poor health, I have a suggestion: <strong>live at ease</strong>.</p><p>Nowadays, many people are tired physically and mentally, but they are very enthusiastic about learning. Whether it’s good intentions or malicious intentions, it’s all intentions, and it’s best not to move too much. When the body is weak, the spirit is not easy to hold back.</p><p>From the perspective of traditional Chinese medicine, Taoism, and Buddhism, cultivating the mind is the priority, because at that time your body is as sensitive as an electronic balance, and a single thought will have a great change.</p><p>Teacher Nan Huaijin’s book often mentions that when you meditate to a relatively subtle level, your body will change and you will feel a single thought. It’s uncomfortable to think about it.</p><p>Subtle Perception - The Kung Fu of Emptying Oneself</p><p>There are two modes of human cognition:</p><p><strong>One is the primordial spirit, and the other is the consciousness of the spirit (in modern times, it is referred to by the heart or the brain).</strong></p><p>Knowledge of God is logical thinking, empirical judgment, and biased towards socialization. It is guided by long-term acquired education, environmental cues, and media, loaded from the outside world, and is a cognitive model used by “I”.</p><p><strong>“Yuanshen” refers to instinct and intuition.</strong> The “mind” and “comprehension” that is often mentioned in Chinese culture, such as calligraphy and painting, Guqin, traditional Chinese medicine, and martial arts, can achieve “superiority, the integration of things and me”, all in the Intuitive and instinctive.</p><p>There is a saying in the Book of Changes:</p><p>“The “Yi” has no thinking, no action, it is still and does not move, and it is easy to feel.”</p><p>The ancient Chinese sages believed that the true understanding of the universe and the universe is not obtained by thinking, not by something that can be approached, but when the mind is in a state of stillness, and when the mind is in a state of stillness and interacts with the universe, it naturally reaches everything.</p><p>Through traditional training methods, meditation, standing, Tai Chi… Let us gradually learn not to rely too much on facial features and logical thinking, and directly experience the reality of the moment with our heart.</p><p>I remember that some classes in college were really boring, and I couldn’t leave, so I just sat there and played: relax, put your fingers gently on Zusanli, put it on for dozens of minutes, and see what happens. This is the mentality of playing.</p><p>“Play” is a very important word in traditional culture. <strong>Many things are inadvertently realized in a relaxed state. If you think too hard and have too many goals, you will often miss them.</strong></p><p>When the finger is placed there, there is no feeling at first, and the acupoint is concave and deflated, which is “empty”; after a while, it starts to jump “suddenly, suddenly, suddenly”, “the meridian qi has arrived”, and the qi and blood begins It senses; after a while, it will slowly start to rise and fall on its own, opening and closing.</p><p>It will keep gaining momentum, and sometimes, it will feel that the force below is pushing upward, and at a certain time it will go down along the stomach meridian, down the calf, and go down to the ankle, but it can’t go down, why? There are joints. These places are not very easy to circulate, and it is easy to store evil spirits, so we must open up the joints.</p><p>After a while, it continued to gain momentum, “bang”, and reached the soles of the feet. It turned out that the cold air and hot air in the body came out in a “hu, hu, hu”.</p><p><strong>When your perception becomes more and more subtle, you will be able to know directly.</strong></p><p>After graduating from university, I helped my mother do moxibustion every weekend, and I also helped a teacher at that time. One night, I was very impressed. When I moxibustion the bladder meridian acupoints on his back, when he reached a certain point, he felt like there was a fountain gushing upwards in the acupoints, like a moxa stick that was hanging in the air.</p><p>This kind of feeling shows that it is real, and “reality is open”. The excess energy inside the human body will naturally spread out. What does emptiness feel like? When moxibustion hangs on the acupoints, it feels like being sucked in.</p><p>Later, I found that if I was relaxed enough, the hand holding the moxa stick would move on its own, and the aura on the patient’s back would change during the process of moxibustion. Guide your hand, which is actually the moxa stick, to where the body needs it.</p><p>This state often occurs when both parties are very relaxed, and the moxibustion is in a state of “emptiness and self-forgetfulness”. If the moxibustion practitioner is unsteady, inattentive, or has a strong purpose, although he is focused, but he is persistent and exerts himself, he will not be able to feel these.</p><p>The same is true of acupuncture. When learning acupuncture, you can often spare an hour to stay in the room and give yourself a needle. After trying it, meditate and experience what it feels like? As I said before, it was like throwing a stone into a pond, and the ripples spread out layer by layer, and I gradually knew where my body was blocked and where I was able to benefit.</p><p>When you are quiet and relaxed, and there are not so many thoughts, thoughts, emotions, desires, plans, and all kinds of troubles surging around, your heart is like a relatively clean mirror.</p><p><strong>Everything is clearly there, waiting for you to discover.</strong></p><p>You face this world every day, and you experience something new every day, like those pictures in fairy tales: Hey, Grandpa Sun is very happy today, the flowers smile at me, a bee flies by as if something happened to tell me.</p><p>Meditation to experience one’s own heart, feel the changes of the four seasons in the heaven and earth, the floating and sinking of flowers, birds, fish, and insects, the mutual sense of spirit, spirit, and body, taking things from afar and taking bodies near.</p><p>The answer is here.</p>]]></content>
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  
</search>
