<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<search>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Every time you listen, speak, read, and write, you are &quot;massaging&quot; your brain</title>
    <link href="/Every-time-you-listen-speak-read-and-write-you-are-massaging-your-brain/"/>
    <url>/Every-time-you-listen-speak-read-and-write-you-are-massaging-your-brain/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>You can’t speak fluently, your ears don’t work well, you can’t name things when you see things… When did you realize that you were suddenly “old”?</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202211.gif"></p><p>In the book “Changing Minds: How Aging Affects Language and How Language Affects Aging”, University of Memphis psychology professors Roger Cruz and Dr. Richard Roberts mentioned that aging is a two-way process, time plays a decisive role, but human intervention is Also important.</p><p>Through the learning and use of language, people can influence the cognitive aging process, promote brain health, and even prolong life and improve the quality of life.</p><p><em><strong>The more language you use, the better your brain becomes</strong></em></p><p>“Language is a very important part of cognitive function.” Cognitive function is a person’s ability to understand the external world, including memory, calculation, execution, attention, language, and orientation (including space, time, and character relationships). ).</p><p><strong>Listening, speaking, reading and writing protect cognitive function</strong></p><p>Clinically, some dementia patients do not have problems with memory, but have language barriers.</p><p>For example, the naming disorder, that is, the patient knows that the cup is used for drinking water, but cannot call the name; and the patient’s language expression is confusing, not fluent, and it is difficult to say a complete sentence. Language training for these patients can play a certain role. improve.</p><p>That is to say, the training of listening, speaking, reading, and writing has a certain protective effect on cognitive function. The famous “Nun Study” in the United States found that an individual’s early language ability may be related to the risk of Alzheimer’s disease.</p><p> <img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202212.webp"></p><p>The nuns participating in the study are playing a competitive scrabble game</p><p>The more developed the language function in the early years, the deeper the depth of thought logic, the better the cognitive function will be maintained in the later years, and the lower the risk of developing Alzheimer’s disease.</p><p><strong>Brains ‘get smaller’ from age 40</strong></p><p>Human brain development generally peaks between the ages of 20 and 40. From the age of 40, the number of nerve cells (neurons) in the brain gradually decreases, which affects memory, coordination, and brain function, and the size of the brain gradually shrinks.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202213.gif"></p><p>From a physiological point of view, people’s memory, reaction ability and executive ability will irreversibly decline with age, <strong>but language ability does not age with the body, on the contrary, the more it is used, the more developed it is.</strong></p><p>Many examples of “late bloomers” show that age does not impair people’s ability to speak, write, and learn new vocabulary, and even the ability to understand, use, and create language develops well in old age.</p><p>For example, Canadian female writer Alice Munro wrote her first novel at the age of 37 and won the Nobel Prize for Literature at the age of 82; British writer Daniel Defoe did not publish her first novel “Lu “Binson Crusoe”; Shandong writer Jiang Shumei began to learn and read at the age of 60, published her first book at the age of 74, and then published 5 works in seven or eight years…</p><p><em><strong>How Listening, Reading, Writing, and Writing Affect Brain Health</strong></em></p><p>Listening, speaking, reading, writing, and reading accompany people throughout their lives, which not only affects people’s cognition and personality, but also affects their brain health.</p><p><strong>Listening: Strengthening Cognitive Resilience</strong></p><p>One of the most obvious signs of physical aging is hearing loss. ENT experts at Johns Hopkins University in the United States have found that people with hearing loss have an accelerated decline of 30% to 40% in hearing and cognitive abilities.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202214.gif"></p><p>Hearing is an important channel for language input to the brain. The reasons for the accelerated impairment of cognitive function due to hearing loss may include:</p><p>Diseases that cause hearing deterioration can also impair cognition; hearing loss reduces stimulation of key areas of the brain, accelerating neurodegeneration; hearing loss affects information acquisition and depletes cognitive reserves.</p><p>A study published in the American Journal of Medicine found that as long as someone listens when speaking, the brain is more cognitively resilient. 4 years.</p><p><em><strong>Speaking: Exercise brain flexibility</strong></em></p><p>Talking is a benign stimulus to the brain and helps keep it alive.</p><p>If a person lives in isolation and no one speaks and communicates, not only will the ability to speak slowly deteriorate, but also loneliness and social isolation will occur, thereby reducing cognitive function.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202215.gif"></p><p>Clinically, some dementia patients also have problems with speaking ability, such as poor expression, difficulty in finding words, and difficulty in naming. Among them, <strong>the difficulty of finding words is a typical cognitive impairment problem</strong>, and suddenly cannot remember familiar things, names, but also proper nouns and object names.</p><p>Studies have shown that when a person reads instructions aloud, they tend to focus better and perform better than those who read them silently. If you need to remember a lot of information, especially in writing, reading aloud is the best way to do it.</p><p><strong>Reading: Boost your brainpower</strong></p><p>When reading, the brain must coordinate numerous perceptual and cognitive functions, including basic visual skills, phonological perception, long-term memory, and working memory.</p><p>When reading, in addition to paying attention to the current information points (story background, characters, details, etc.), you should also connect with the content you read before.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202216.gif"></p><p>There are hundreds of millions of information points in each book, and the brain needs to continuously remember this information and store it, which ultimately enhances memory.</p><p>Brain scans of people with an average age of 76 at the University of California, Berkeley, found that reading at an early age can prevent Alzheimer’s disease.</p><p>According to a study by the Rush University Medical Center in the United States, the elderly who regularly read and read newspapers have a 32% lower risk of mental decline than the general population.</p><p>A large-scale study led by the Yale School of Public Health found that people who read at least 30 minutes a day lived nearly two years longer on average than those who didn’t.</p><p>It should also be reminded that the carrier of this reading is a paper book, not an e-ink product.</p><p><strong>Write: Strengthen memory</strong></p><p>Writing activates the motor, visual and cognitive areas of the brain.</p><p>“Writing not only mobilizes cognition, but also the motor function of the body.” Shen Lu said that writing is the strengthening of memory. In the process of choosing words and sentences, both the mind and the body are well exercised.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202217.gif"></p><p>Gerontologists at Utah State University found that people who kept a diary throughout their lives had a 53 percent lower risk of developing cognitive impairment.</p><p>It should be noted that the four dimensions of language listening, speaking, reading, and writing can operate relatively independently. For example, a stroke patient may lose the ability to read, but not necessarily the ability to understand language and speak, and even continue to write.</p><p>Language ability “uses it and loses it” will also decline in the normal aging process, but maintaining and exercising language ability can optimize cognitive function and fight to age.</p><p><em><strong>5 small things to exercise language function</strong></em></p><p>Like physical exercise, language exercise should also be adhered to, especially for the elderly. Experts recommend starting from the following points.</p><p><strong>Keep listening</strong></p><p>When hearing loss occurs, you should seek medical attention or get hearing aids in time; listen to soothing and familiar music or stories from your youth to awaken pleasant memories.</p><p>Research from institutions such as the University of Toronto confirms that repeated listening to meaningful music produces beneficial brain plasticity in mild cognitive impairment or early Alzheimer’s disease.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202218.gif"></p><p><strong>Actively communicate</strong></p><p>The elderly should communicate more with their family members in their lives. For example, after watching TV and discussing the plot with their family members, they can not only exercise memory, but also enhance their feelings.</p><p>Participate in more social activities, such as speech contests, etc., to exercise language skills; maintain healthy social interactions, and refuse bad social behaviors such as gambling and alcoholism.</p><p><strong>Keep reading</strong></p><p>It is recommended that the elderly read more books and newspapers, at least 3 to 5 days a week, and read at least 30 minutes a day, which can not only help memorize words and knowledge, but also understand the latest information, so as not to be out of touch with society.</p><p>The material to be read should be scientific and slightly challenging, to mobilize the elderly’s thinking or learn new knowledge.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202219.gif"></p><p><strong>Develop the habit of writing</strong></p><p>Cultivate the habit of writing a diary, copying poems or words of interest, not only to exercise writing ability, but also to exercise work and motor functions.</p><p>The elderly can also read the written diary regularly to evoke memories and exercise memory function. Anxiety and depression patients usually write more, which can also reduce the symptoms of emotional tension.</p><p><strong>Try to learn a new language</strong></p><p>A new study from New York University shows that in addition to enhancing cognition, learning a second language can also broaden your horizons and add joy to life.</p><p>Experts remind that the decline in listening, speaking, reading, and writing skills often indicate cognitive dysfunction, and every change in function may be a signal of some diseases:</p><ol><li>The language fluency is decreased, and the language fluency test can be used for self-examination.</li></ol><p>Say the names of fruits, vegetables, or animals as much as possible within 1 minute, 14 with a college degree or above are considered qualified; 12 with a high school degree; 11 with a junior high school degree; and 10 with a primary school degree or below.</p><ol start="2"><li><p>Difficulty finding words, unable to understand other people’s speech, such as watching TV and unable to keep up with the plot.</p></li><li><p>The speech is simple and repeated. After the next sentence is finished, you do not know what the previous sentence is saying.</p></li><li><p>Difficulty in writing or reading, unable to write complex characters, unable to read newspapers.</p></li></ol><p>Once the above situation occurs, you should pay attention to it and see a memory clinic or a cognitive specialist.</p>]]></content>
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Quit smoking gradually VS Quit smoking immediately</title>
    <link href="/Quit-smoking-gradually-VS-Quit-smoking-immediately/"/>
    <url>/Quit-smoking-gradually-VS-Quit-smoking-immediately/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>A single cigarette produces at least 4,000 chemicals from lighting to burning out, 69 of which are identified as carcinogens.</p><p>A study published in The Lancet shows that quitting smoking early can prevent 28 diseases such as myocardial infarction and lung cancer.</p><p>Many smokers are aware of the dangers of smoking and try to quit smoking, but they are often unbearable with various withdrawal reactions and fail repeatedly.</p><p>From a scientific point of view, gradually quit smoking vs abruptly quit smoking, which method has a higher success rate?</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202201.webp"></p><p><em>Gradually quit smoking VS immediate smoking cessation, which one to choose?</em></p><p>Scientists from the Universities of Oxford and Birmingham, UK, conducted a randomized controlled clinical trial to evaluate the smoking cessation effect of “gradual withdrawal” and “immediate withdrawal”.</p><p>The researchers included 697 ex-smokers with established addictions and randomly divided them into two groups:</p><p>The first group is the “immediate smoking-cessation group”, that is, quit smoking directly and completely from the beginning;</p><p>The other group gradually reduced the amount of smoking 2 weeks in advance, reduced it to 1&#x2F;2 of the original smoking amount on the first weekend, reduced it to 1&#x2F;4 of the original smoking amount on the second weekend, and then stopped smoking.</p><p>In addition, both groups of participants received the same behavioral supportive treatment and short-acting nicotine replacement therapy to cope with the uncomfortable symptoms of smoking cessation and improve the success rate.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202202.webp"></p><p>The research team compared the smoking cessation effects of the participants at 4 weeks, 8 weeks, and 6 months after the start of complete smoking cessation.</p><p>The criteria for evaluating the effect of smoking cessation include the quitter’s oral and the exhaled carbon monoxide concentration of the quitter. The results show that:</p><p><strong>At 4 weeks</strong></p><p>39.2% of the people in the “gradual tapering group” quit smoking successfully without relapse; while 49% of the people in the “immediately stop smoking group” quit smoking successfully without relapse.</p><p><strong>At 8 weeks</strong></p><p>The success rate of smoking cessation was 29.2% in the “taper tape group” and 36.6% in the “immediate withdrawal group”.</p><p><strong>At 6 months</strong></p><p>15.1% of the “gradually tapering group” quit smoking successfully without relapse, and 22% of the “immediately stop smoking group” quit smoking successfully without relapse.</p><p>The above three groups of data show that the success rate of smoking cessation in the “immediate smoking-cessation group” is higher than that in the “gradually tapering group”.</p><p>The conclusion is clear: To improve your chances of quitting smoking, it is best to stop smoking from the moment you decide to start quitting.</p><p><strong>Smoking Addiction</strong></p><p><strong>Chronic diseases recognized by WHO</strong></p><p>The famous writer Mark Twain said: “It’s easy to quit smoking. I have quit dozens of times in my life.” A joke is enough to show how difficult it is to quit smoking.</p><p>Nicotine in tobacco is a highly addictive substance, which is an important reason for many “old smokers” to smoke for a long time.</p><p>After nicotine is inhaled into the human body, it will enter the brain center with the blood within 10 seconds, stimulating a sharp and short-term release of dopamine.</p><p>Dopamine’s euphoric effect wears off quickly once nicotine intake is stopped, leaving smokers unable to continue experiencing euphoria and experiencing withdrawal and cravings.</p><p>Therefore, addicts smoke cigarettes every once in a while to maintain nicotine levels in the brain.</p><p>It should be emphasized that smoking addiction (also known as tobacco dependence) is not a behavioral habit, but a chronic disease. The World Health Organization has included it in the International Classification of Diseases, coded as F17.2.</p><p>The study found that the brain structure and function of tobacco-dependent patients will change, manifested as gray and white matter atrophy, abnormal neural activity in the frontal lobe, temporal lobe, and limbic lobe, and significantly reduced functional connectivity of the insula-related brain regions, proving the pathological site of this chronic disease. in the brain.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202203.gif"></p><p>Tobacco dependence is divided into physical dependence and psychological dependence:</p><p>Physical dependence refers to a series of unbearable withdrawal symptoms, including irritability, anxiety, restlessness, headache, inability to concentrate, sleep disturbance, etc., after smokers stop smoking or reduce the amount of smoking.</p><p>Psychological dependence, also known as spiritual dependence, is manifested as a strong subjective desire to smoke.</p><p>Physical dependence and psychological dependence cannot be completely separated, and often coexist, which affects the success rate of smoking cessation.</p><p><strong>“Withdrawal” is the biggest obstacle</strong></p><p>The reason why quitting smoking is particularly difficult is often because of “withdrawal symptoms”.</p><p>In general, withdrawal symptoms are a normal phenomenon in the process of smoking cessation. They usually begin to appear a few hours after smoking cessation, are most intense during the first 14 days of smoking cessation, and gradually decrease until they disappear.</p><p>Therefore, relapse is most likely when you first quit smoking.</p><p>Most withdrawal symptoms last about a month, and there are steps you can take during this period to help you get through the toughest phase.</p><p><em><strong>How to deal with “withdrawal reaction”?</strong></em></p><p>For example, take a deep breath or go for a walk outside when feeling tense or irritable;</p><p>When you can’t concentrate, try to reduce the workload and take a short rest;</p><p>When feeling tired, be sure to get enough sleep and take a proper nap at noon;</p><p>When you always want to eat, choose some fresh vegetables and fruits instead of high-calorie snacks.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/20220204.gif"></p><p>It should be noted that some people still relapse after quitting smoking for several months or even years, generally due to inducing factors, such as high work pressure, sudden accidents at home, social gatherings, etc.</p><p>When encountering such a situation, one must firm up the belief that quitting smoking is to say goodbye to the cigarette completely, not to touch a cigarette again, and not to take a fluke mentality that “it’s okay to take a puff or two”;</p><p>Secondly, to avoid factors that induce smoking, stay away from other smokers, limit alcohol consumption, etc.;</p><p>Smoking can be replaced by some compensatory behaviors, such as drinking water, chewing sugar-free gum, taking a walk, listening to music, etc.</p><p>In this case, the craving for smoking will not last too long, and as long as you stick to it for a few more minutes, it is likely to avoid a relapse.</p><p><strong>Smoking cessation clinics may improve success rates</strong></p><p>Some smokers can rely on perseverance to quit smoking. For tobacco-dependent patients, smoking cessation clinics can help improve the success rate of smoking cessation.</p><p>Doctors will formulate personalized smoking cessation treatment plans according to the methods recommended by clinical smoking cessation guidelines, including smoking cessation advice, smoking cessation drug treatment, and other intervention methods.</p><p>The doctor will also regularly track and follow up on the smoking cessation situation to help solve the problems encountered in the process of smoking cessation.</p><p>Don’t be afraid of smoking cessation drugs. Smoking addiction is a chronic disease and the use of drugs is a very formal approach. There is ample evidence that smoking cessation drugs can relieve withdrawal symptoms and improve the success rate of smoking cessation.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202045.webp"></p><p>Whether it is an “old smoker” or someone who has recently become addicted, some preparations need to be done before quitting smoking to help quit smoking successfully.</p><p><strong>Determine a quit smoking day</strong></p><p>You can choose an important day, such as holidays, birthdays, anniversaries, etc. From this day on, don’t smoke again.</p><p><strong>Create an environment conducive to smoking cessation</strong></p><p>Before quitting smoking, dispose of all smoking-related items around you, including cigarettes, lighters, ashtrays, etc. at home, in the car, in the office, and with you, and try to create a smoke-free environment.</p><p><strong>Review past smoking cessation experiences</strong></p><p>If you have tried to quit smoking before, you can summarize your past experience and find out what helped you quit smoking and what was more likely to lead to relapse.</p><p>Especially for problems or difficulties that may arise in the first few weeks, such as nicotine withdrawal symptoms, and plan ahead.</p><p><strong>Team up to quit smoking or get personal supervision</strong></p><p>Tell family, friends, and colleagues that you have decided to quit smoking, and get their understanding and support. In addition, smokers around you should be encouraged to quit smoking together, at least not in front of you.</p><p><strong>Write a commitment</strong></p><p>It is recommended to sign a smoking cessation commitment letter with yourself, and you can also leave one for your supporters, which will help you get encouragement and supervision from others.</p>]]></content>
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>People with magnesium deficiency have poor anti-cancer ability! How to be an &quot;Mg&quot; eater?</title>
    <link href="/People-with-magnesium-deficiency-have-poor-anti-cancer-ability-How-to-be-an-Mg-eater/"/>
    <url>/People-with-magnesium-deficiency-have-poor-anti-cancer-ability-How-to-be-an-Mg-eater/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Many people think about supplementing calcium, vitamin D, and even iron when supplementing nutrition, but few people think about supplementing magnesium.</p><p>But in fact, magnesium is needed for many activities in the human body: activating muscles and nerves, increasing body energy, digesting protein, carbohydrates, and fats, etc.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202191.webp"></p><p>Magnesium deficiency can cause 21 conditions including anxiety and asthma.</p><p><em><strong>Study finds that magnesium may help immune cells fight cancer</strong></em></p><p>On January 19, 2022, a research team from the University of Basel in Switzerland published a study in the American journal “Cell”, showing that T cells can help immune cells fight cancer in a magnesium-rich environment.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202192.webp"></p><p>The experiment provided mice with cancer cells in a diet deficient in magnesium ions, and found that the cancer cells in the mice spread faster, and then supplemented with a diet containing magnesium ions, and found that the immune capacity of the mice was enhanced.</p><p>Further analysis found that in an environment rich in magnesium ions, magnesium binds to the T cell surface protein LFA-1, thereby increasing the immune capacity of T cells and effectively resisting cancer cells.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202193.webp"></p><p>T cells (blue) form immune synapses through LFA-1 to attack tumor cells (white)</p><p>Experiments show that:</p><p>Low levels of magnesium in serum have poor immunity;</p><p>Tumors locally increased magnesium levels, and T cells enhanced immune responses to cancer cells.</p><p>Using data from an earlier study in cancer patients, the researchers re-analyzed it and found that immunotherapy was less effective in patients with insufficient blood levels of magnesium.</p><p>Therefore, magnesium may be able to act as a “right-hand man” for the human immune system and play a role in promoting cancer treatment.</p><p><em><strong>The body sends these signals when magnesium is deficient</strong></em></p><p>In life, many people will have symptoms such as insomnia, depression, anorexia, and fatigue, which may be due to magnesium deficiency in the body. Magnesium is one of the essential minerals in the human body. When magnesium is deficient, the body will prompt 7 signals:</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202194.gif"></p><p><strong>Difficulty falling asleep</strong></p><p>Magnesium helps to increase levels of a neurotransmitter in the brain called gamma-aminobutyric acid (GABA), which promotes relaxation and sleep, helping to relieve sleep disorders.</p><p><strong>Depression</strong></p><p>Magnesium can improve human hormone regulation and brain serotonin levels, which is beneficial to blood sugar balance. Brain serotonin is essential for maintaining emotional stability, so magnesium deficiency is more prone to depression and anxiety.</p><p><strong>Migraine</strong></p><p>“European Journal of Neuroscience Research” has published research that magnesium can effectively reduce the severity and frequency of migraine symptoms, which is related to magnesium’s ability to regulate hormones and relax muscles.</p><p><strong>Eyelid jump</strong></p><p>One of the most common manifestations of magnesium deficiency is eyelid twitching. This is because magnesium regulates muscle movement, and when magnesium levels in the body are low, muscle spasms and twitching occur in many parts of the body.</p><p><strong>Abnormal heart rhythm</strong></p><p>Magnesium helps maintain a normal heart rhythm. Doctors give magnesium supplements intravenously to reduce atrial fibrillation and arrhythmias because magnesium reduces levels of nutrients such as calcium.</p><p><strong>Always feel tired</strong></p><p>Magnesium is an essential element of the human body’s energy production system, and the human body needs magnesium to generate adenosine triphosphate for energy production.</p><p><strong>Prone to skin problems</strong></p><p>Magnesium reduces inflammation in the body that can lead to skin conditions like acne, eczema, psoriasis, and more. Magnesium also regulates vitamin D levels and maintains healthy skin.</p><p><em><strong>6 types of people are prone to lack of “magnesium”</strong></em></p><p>Insufficient magnesium intake, malabsorption, or increased excretion can lead to magnesium deficiency, causing loss of appetite, nausea, vomiting, fatigue, and weakness.</p><p>With the increase of the deficiency, numbness, tingling, muscle spasm, arrhythmia, etc. may also occur, and even lead to hypocalcemia and hypokalemia. There are 6 types of people who are easy to be recruited:</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202195.gif"></p><p><strong>Calcium supplement population</strong></p><p>After middle age, calcium loss is faster than calcium deposition. The risk of osteoporosis is increased, and many middle-aged and elderly people will supplement calcium, but high calcium will competitively inhibit the absorption of magnesium.</p><p><strong>Unbalanced diet</strong></p><p>Middle-aged people tend to gain weight. People who don’t have time to exercise will lose weight by dieting, and hunger will affect the intake of magnesium. Some middle-aged people don’t like meat, but a high-protein diet will reduce the absorption rate of magnesium.</p><p><strong>Strong tea drinkers</strong></p><p>The caffeine in strong tea contains a diuretic component that increases magnesium loss.</p><p><strong>People with diabetes</strong></p><p>Middle-aged and elderly people are a high-risk group of diabetes. Diabetes increases the excretion of magnesium, and magnesium deficiency, in turn, reduces the working efficiency of insulin, forming a vicious circle.</p><p><strong>People who take certain drugs for a long time</strong></p><p>Some drugs such as bisphosphonates and tetracycline antibiotics can affect the absorption of magnesium, and some diuretics (such as furosemide, hydrochlorothiazide tabletsdiureticic acid) can increase the excretion of magnesium.</p><p><strong>Frequent drinkers</strong></p><p>Alcohol abuse can cause pancreatitis, alcoholic ketoacidosis, etc., and increase the excretion of magnesium. Long-term excessive drinking can easily lead to serious loss of magnesium.</p><p><em><strong>To become a “magnesium” eater should do:</strong></em></p><p><strong>Eat green leafy vegetables</strong></p><p>Leafy greens are the richest in magnesium, followed by whole grains, nuts, meat, and milk.</p><p>However, green leafy vegetables contain oxalic acid, which affects magnesium absorption, and whole grains contain phytic acid, which affects magnesium absorption. It is recommended to blanch the vegetables in boiling water before cooking them; when cooking coarse grains, soak them for a while in advance.</p><p><strong>There is no need to take magnesium supplements if you</strong></p><p>Drinking milk every day, eating meat, and eating more “magnesium” foods can fully meet the body’s magnesium needs, and there is no need to take magnesium supplements.</p><p><strong>Avoid these drinks</strong></p><p>Avoid beverages that cause magnesium loss in the body, such as alcohol, strong tea, coffee, etc., and drink plenty of water.</p><p><strong>A balanced and varied diet</strong></p><p>Usually moderate intake of fruits and vegetables, with staple food thickness. Reduce high-salt, high-fat diets.</p><p>If necessary, magnesium supplements can be taken in moderation under the guidance of a doctor. It is recommended that the calcium and magnesium intake ratio should be maintained at 1:1.</p><p>For children and the elderly, magnesium is more important than calcium; if the kidneys are not functioning well, magnesium supplementation must be evaluated by a doctor.</p>]]></content>
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>3 kinds of &quot;functional&quot; toothpaste that doctors are afraid of! These ingredients may induce enteritis</title>
    <link href="/3-kinds-of-functional-toothpaste-that-doctors-are-afraid-of-New-research-These-ingredients-may-induce-enteritis/"/>
    <url>/3-kinds-of-functional-toothpaste-that-doctors-are-afraid-of-New-research-These-ingredients-may-induce-enteritis/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Anti-moth, whitening, hemostasis, antibacterial, anti-allergic… Many people pay attention to the “function” written on the package when buying toothpaste and rarely look at the specific ingredients.</p><p>Recently, the international academic journal “Nature Communications” published a study: antibacterial agent triclosan (TCS) contained in some toothpaste may cause damage to the human intestine and induce enteritis.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202181.gif"></p><p><em><strong>This ingredient in toothpaste can induce enteritis</strong></em></p><p>The research, carried out by Tsai Zongwei’s team at Hong Kong Baptist University in collaboration with a foreign team, explains how the antibacterial agent triclosan (TCS) triggers intestinal inflammation.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202182.webp"></p><p>Studies have shown that after exposure to TCS, the intestinal toxicity of TCS is stimulated under the action of human gut microbial GUS enzymes, which in turn leads to the appearance of enteritis. By targeting the inhibition of gut microbial GUS enzymes, the harm of TCS to the human gut may be eliminated.</p><p>This study also further confirmed that TCS, a common ingredient in daily necessities, will cause certain harm to the human body, so you must pay more attention when choosing daily necessities.</p><p><em><strong>Dentists are afraid of 3 toothpaste ingredients</strong></em></p><p>According to the British “Daily Mail” report, many toothpaste ingredients are harmful to our health, Dr. Toby Talbert, a dental expert at the Royal College of Surgeons, reminded us to pay attention to these 3 ingredients:</p><p><strong>Descaler: It can easily cause mouth ulcers</strong></p><p>The oral mucosa is one of the most delicate tissues, and sodium lauryl sulfate is the most effective cleaning agent, which can cause irritation or damage the oral mucosa, leading to chronic oral ulcers.</p><p>People with frequent oral ulcers and those with ulcers are best not to use a toothpaste containing sodium lauryl sulfate.</p><p><strong>Whitening agent: easy to damage gums</strong></p><p>Bleaching agents such as hydrogen peroxide are added to many to toothpaste to whiten teeth. However, they can irritate soft tissues, damage the oral mucosa, and damage the gums.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202183.gif"></p><p>The whiteness of teeth is related to enamel and dentin, which is difficult to change with toothpaste. Although bleaching agents can remove some stains on the surface of the teeth, they have little effect on the deep stains that are endogenous to the teeth.</p><p><strong>Abrasives: can damage tooth enamel</strong></p><p>Fine particles are added to many to toothpaste to remove stains from the surface of the teeth, however, some ointments are not abrasive enough and can wear away the enamel, which can lead to sensitive teeth over time.</p><p>It is recommended to purchase toothpaste containing aluminum hydroxide or calcium hydrogen phosphate with fine particles. These abrasives are relatively good and cause less damage to the tooth surface.</p><p><em><strong>“Functional toothpaste” should not be used indiscriminately</strong></em></p><p>Toothpaste is used as a brushing aid. Its basic function is to clean the oral cavity. Generally, commercially available toothpaste can be satisfied after strict testing. The effects of whitening, anti-cavity, desensitization, and hemostasis are all auxiliary and are not enough to directly affect oral health.</p><p><strong>Whitening toothpaste:</strong></p><p>Mainly, some special “friction particles” are added, which can remove the cigarette stains and tea stains deposited on the surface of the teeth, but do not affect deep endogenous stains such as tetracycline teeth and fluorosis teeth.</p><p>If the friction particles are large and hard, long-term use may also cause tooth wear.</p><p>There is also some whitening toothpaste with blue paste, which can only achieve the “visual effect” of temporary whitening through the blue foam.</p><p><strong>Acid-proof toothpaste:</strong></p><p>The principle is to form a protective film on the surface of the tooth, thereby enhancing the disease prevention ability of the periodontal tissue, but it should be stopped after symptoms improve, otherwise it will destroy the microbial ecological balance in the oral cavity.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202184.gif"></p><p><strong>Antibacterial toothpaste:</strong></p><p>Some medicated toothpaste has bactericidal and bacteriostatic ingredients, which can help kill some bacteria in the oral cavity in a short time, but daily use is equivalent to taking a small number of antibiotics for a long time, which is not conducive to the microbalance of oral flora and is prone to drug resistance.</p><p><strong>Anti-sensitive toothpaste:</strong></p><p>Desensitizing ingredients such as fluoride and strontium chloride are added, which can only relieve mild dentin hypersensitivity to a certain extent.</p><p><strong>Fresh breath toothpaste:</strong></p><p>The freshness of the breath comes from brushing your teeth carefully, removing plaque and some harmful bacteria, not the fragrance of the toothpaste itself, so the “scent” of the toothpaste is not so important.</p><p><em><strong>Choose a toothpaste that suits you</strong></em></p><p>The use of toothpaste should vary from person to region and region, and should not be used blindly for a long time.</p><p> <img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202185.gif"></p><p><strong>Mainly depends on the quality of the friction agent</strong></p><p>Small particles should be selected to prevent damage to the tooth. The ones containing aluminum hydroxide and calcium hydrogen phosphate are better, followed by silica, and the particles of calcium carbonate are the largest.</p><p><strong>Change toothpaste</strong></p><p>Using a toothpaste for a long time, the bacteria in the mouth will develop resistance and learn to “resist” the effect of toothpaste to clean the mouth.</p><p><strong>Sharing a toothpaste</strong></p><p>Sharing a toothpaste can easily lead to cross-infection of many oral diseases. If someone in the family catches a cold or suffers from other oral diseases, some viruses and bacteria may remain in the crevices of the toothbrush after brushing.</p><p>The next time you brush your teeth, the toothpaste comes in contact with the toothbrush, potentially transferring the virus to the toothpaste and spreading it to others through the toothpaste.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202186.gif"></p><p><strong>Choose according to an oral condition</strong></p><p>For example, children can choose children’s toothpaste; family members with caries can use fluoride toothpaste; people with periodontitis can choose Chinese herbal toothpaste or toothpaste with anti-inflammatory ingredients.</p><p><strong>Some areas are not suitable for fluoride toothpaste</strong></p><p>Fluoride toothpaste can reduce the chance of cavities, prevent the surface of the teeth from being dissolved, and also make the dissolved teeth stronger. However, in high fluoride areas such as Shanxi, Inner Mongolia, and Hebei, the drinking water contains fluoride, so it is not suitable to use fluoride toothpaste.</p><p>Reminder: toothpaste is not a substitute for medical treatment. If you have oral ulcers, black teeth, toothache, caries, bad breath, etc., you should go to the doctor in time.</p>]]></content>
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Being with someone who makes you feel comfortable is also a regimen</title>
    <link href="/Being-with-someone-who-makes-you-feel-comfortable-is-also-a-regimen/"/>
    <url>/Being-with-someone-who-makes-you-feel-comfortable-is-also-a-regimen/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/Being-with-someone-who-makes-you-feel-comfortable.webp" alt="Being with someone who makes you feel comfortable is also a regimen"></p><p>Everything in the whole world is like a huge symphony. Walking with the big symphony of heaven and earth, walking in a normal and neutral way is the standard of health.</p><p>When you are sick, you are actually kicked out by God.</p><p>Therefore, the disease was called “disorder” in ancient times, and the cause was called “disorder” or “lost power”.</p><p>So what is health? <strong>Health is “normal”</strong>.</p><p>Health does not mean that you are ruddy, full of energy or something, not these things, nor how much muscle strength, how much heartbeat…</p><p>What is “usually”?</p><p><strong>The most important point is to be in a relatively harmonious relationship with oneself, with the society, and with this big world, and to be able to play with the natural rhythm.</strong></p><p>When the weather is hot, everyone else sweats, and you can sweat too; you can walk without getting tired after walking for two hours. But if everyone else is afraid of cold, you still feel hot; if everyone else is sleepy, and you can’t sleep at 3:00 in the middle of the night, in fact, you have already begun to keep up.</p><p>If you think you are healthy, you are already very sick.</p><p>There are several stages of disease in the eyes of traditional Chinese medicine, the first stage is “shen” disease.</p><p>The mind is scattered, the mind is uncertain, and the concentration is not concentrated. This is a kind of.</p><p>Sensitive, easily attracted by the outside world, tempted, emotional, lustful, poor self-control, this is the second type.</p><p>In ordinary life, if you don’t sleep well, wake up easily, you are afraid of noise, the dark, and ghosts, this is a weak spirit.</p><p>The mental illness is serious, the form and spirit are separated, the heart and the mouth are different, the outside and inside are conflicting, you are no longer with yourself, you are not sincere, you can’t even express your emotions, or you can’t express your emotions too much.</p><p>For example, many varieties of shows now belong to “too”, the purpose is to exaggerate and provoke emotional outbursts, create obsessed fans, and easily get confused.</p><p>There is also “not enough”. When you should be happy, you have to suppress it. If you get used to it, you will not be happy anymore.</p><p>Too much, not too much, it’s all abnormal.</p><p>“There is no air at the moment” is also abnormal. I suddenly cried when it was time to be happy. It was originally sad but forced me to be strong. There are many such situations in real life, which is abnormal.</p><p>What is health?</p><p><strong>Health is “normal”, and “neutralization”.</strong></p><p>Therefore, after learning Chinese medicine, you will know that <strong>“I wish you every day is normal</strong>“ is the greatest blessing.</p><p>In the past, my teacher taught me a trick to see a doctor: When Western medicine doesn’t know what it is, and Chinese medicine doesn’t know the cause, and you don’t know how to treat it, what should you do? <strong>Adjust normally.</strong></p><p>Every time a patient comes for a follow-up consultation, he should be asked about his living condition, eat, drink, sleep, and sleep. These are the basic indicators of Chinese medicine treatment.</p><p>eat well? Did you sleep well? Are you moving? Does it pull well? Is it normal to sweat? Especially for chronic diseases, when these basic indicators are adjusted to normal, it means that the vitality is restored, and the qi mechanism becomes normal. At this time, the original vitality of the human body can resolve the disease.</p><p>Any disease is like this.</p><p>Now there is a big misunderstanding: if you have a disease, you must cure it.</p><p>Therefore, the patient or even the entire family will forget the normal life, no exercise, no life, no entertainment, no love, nothing, and only the tension and anxiety are left to fight the disease.</p><p>what is this? Abnormal.</p><p>Your swing is being disturbed or even stopped! In this case, even if you have the resources to find the best doctor in the world, it is useless. For a person to recover, he must enter a real and orderly normal life, in a state of ups and downs and mutual interaction with all things, to slowly heal the disease.</p><p>Therefore, about health preservation and conditioning, the really important thing is to find a state of peace and comfort as much as possible. The same is true for healthy people. To do the right thing at the right time, at the right place, with the right person, in the right way, is health preservation. In Buddhism, it is called “right conduct” and “right action”.</p><p><strong>All diseases are first “SHEN” diseases</strong></p><p>Chinese medicine believes that all diseases are mental diseases first, then qi diseases, then blood diseases, and finally what? <strong>physical disease</strong>.</p><p>Diseases start from the invisible part of life, that is, from the spiritual and information level; in the second stage, to the qi part, the energy pattern and operation law are disordered; in the third stage, to the visible disease level.</p><p>The source of many people’s illnesses is some kind of great trouble, great resentment, or a lot of confusion that they cannot resolve. <strong>Many times, the disease is because they are unwilling to face, clarify, and solve.</strong></p><p>Why do Confucianism, Buddhism, and Taoism attach so much importance to “ashamed”, “introspection”, and “repentance”? First, you have to realize that you are wrong before you can “get away from it”.</p><p><strong>As soon as one’s mind changes, so does his demeanor, and the direction of the life train also changes.</strong></p><p>When a person’s body is seriously ill, the direction of the life train has been wrong for a long time.</p><p>But one thing must be remembered, beliefs have the opportunity to turn back at any time, and once the beliefs change, the demeanor has the opportunity to be corrected at any time.</p><p>Many people are ignorant of their own life, inner state, and physical and mental feelings, but they expect to change a lot by eating a handful of mung beans and a few cordyceps. This is fine for simple and agile chicks and birds, but it is not so easy for people as big and complex as our bodies and minds to rely on it to change. Unless you have a very clean body, a very clear mind, and live a very simple life, a handful of mung beans will not be able to mobilize you, and a packet of soup is not easy to do.</p><p>There is a dialogue in the Yellow Emperor’s Classic of Internal Medicine:</p><p>“The Emperor said: Who is the one who has exhausted the form and blood, but has no merit?”</p><p>The Yellow Emperor asked Qi Bo, when a human body is broken and the blood is drained, it is difficult to cure the disease. Why is this?</p><p>“Qi Bo said: “God does not make it.”</p><p><strong>The patient’s spirit has not played its due role, and the doctor has no way to mobilize it.</strong></p><p>The Yellow Emperor then asked: What is the meaning of God not envoys?</p><p>Qi Bo replied: “Needle stone, Tao is also. If the spirit does not enter, the will will not be cured, so the disease cannot be cured. Now that the spirit has been destroyed, the honor and guard cannot be recovered. What? Weeping guards are removed, so the gods go away and the disease will not heal.”</p><p>Everyone is slowly pondering over this passage, why there are more and more illnesses and more and more incurable diseases, you can find the reasons from here.</p><p><strong>The source of everything lies in the invisible thoughts and spirits, and then there is energy, and then it is transformed into matter.</strong></p><p>All diseases, or the beginning of the world, come from this.</p><p><strong>The real wellness</strong><br><strong>is to feel yourself</strong></p><p>When a person lives with his own feelings, he starts from his heart, the origin is himself, and there is no dislocation.</p><p>What are the problems that are prone to occur in modern people?</p><p>We ask for a thing, a person, or a thing. There are always many lofty development plans, always thinking, thinking very far. Or follow a star and keep it in mind. Keep looking at this or that, or keep talking, keep doing things.</p><p><strong>When we take external things as the origin, we lose our sense of who we are and our surroundings.</strong></p><p>What is this state called in Chinese medicine? It is the “<strong>separation of form and spirit</strong>“.</p><p>What is the state of sitting quietly? It is the “Yellow Emperor’s Classic of Internal Medicine” that “form and spirit are combined”, or “body and mind are one”.</p><p>Now when it comes to nutrition, we need to eat well, an egg in the morning and a meal of meat in the evening, right?</p><p>We all burned stoves when we were young. The size of the fire determines how much firewood you should put in it. The reason is simple, right?</p><p>So why don’t we understand these truths when it comes to eating?</p><p>Your fire is obviously very small and weak, you have no digestion power, the flue is blocked, you have no bowel movement, no sweat, no exercise, you still eat steak and drink milk, it will only increase Fertilizers and blockages, put out the fire.</p><p>These truths do not need to be learned through medical knowledge to understand, they are the most basic common sense in daily life, and should be experienced in life.</p><p>Experience the different feelings of what you eat. Live consciously. If you feel uncomfortable after eating something, even if you don’t realize it until the tenth time, it is the beginning of awareness.</p><p><strong>It is best to be suitable for yourself, not to look for an external unified standard.</strong></p><p>Therefore, in life, you must develop the habit of mindfulness, to feel yourself, observe yourself, and then at least know:</p><ol><li><p>What is comfortable to eat and what is uncomfortable;</p></li><li><p>Who is comfortable with and who is uncomfortable with;</p></li><li><p>Thinking, saying, and doing will make you feel more at ease, or conversely, you will be unable to sleep, tangled and sad.</p></li></ol><p><strong>In life, if you observe yourself all the time, you can adjust yourself all the time. This is the real health preservation.</strong></p><p>Tune your mind and body</p><p>“The Yellow Emperor’s Classic of Internal Medicine” also has a higher requirement for health preservation and spiritual nourishment - “<strong>calm and emptiness</strong>“, which is close to the state of Taoist and Buddhist achievers.</p><p>“Tian” means quiet and peaceful, with a relaxed, slight sweetness.</p><p>The great joy and great sorrow that are common in TV dramas are relatively paranoid, lost, and lost, not an ordinary neutral state.</p><p>If this “tian” is replaced with “sweet”, which means “sweet”, there is a principle in traditional Chinese medicine called “sweetness to slow it down”, which means that all medicines, as long as they are sweet, such as licorice, can make people’s spirits. , The operation of the body, including the way people look at problems and their attitudes is softened and relaxed.</p><p>Many diseases now stem from the lack of “<strong>relief</strong>“.</p><p>For example, neurasthenia, anxiety disorders, bipolar syndrome, etc. are all common in this era. Everyone has fallen into a state of mental and psychological life that is too fast and too urgent.</p><p>If you are in a hurry, the gods will float outside, and the qi will be unstable. If it is tight and chaotic, the physiological functions will also be out of tune.</p><p>What does “light” mean? “I don’t care so much, I can do anything, I can.” So there is a lot of space, this is OK, that is OK; instead of having expectations, clinging to goals, and not wanting to control the situation.</p><p><strong>Ask and think less, and have less promising habits.</strong></p><p>Buddhism often says “purify one’s own mind”, Confucianism says “thinking without evil”, and Taoism says “destruction for the day”.</p><p>For people with poor health, I have a suggestion: <strong>live at ease</strong>.</p><p>Nowadays, many people are tired physically and mentally, but they are very enthusiastic about learning. Whether it’s good intentions or malicious intentions, it’s all intentions, and it’s best not to move too much. When the body is weak, the spirit is not easy to hold back.</p><p>From the perspective of traditional Chinese medicine, Taoism, and Buddhism, cultivating the mind is the priority, because at that time your body is as sensitive as an electronic balance, and a single thought will have a great change.</p><p>Teacher Nan Huaijin’s book often mentions that when you meditate to a relatively subtle level, your body will change and you will feel a single thought. It’s uncomfortable to think about it.</p><p>Subtle Perception - The Kung Fu of Emptying Oneself</p><p>There are two modes of human cognition:</p><p><strong>One is the primordial spirit, and the other is the consciousness of the spirit (in modern times, it is referred to by the heart or the brain).</strong></p><p>Knowledge of God is logical thinking, empirical judgment, and biased towards socialization. It is guided by long-term acquired education, environmental cues, and media, loaded from the outside world, and is a cognitive model used by “I”.</p><p><strong>“Yuanshen” refers to instinct and intuition.</strong> The “mind” and “comprehension” that is often mentioned in Chinese culture, such as calligraphy and painting, Guqin, traditional Chinese medicine, and martial arts, can achieve “superiority, the integration of things and me”, all in the Intuitive and instinctive.</p><p>There is a saying in the Book of Changes:</p><p>“The “Yi” has no thinking, no action, it is still and does not move, and it is easy to feel.”</p><p>The ancient Chinese sages believed that the true understanding of the universe and the universe is not obtained by thinking, not by something that can be approached, but when the mind is in a state of stillness, and when the mind is in a state of stillness and interacts with the universe, it naturally reaches everything.</p><p>Through traditional training methods, meditation, standing, Tai Chi… Let us gradually learn not to rely too much on facial features and logical thinking, and directly experience the reality of the moment with our heart.</p><p>I remember that some classes in college were really boring, and I couldn’t leave, so I just sat there and played: relax, put your fingers gently on Zusanli, put it on for dozens of minutes, and see what happens. This is the mentality of playing.</p><p>“Play” is a very important word in traditional culture. <strong>Many things are inadvertently realized in a relaxed state. If you think too hard and have too many goals, you will often miss them.</strong></p><p>When the finger is placed there, there is no feeling at first, and the acupoint is concave and deflated, which is “empty”; after a while, it starts to jump “suddenly, suddenly, suddenly”, “the meridian qi has arrived”, and the qi and blood begins It senses; after a while, it will slowly start to rise and fall on its own, opening and closing.</p><p>It will keep gaining momentum, and sometimes, it will feel that the force below is pushing upward, and at a certain time it will go down along the stomach meridian, down the calf, and go down to the ankle, but it can’t go down, why? There are joints. These places are not very easy to circulate, and it is easy to store evil spirits, so we must open up the joints.</p><p>After a while, it continued to gain momentum, “bang”, and reached the soles of the feet. It turned out that the cold air and hot air in the body came out in a “hu, hu, hu”.</p><p><strong>When your perception becomes more and more subtle, you will be able to know directly.</strong></p><p>After graduating from university, I helped my mother do moxibustion every weekend, and I also helped a teacher at that time. One night, I was very impressed. When I moxibustion the bladder meridian acupoints on his back, when he reached a certain point, he felt like there was a fountain gushing upwards in the acupoints, like a moxa stick that was hanging in the air.</p><p>This kind of feeling shows that it is real, and “reality is open”. The excess energy inside the human body will naturally spread out. What does emptiness feel like? When moxibustion hangs on the acupoints, it feels like being sucked in.</p><p>Later, I found that if I was relaxed enough, the hand holding the moxa stick would move on its own, and the aura on the patient’s back would change during the process of moxibustion. Guide your hand, which is actually the moxa stick, to where the body needs it.</p><p>This state often occurs when both parties are very relaxed, and the moxibustion is in a state of “emptiness and self-forgetfulness”. If the moxibustion practitioner is unsteady, inattentive, or has a strong purpose, although he is focused, but he is persistent and exerts himself, he will not be able to feel these.</p><p>The same is true of acupuncture. When learning acupuncture, you can often spare an hour to stay in the room and give yourself a needle. After trying it, meditate and experience what it feels like? As I said before, it was like throwing a stone into a pond, and the ripples spread out layer by layer, and I gradually knew where my body was blocked and where I was able to benefit.</p><p>When you are quiet and relaxed, and there are not so many thoughts, thoughts, emotions, desires, plans, and all kinds of troubles surging around, your heart is like a relatively clean mirror.</p><p><strong>Everything is clearly there, waiting for you to discover.</strong></p><p>You face this world every day, and you experience something new every day, like those pictures in fairy tales: Hey, Grandpa Sun is very happy today, the flowers smile at me, a bee flies by as if something happened to tell me.</p><p>Meditation to experience one’s own heart, feel the changes of the four seasons in the heaven and earth, the floating and sinking of flowers, birds, fish, and insects, the mutual sense of spirit, spirit, and body, taking things from afar and taking bodies near.</p><p>The answer is here.</p>]]></content>
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  
</search>
