<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<search>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>3 kinds of &quot;functional&quot; toothpaste that doctors are afraid of! These ingredients may induce enteritis</title>
    <link href="/3-kinds-of-functional-toothpaste-that-doctors-are-afraid-of-New-research-These-ingredients-may-induce-enteritis/"/>
    <url>/3-kinds-of-functional-toothpaste-that-doctors-are-afraid-of-New-research-These-ingredients-may-induce-enteritis/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Anti-moth, whitening, hemostasis, antibacterial, anti-allergic… Many people pay attention to the “function” written on the package when buying toothpaste, and rarely look at the specific ingredients.</p><p>Recently, the international academic journal “Nature Communications” published a study: an antibacterial agent triclosan (TCS) contained in some toothpastes may cause damage to the human intestine and induce enteritis.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202181.gif"></p><p>This ingredient in toothpaste can induce enteritis</p><p>The research, carried out by Tsai Zongwei’s team at Hong Kong Baptist University in collaboration with a foreign team, explains how the antibacterial agent triclosan (TCS) triggers intestinal inflammation.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202182.webp"></p><p>Studies have shown that after exposure to TCS, the intestinal toxicity of TCS is stimulated under the action of human gut microbial GUS enzymes, which in turn leads to the appearance of enteritis. By targeting the inhibition of gut microbial GUS enzymes, the harm of TCS to the human gut may be eliminated.</p><p>This study also further confirmed that TCS, a common ingredient in daily necessities, will cause certain harm to the human body, so you must pay more attention when choosing daily necessities.</p><p>Dentists are afraid of 3 toothpaste ingredients</p><p>According to the British “Daily Mail” report, many toothpaste ingredients are harmful to our health, Dr. Toby Talbert, a dental expert at the Royal College of Surgeons, reminded to pay attention to these 3 ingredients:</p><p>Descaler: It can easily cause mouth ulcers</p><p>The oral mucosa is one of the most delicate tissues, and sodium lauryl sulfate is the most effective cleaning agent, which can cause irritation or damage the oral mucosa, leading to chronic oral ulcers.</p><p>People with frequent oral ulcers and those with ulcers are best not to use toothpaste containing sodium lauryl sulfate.</p><p>Whitening agent: easy to damage gums</p><p>Bleaching agents such as hydrogen peroxide are added to many toothpastes to whiten teeth. However, they can irritate soft tissues, damage the oral mucosa, and damage the gums.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202183.gif"></p><p>In fact, the whiteness of teeth is related to enamel and dentin, which is difficult to change with toothpaste. Although bleaching agents can remove some stains on the surface of the teeth, they have little effect on the deep stains that are endogenous to the teeth.</p><p>Abrasives: can damage tooth enamel</p><p>Fine particles are added to many toothpastes to remove stains from the surface of the teeth, however, some ointments are not abrasive enough and can wear away the enamel, which can lead to sensitive teeth over time.</p><p>It is recommended to purchase toothpastes containing aluminum hydroxide or calcium hydrogen phosphate with fine particles. These abrasives are relatively good and cause less damage to the tooth surface.</p><p>“Functional toothpaste” should not be used indiscriminately</p><p>Toothpaste is used as a brushing aid. Its basic function is to clean the oral cavity. Generally, commercially available toothpastes can be satisfied after strict testing. The effects of whitening, anti-cavity, desensitization, and hemostasis are all auxiliary, and are not enough to directly affect oral health.</p><p>Whitening toothpaste:</p><p>Mainly, some special “friction particles” are added, which can remove the cigarette stains and tea stains deposited on the surface of the teeth, but have no effect on deep endogenous stains such as tetracycline teeth and fluorosis teeth.</p><p>If the friction particles are large and hard, long-term use may also cause tooth wear.</p><p>There are also some whitening toothpastes with blue paste, which can only achieve the “visual effect” of temporary whitening through blue foam.</p><p>Acid-proof toothpaste:</p><p>The principle is to form a protective film on the surface of the tooth, thereby enhancing the disease prevention ability of the periodontal tissue, but it should be stopped after symptoms improve, otherwise it will destroy the microbial ecological balance in the oral cavity.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202184.gif"></p><p>Antibacterial toothpaste:</p><p>Some medicated toothpastes have bactericidal and bacteriostatic ingredients, which can help kill some bacteria in the oral cavity in a short time, but daily use is equivalent to taking a small amount of antibiotics for a long time, which is not conducive to the microbalance of oral flora and is prone to drug resistance.</p><p>Anti-sensitive toothpaste:</p><p>Desensitizing ingredients such as fluoride and strontium chloride are added, which can only relieve mild dentin hypersensitivity to a certain extent.</p><p>Fresh breath toothpaste:</p><p>The freshness of the breath comes from brushing your teeth carefully, removing plaque and some harmful bacteria, not the fragrance of the toothpaste itself, so the “scent” of the toothpaste is not so important.</p><p>Choose a toothpaste that suits you</p><p>The use of toothpaste should vary from person to region and region, and should not be used blindly for a long time.</p><p> <img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202185.gif"></p><p>Mainly depends on the quality of the friction agent</p><p>Small particles should be selected to prevent damage to the tooth. The ones containing aluminum hydroxide and calcium hydrogen phosphate are better, followed by silica, and the particles of calcium carbonate are the largest.</p><p>change toothpaste</p><p>Using a toothpaste for a long time, the bacteria in the mouth will develop resistance and learn to “resist” the effect of toothpaste to clean the mouth.</p><p>One tube of household toothpaste</p><p>Sharing a toothpaste can easily lead to cross-infection of many oral diseases. If someone in the family catches a cold or suffers from other oral diseases, some viruses and bacteria may remain in the crevices of the toothbrush after brushing.</p><p>The next time you brush your teeth, the toothpaste comes in contact with the toothbrush, potentially transferring the virus to the toothpaste and spreading it to others through the toothpaste.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202186.gif"></p><p>Choose according to oral condition</p><p>For example, children can choose children’s toothpaste; family members with caries can use fluoride toothpaste; people with periodontitis can choose Chinese herbal toothpaste or toothpaste with anti-inflammatory ingredients.</p><p>Some areas are not suitable for fluoride toothpaste</p><p>Fluoride toothpaste can reduce the chance of cavities, prevent the surface of the teeth from being dissolved, and also make the dissolved teeth stronger. However, in high fluoride areas such as Shanxi, Inner Mongolia, and Hebei, the drinking water contains fluoride, so it is not suitable to use fluoride toothpaste.</p><p>Reminder: toothpaste is not a substitute for medical treatment. If you have oral ulcers, black teeth, toothache, caries, bad breath, etc., you should go to the doctor in time.</p>]]></content>
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Being with someone who makes you feel comfortable is also a regimen</title>
    <link href="/Being-with-someone-who-makes-you-feel-comfortable-is-also-a-egimen/"/>
    <url>/Being-with-someone-who-makes-you-feel-comfortable-is-also-a-egimen/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/Being-with-someone-who-makes-you-feel-comfortable.webp" alt="Being with someone who makes you feel comfortable is also a regimen"></p><p>Everything in the whole world is like a huge symphony. Walking with the big symphony of heaven and earth, walking in a normal and neutral way is the standard of health.</p><p>When you are sick, you are actually kicked out by God.</p><p>Therefore, disease was called “disorder” in ancient times, and the cause was called “disorder” or “lost power”.</p><p>So what is health? Health is “normal”.</p><p>Health does not mean that you are ruddy, full of energy or something, not these things, nor how much muscle strength, how much heartbeat…</p><p>What is “usually”?</p><p>The most important point is to be in a relatively harmonious relationship with oneself, with the society, and with this big world, and to be able to play with the natural rhythm.</p><p>When the weather is hot, everyone else sweats, and you can sweat too; you can walk without getting tired after walking for two hours. But if everyone else is afraid of cold, you still feel hot; if everyone else is sleepy, and you can’t sleep at 3:00 in the middle of the night, in fact, you have already begun to keep up.</p><p>If you think you are healthy, you are already very sick.</p><p>There are several stages of disease in the eyes of traditional Chinese medicine, the first stage is “shen” disease.</p><p>The mind is scattered, the mind is uncertain, and the concentration is not concentrated. This is a kind of.</p><p>Sensitive, easily attracted by the outside world, tempted, emotional, lustful, poor self-control, this is the second type.</p><p>In ordinary life, if you don’t sleep well, wake up easily, you are afraid of noise, the dark, and ghosts, this is a weak spirit.</p><p>The mental illness is serious, the form and spirit are separated, the heart and the mouth are different, the outside and inside are conflicting, you are no longer with yourself, you are not sincere, you can’t even express your emotions, or you can’t express your emotions too much.</p><p>For example, many variety shows now belong to “too”, the purpose is to exaggerate and provoke emotional outbursts, create obsessed fans, and easily get confused.</p><p>There is also “not enough”. When you should be happy, you have to suppress it. If you get used to it, you will not be happy anymore.</p><p>Too much, not too much, it’s all abnormal.</p><p>“There is no air at the moment” is also abnormal. I suddenly cried when it was time to be happy. It was originally sad, but forced myself to be strong. There are many such situations in real life, which is abnormal.</p><p>What is health?</p><p>Health is “normal”, and “neutralization”.</p><p>Therefore, after learning Chinese medicine, you will know that “I wish you every day is normal” is the greatest blessing.</p><p>In the past, my teacher taught me a trick to see a doctor: When Western medicine doesn’t know what it is, and Chinese medicine doesn’t know the cause, and you don’t know how to treat it, what should you do? Adjust normally.</p><p>Every time a patient comes for a follow-up consultation, he should be asked about his living condition, eat, drink, sleep, and sleep. These are the basic indicators of Chinese medicine treatment.</p><p>eat well? Did you sleep well? Are you moving? Does it pull well? Is it normal to sweat? Especially for chronic diseases, when these basic indicators are adjusted to normal, it means that the vitality is restored, and the qi mechanism becomes normal. At this time, the original vitality of the human body can resolve the disease.</p><p>Any disease is like this.</p><p>Now there is a big misunderstanding: if you have a disease, you must cure it.</p><p>Therefore, the patient or even the entire family will forget the normal life, no exercise, no life, no entertainment, no love, nothing, and only the tension and anxiety are left to fight the disease.</p><p>what is this? Abnormal.</p><p>Your swing is being disturbed or even stopped! In this case, even if you have the resources to find the best doctor in the world, it is useless. For a person to recover, he must enter a real and orderly normal life, in a state of ups and downs and mutual interaction with all things, in order to slowly heal the disease.</p><p>Therefore, with regard to health preservation and conditioning, the really important thing is to find a state of peace and comfort as much as possible. The same is true for healthy people. To do the right thing at the right time, at the right place, with the right person, in the right way, is health preservation. In Buddhism, it is called “right conduct” and “right action”.</p><p>All diseases are first “SHEN” diseases</p><p>Chinese medicine believes that all diseases are mental diseases first, then qi diseases, then blood diseases, and finally what? shape disease.</p><p>Diseases start from the invisible part of life, that is, from the spiritual and information level; in the second stage, to the qi part, the energy pattern and operation law are disordered; in the third stage, to the visible disease level.</p><p>The source of many people’s illnesses is some kind of great trouble, great resentment, or a lot of confusion that they cannot resolve. Many times, the disease is because they are unwilling to face, clarify, and solve.</p><p>Why do Confucianism, Buddhism and Taoism attach so much importance to “ashamed”, “introspection”, and “repentance”? First, you have to realize that you are wrong before you can “get away from it”.</p><p>As soon as one’s mind changes, so does his demeanor, and the direction of the life train also changes.</p><p>When a person’s body is seriously ill, the direction of the life train has been wrong for a long time.</p><p>But one thing must be remembered, beliefs have the opportunity to turn back at any time, and once the beliefs change, the demeanor has the opportunity to be corrected at any time.</p><p>Many people are ignorant of their own life, inner state, and physical and mental feelings, but they expect to change a lot by eating a handful of mung beans and a few cordyceps. This is fine for simple and agile chicks and birds, but it is not so easy for people as big and complex as our bodies and minds to rely on it to change. Unless you have a very clean body, a very clean mind, and live a very simple life, a handful of mung beans will not be able to mobilize you, and a packet of soup is not easy to do.</p><p>There is a dialogue in the Yellow Emperor’s Classic of Internal Medicine:</p><p>“The Emperor said: Who is the one who has exhausted the form and blood, but has no merit?”</p><p>The Yellow Emperor asked Qi Bo, when a human body is broken and the blood is drained, it is difficult to cure the disease. Why is this?</p><p>“Qi Bo said: “God does not make it.”</p><p>The patient’s spirit has not played its due role, and the doctor has no way to mobilize it.</p><p>The Yellow Emperor then asked: What is the meaning of God not envoys?</p><p>Qi Bo replied: “Needle stone, Tao is also. If the spirit does not enter, the will will not be cured, so the disease cannot be cured. Now that the spirit has been destroyed, the honor and guard cannot be recovered. What? Weeping guards are removed, so the gods go away and the disease will not heal.”</p><p>Everyone is slowly pondering over this passage, why there are more and more illnesses and more and more incurable diseases, you can find the reasons from here.</p><p>The source of everything lies in the invisible thoughts and spirits, and then there is energy, and then it is transformed into matter.</p><p>All diseases, or the beginning of the world, come from this.</p><p>real wellness<br>is to feel oneself</p><p>When a person lives with his own feelings, he starts from his heart, the origin is himself, and there is no dislocation.</p><p>What are the problems that are prone to occur in modern people?</p><p>We ask for a thing, a person or a thing. There are always many lofty development plans, always thinking, thinking very far. Or follow a star and keep it in mind. Keep looking at this or that, or keep talking, keep doing things.</p><p>When we take external things as the origin, we lose our sense of who we are and our surroundings.</p><p>What is this state called in Chinese medicine? It is “separation of form and spirit”.</p><p>What is the state of sitting quietly? It is the “Yellow Emperor’s Classic of Internal Medicine” that “form and spirit are combined”, or “body and mind are one”.</p><p>Now when it comes to nutrition, we need to eat well, an egg in the morning and a meal of meat in the evening, right?</p><p>We all burned stoves when we were young. The size of the fire determines how much firewood you should put in it. The reason is simple, right?</p><p>So why don’t we understand these truths when it comes to eating?</p><p>Your fire is obviously very small and weak, you have no digestion power, the flue is blocked, you have no bowel movement, no sweat, no exercise, you still eat steak and drink milk, it will only increase Fertilizers and blockages, put out the fire.</p><p>These truths do not need to be learned through medical knowledge to understand, they are the most basic common sense in daily life, and should be experienced in life.</p><p>Experience the different feelings of what you eat. Live consciously. If you feel uncomfortable after eating something, even if you don’t realize it until the tenth time, it is the beginning of awareness.</p><p>It is best to be suitable for yourself, not to look for an external unified standard.</p><p>Therefore, in life, you must develop the habit of mindfulness, to feel yourself, observe yourself, and then at least know:</p><ol><li><p>What is comfortable to eat and what is uncomfortable;</p></li><li><p>Who is comfortable with and who is uncomfortable with;</p></li><li><p>Thinking, saying, and doing will make you feel more at ease, or conversely, you will be unable to sleep, tangled and sad.</p></li></ol><p>In life, if you observe yourself all the time, you can adjust yourself all the time. This is the real health preservation.</p><p>Tune your mind and body</p><p>“The Yellow Emperor’s Classic of Internal Medicine” also has a higher requirement for health preservation and spiritual nourishment - “calm and emptiness”, which is close to the state of Taoist and Buddhist achievers.</p><p>“Tian” means quiet and peaceful, with a relaxed, slightly sweetness.</p><p>The great joy and great sorrow that are common in TV dramas are relatively paranoid, lost, and lost, not an ordinary neutral state.</p><p>If this “tian” is replaced with “sweet”, which means “sweet”, there is a principle in traditional Chinese medicine called “sweetness to slow it down”, which means that all medicines, as long as they are sweet, such as licorice, can make people’s spirits. , The operation of the body, including the way people look at problems and their attitudes are softened and relaxed.</p><p>Many diseases now stem from the lack of “relief”.</p><p>For example, neurasthenia, anxiety disorders, bipolar syndrome, etc. are all common in this era. In fact, everyone has fallen into a state of mental and psychological life that is too fast and too urgent.</p><p>If you are in a hurry, the gods will float outside, and the qi will be unstable. If it is tight and chaotic, the physiological functions will also be out of tune.</p><p>What does “light” mean? “I don’t care so much, I can do anything, I can.” So there is a lot of space, this is OK, that is OK; instead of having expectations, clinging to goals, and not wanting to control the situation.</p><p>Ask and think less, and have less promising habits.</p><p>Buddhism often says “purify one’s own mind”, Confucianism says “thinking without evil”, and Taoism says “destruction for the day”.</p><p>For people with poor health, I have a suggestion: don’t study too much.</p><p>Nowadays, many people are tired physically and mentally, but they are very enthusiastic about learning. Whether it’s good intentions or malicious intentions, it’s all intentions, and it’s best not to move too much. When the body is weak, the spirit is not easy to hold back.</p><p>From the perspective of traditional Chinese medicine, Taoism and Buddhism, cultivating the mind is the first priority, because at that time your body is as sensitive as an electronic balance, and a single thought will have a great change.</p><p>Teacher Nan Huaijin’s book often mentions that when you meditate to a relatively subtle level, your body will change and you will feel a single thought. It’s uncomfortable to think about it.</p><p>Subtle Perception - The Kung Fu of Emptying Oneself</p><p>There are two modes of human cognition:</p><p>One is the primordial spirit, and the other is the consciousness of the spirit (in modern times, it is referred to by the heart or the brain).</p><p>Knowledge of God is logical thinking, empirical judgment, and biased towards socialization. It is guided by long-term acquired education, environmental cues, and media, loaded from the outside world, and is a cognitive model used by “I”.</p><p>“Yuanshen” refers to instinct and intuition. The “mind” and “comprehension” that are often mentioned in Chinese culture, such as calligraphy and painting, Guqin, traditional Chinese medicine, and martial arts, can achieve “superiority, the integration of things and me”, all in the Intuitive and instinctive.</p><p>There is a saying in the Book of Changes:</p><p>“The “Yi” has no thinking, no action, it is still and does not move, and it is easy to feel.”</p><p>The ancient Chinese sages believed that the true understanding of the universe and the universe is not obtained by thinking, not by something that can be approached, but when the mind is in a state of stillness, and when the mind is in a state of stillness and interacts with the universe, it naturally reaches everything.</p><p>Through traditional training methods, meditation, standing, Tai Chi… Let us gradually learn not to rely too much on facial features and logical thinking, and directly experience the reality of the moment with our heart.</p><p>I remember that some classes in college were really boring, and I couldn’t leave, so I just sat there and played: relax, put your fingers gently on Zusanli, put it on for dozens of minutes, and see what happens. This is the mentality of playing.</p><p>“Play” is a very important word in traditional culture. Many things are inadvertently realized in a relaxed state. If you think too hard and have too many goals, you will often miss them.</p><p>When the finger is placed there, there is no feeling at first, and the acupoint is concave and deflated, which is “empty”; after a while, it starts to jump “suddenly, suddenly, suddenly”, “the meridian qi has arrived”, and the qi and blood begins It senses; after a while it will slowly start to rise and fall on its own, opening and closing.</p><p>It will keep gaining momentum, and sometimes, it will feel that the force below is pushing upward, and at a certain time it will go down along the stomach meridian, down the calf, and go down to the ankle, but it can’t go down, why? There are joints. These places are not very easy to circulate, and it is easy to store evil spirits, so we must open up the joints.</p><p>After a while, it continued to gain momentum, “bang”, and reached the soles of the feet. It turned out that the cold air and hot air in the body came out in a “hu, hu, hu”.</p><p>When your perception becomes more and more subtle, you will be able to know directly.</p><p>After graduating from university, I helped my mother do moxibustion every weekend, and I also helped a teacher at that time. One night, I was very impressed. When I moxibusted the bladder meridian acupoints on his back, when he reached a certain point, he felt like there was a fountain gushing upwards in the acupoints, like a moxa stick that was hanging in the air.</p><p>This kind of feeling shows that it is real, and “reality is open”. The excess energy inside the human body will naturally spread out. What does emptiness feel like? When moxibustion hangs on the acupoints, it feels like being sucked in.</p><p>Later, I found that if I was relaxed enough, the hand holding the moxa stick would move on its own, and the aura on the patient’s back would change during the process of moxibustion. Guide your hand, which is actually the moxa stick, to where the body needs it.</p><p>This state often occurs when both parties are very relaxed, and the moxibustor is in a state of “emptiness and self-forgetfulness”. If the moxibustion practitioner is unsteady, inattentive, or has a strong purpose, although he is focused, but he is persistent and exerts himself, he will not be able to feel these.</p><p>The same is true of acupuncture. When learning acupuncture, you can often spare an hour to stay in the room and give yourself a needle. After tying it, meditate and experience what it feels like? As I said before, it was like throwing a stone into a pond, and the ripples spread out layer by layer, and I gradually knew where my body was blocked and where I was able to benefit.</p><p>When you are quiet and relaxed, and there are not so many thoughts, thoughts, emotions, desires, plans and all kinds of troubles surging around, your heart is like a relatively clean mirror.</p><p>Everything is clearly there, waiting for you to discover.</p><p>You face this world every day, and you experience something new every day, like those pictures in fairy tales: Hey, Grandpa Sun is very happy today, the flowers smile at me, a bee flies by, as if something happened tell me.</p><p>Meditation to experience one’s own heart, feel the changes of the four seasons in the heaven and earth, the floating and sinking of flowers, birds, fish and insects, the mutual sense of spirit, spirit and body, taking things from afar and taking bodies near.</p><p>The answer is here.</p>]]></content>
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  
</search>
