<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<search>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Can a ketogenic diet help you lose weight Scientist Yes! but can also promote a variety of diseases</title>
    <link href="/Can-a-ketogenic-diet-help-you-lose-weight-Scientist-Yes-but-can-also-promote-a-variety-of-diseases/"/>
    <url>/Can-a-ketogenic-diet-help-you-lose-weight-Scientist-Yes-but-can-also-promote-a-variety-of-diseases/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>For many people, losing weight is a “blocked and long” thing, and the “ketogenic diet” seems to be a shortcut for many people who want to lose weight: as long as you adjust the diet pattern, you can lose weight quickly.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203161.webp"></p><p>This eating pattern may help you lose weight, but a new study suggests that the ketogenic diet may cause long-term health damage and increase the risk of several diseases.</p><p>What exactly is a ketogenic diet? How does it make you lose weight? What are the health effects of sticking to this eating pattern for a long time?</p><p><strong>What is a ketogenic diet?</strong></p><p>The ketogenic diet is a very low-carb, high-fat dietary pattern.</p><p>In an ordinary balanced diet, carbohydrates account for 50% to 65% of total calories, fat accounts for 20% to 30%, and protein accounts for 10% to 15%.</p><p>In the ketogenic diet mode, carbohydrate energy supply only accounts for 4% to 17% of total calories, fat accounts for 60% to 90%, and protein accounts for 6% to 35%.</p><p>To put it bluntly, it is to eat less or even no carbohydrates, eat a moderate amount of protein, and a lot of fat.</p><p>During a ketogenic diet, the body produces a class of substances called ketone bodies, hence the name.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203162.gif"></p><p><em><strong>What does this eating pattern do?</strong></em></p><p><strong>Relieve epilepsy in children</strong></p><p>The ketogenic diet first appeared in the early 1920s. It was first used by a doctor named Russel Wilder to treat patients, and the therapy spread. Data show that the ketogenic diet can stop 14% of children with epilepsy and reduce the intensity of the disease in about 50% of children with epilepsy.</p><p><strong>lose weight</strong></p><p>Burn fat: Low carbohydrate intake forces the body to break down glycogen stored in the muscles and liver for energy. Glycogen is depleted, and the body turns to use fat for metabolic decomposition, producing ketone bodies, which provide energy for the body. In this way, ketone bodies replace glucose to provide energy to the body.</p><p>Block fat synthesis: Without the stimulation of glucose, the level of insulin secretion by the body also becomes very low, so that the body’s pathway for fat synthesis and metabolism is hindered.</p><p>While constantly decomposing fat, while unable to synthesize adipose tissue, the body fat content will drop again and again to achieve the effect of weight loss.</p><p><strong>A ketogenic diet increases the risk of multiple diseases</strong></p><p>Some people indeed lose weight after following the ketogenic diet, and many people indeed experience various side effects after the ketogenic diet, including hair loss, constipation, irregular menstruation in women, fatigue, headaches, nausea, rough skin, etc.</p><p>In an article recently published in the Swiss journal Frontiers in Nutrition, researchers from the American Society of Responsible Physicians, New York University, the University of Pennsylvania, George Washington University, and Bellevue Hospital in New York evaluated the ketogenic diet. The conclusion is that a ketogenic diet may cause long-term health damage: A high-fat diet increases the risk of several diseases, including heart disease, cancer, diabetes, and Alzheimer’s disease.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203163.webp"></p><p>“The typical ketogenic diet is a disease-causing disaster,” said the study leader.</p><p>The researchers say there is currently a lack of long-term and large-scale studies on the ketogenic diet. Based on the available evidence, the risks of a ketogenic diet clearly outweigh the benefits for most people.</p><p>The following injuries make the body unbearable:</p><p><strong>Affect tissue repair</strong></p><p>Protein utilization is altered during the ketogenic diet-induced ketosis process, causing the body to allocate as much protein as possible to gluconeogenesis and only the least necessary amount for tissue repair.</p><p><strong>impaired bowel function</strong></p><p>Ketogenic diets are low in fiber and can be detrimental to healthy gut function, and gut health affects every aspect of your body’s health.</p><p><strong>cause malnutrition</strong></p><p>Rejecting carbohydrate foods is bound to bring the risk of an unbalanced diet and micronutrient deficiencies, which can lead to serious health problems if maintained for a long time without timely correction.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203164.gif"></p><p><strong>Cause “ketone” poisoning</strong></p><p>Excessive accumulation of ketone bodies in the blood can cause ketoacidosis, nausea, vomiting, the smell of rotten apples in the breath, dehydration, shock, headache, dizziness, drowsiness, severe cases, coma, and cerebral hypoxia.</p><p><strong>lead to the formation of kidney stones</strong></p><p>One of the greatest potential risks of a ketogenic diet is the formation of kidney stones, a finding that is frequently mentioned in the pediatric epilepsy literature. Moreover, a high-protein ketogenic diet can also accelerate kidney failure in patients with kidney disease.</p><p><strong>cause cardiovascular disease</strong></p><p>With such a high proportion of fat, it is bound to bring the risk of excessive intake of saturated fatty acids and increase the risk of cardiovascular disease.</p><p><strong>increased cancer risk</strong></p><p>In epidemiological studies, diets high in saturated fat, trans fat, monosaccharides, and animal protein (especially from red and processed meat), as well as low in dietary fiber, substantially increase the risk of nonalcoholic fatty liver disease risk of developing nonalcoholic steatohepatitis, which increases the risk of hepatocellular carcinoma.</p><p><strong>6 diets for weight control</strong></p><p>The ketogenic diet is particularly difficult for people who have difficulty losing weight. Under the supervision of professionals, they may be able to try it for a short time. After reaching the weight loss goal, they should slowly transition back to a healthy and balanced diet.</p><p>For ordinary people, don’t try it lightly, especially don’t use it for a long time without authorization.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203165.gif"></p><p>If you want to control your weight scientifically and healthily, you can do the following things in terms of diet.</p><p><strong>Eat enough 5 nutrients</strong></p><p>These 5 types of nutrients are essential when losing weight, otherwise, the body will not even have the power to break down fat.</p><p>necessary sugars. Each person should consume at least 100 grams of carbohydrates per day, which is equivalent to about 150 grams of rice or wheat (raw weight).</p><p>B vitamins. In particular, the intake of B1 (thiamine) and B2 (riboflavin) is the premise to ensure vigorous energy metabolism during physical exercise.</p><p>Vitamin C. During exercise, a large number of reactive oxygen species are produced, which can cause oxidative damage to the body. Vitamin C can effectively scavenge active oxygen free radicals.</p><p>Mineral elements. Iron is involved in the transport of oxygen in the body and the process of tissue respiration; zinc can ensure the smooth metabolism of substances and energy in the body during exercise; chromium can promote the utilization of energy substances such as glucose by muscles, increase muscle growth and fat burning efficiency.</p><p>High-quality protein. Adequate intake of high-quality protein can promote the burning efficiency of muscle on fat and improve the weight loss effect of exercise.</p><p><strong>Choose a light cooking method</strong></p><p>Compared with frying, cooking methods such as steaming and blanching help people reduce fat intake and control energy intake. Usually, you can try to choose cooking methods such as steaming and blanching, and the operation is simpler.</p><p><strong>4 “Energy Dishes” to Avoid</strong></p><p>When eating out, try to avoid dishes with words such as “boiled”, “dry pot”, “dry stir-fry” and “salted egg yolk baked”. These are high-oil, high-salt, and high-fat dishes, which are not only bad for weight loss but also will cause a burden on health.</p><p>Adhere to eating until you are full for a long time, not only is it conducive to weight control, but also can ensure nutritional intake and keep your mind clear.</p><p><strong>Eat less high-energy snacks</strong></p><p>Do not put high-calorie snacks in the office, living room, etc., and replace them with nuts, yogurt, etc. Do not deal with breakfast, eat and drink dinner, office workers try to prepare their own lunch, less takeout.</p><p><strong>eat the right staple</strong></p><p>Substitute beans and potatoes for some bread, rice, and add beans to staples. When eating foods such as steamed sweet potatoes and shredded potatoes, be sure to deduct the amount of other staple foods.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203166.gif"></p><p><strong>Eat meat, prefer poultry, fish, and shrimp</strong></p><p>The fat content of poultry meat and fish and shrimp is low, which is beneficial to control calories. It is recommended that obese people increase the intake of poultry meat, fish, and shrimp, and appropriately reduce the proportion of livestock meat.</p><p>It is best to remove the skin when eating chicken and duck meat. The skin fat content is as high as 50%, which can be described as half a mouthful of oil.</p><p>If you prefer livestock meat, choose pure lean meat with lower calories.</p>]]></content>
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Women who eat spicily often have a lower risk of high blood pressure</title>
    <link href="/Women-who-eat-spicy-often-have-lower-risk-of-high-blood-pressure/"/>
    <url>/Women-who-eat-spicy-often-have-lower-risk-of-high-blood-pressure/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>“Spicy”, a taste that can directly hit the soul, is actually a burning sensation in the body. Eating spicy food is not only good for mouth addiction, but also good for health: new research finds that eating spicy food regularly can prevent high blood pressure.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203151.webp"></p><p><strong>Eating spicy food often reduces the risk of high blood pressure</strong></p><p>Recently, Li Liming and others from the School of Public Health of Peking University analyzed the data of nearly 54,000 people in Tongxiang, Zhejiang Province in the China Chronic Disease Perspective Research Project and found that eating spicy food can prevent high blood pressure, but this phenomenon is only seen in women.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203152.webp"></p><p>The study included 53,916 adults aged 30 to 79, of whom 44.4% had high blood pressure and 12.3% ate spicy food at least once a week.</p><p>After adjusting for potential confounding factors such as sociodemographic status, lifestyle factors, body mass index, waist circumference, sleep duration, and snoring, among women, eating spicy food 1–2 times per week and greater than Three times, the risk of developing high blood pressure was reduced by 10% and 12%, respectively. The more times women ate spicy food per week, the more significant the decrease in systolic and diastolic blood pressure.</p><p>For men, there was no significant difference in the risk of hypertension and systolic and diastolic blood pressure levels according to the number of times spicy food was consumed per week.</p><p>Among those who drank alcohol, those who ate spicy food daily had only a 2% lower risk of developing high blood pressure compared with those who never ate spicy food; but among those who did not drink alcohol, those who ate spicy food daily had a 28% lower risk of high blood pressure %. After excluding 1128 patients with a diagnosis of gastric ulcer, the inverse association between the number of spicy meals per week and the risk of hypertension remained.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203153.gif"></p><p>The researchers pointed out that the specific mechanism of eating spicy food to reduce the risk of high blood pressure is still unclear, and the possible reason may be related to the capsaicin contained in red peppers.</p><p><strong>Eating spicy food is a kind of “benign masochism”</strong></p><p>Spicy is not a taste, but a “painful feeling”. Since chili is painful, why do people enjoy it so much?</p><p>This may be related to “benign masochism,” which refers to people enjoying negative experiences that the body or brain misinterprets as a threat. Once the real danger is realized, the difference in cognitive and physical responses leads to a The pleasant excitement of people can also be understood as a kind of “adventure”.</p><p>The fear of bungee jumping, the fear of watching horror movies, the thrill of riding a roller coaster, the bitterness of tasting coffee, the pain of feeling massage, etc., can all be said to be a kind of “benign masochism”.</p><p>This may be a mechanism of self-preservation, regularly experiencing manageable danger, and may help us survive when we are actually faced with a threat because of the ability to cope better with repeated practice in the past.</p><p>Eating spicy food is not just as simple as a mouthful. Chili can not only promote the secretion of digestive juice, increase appetite, but also help health:</p><p><strong>vitamin supplement</strong></p><p>Chili peppers are rich in vitamin A, vitamin C, vitamin E, vitamin K, B vitamins, carotene, folic acid, and other vitamins, as well as minerals such as calcium and iron, and dietary fiber.</p><p><strong>Pain relief and heat dissipation</strong></p><p>Chili can reduce body temperature through sweating, relieve muscle pain, and have auxiliary antipyretic and analgesic effects. American studies have found that capsaicin can reduce the neurotransmitters that convey pain and reduce pain.</p><p><strong>Promote blood circulation</strong></p><p>Chinese medicine believes that chili peppers have certain medicinal properties, which can “perspire, remove phlegm, and dehumidify”. Modern medicine believes that pepper can promote blood circulation and prevent frostbite.</p><p><strong>Relieve stress</strong></p><p>The stimuli of spicy will prompt the body to secrete a lot of endorphins, which makes people feel happy and euphoric.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203154.gif"></p><p><strong>Improve skin</strong></p><p>Chili can promote hormone secretion in the body and improve skin conditions. Acne is not a problem with peppers. Only if you have a physique that loves acne, it will add fuel to the fire after eating peppers.</p><p><strong>Help prevent cancer</strong></p><p>An analysis of chronic prospective studies in China showed that compared with those who never or rarely ate spicy food, those who ate spicy food every month had a 12% lower risk of esophageal cancer; those who ate spicy food 1-2 days a week had a 24% lower risk of esophageal cancer.</p><p><strong>Helps reduce mortality</strong></p><p>A US study found that compared with people who rarely or never eat spicy food, those who eat spicy food have a 26% relative reduction in cardiovascular disease mortality; a 23% relative reduction in cancer mortality; and a 25% relative reduction in all-cause mortality.</p><p><em><strong>4 things to eat healthy and spicy</strong></em></p><p>Although it is good to eat spicy food, it should not be blind. When you eat it, do the following 4 things well to add points to your health.</p><p><strong>Grasp the spiciness</strong></p><p>When the spiciness is obviously beyond the body’s capacity, the body will excrete capsaicin as soon as possible through diarrhea and vomiting, and once the spiciness is too high, the joy of eating spicy food may be less than the pain, so eat spicy food according to your ability.</p><p><strong>Choose the right food</strong></p><p>You can choose fresh peppers, which are more nutritious, and after high-temperature cooking, the spicy taste will be reduced.</p><p>Match with cool foods, such as duck, fish, bitter gourd, lotus root, tofu, lettuce, etc.;</p><p>Coarse grains such as corn or sweet potatoes are rich in dietary fiber, which can prevent constipation caused by heat in the stomach;</p><p>Drink more water or soup to avoid dry throat and cleft lips, you can choose chrysanthemum tea;</p><p>Eating some sour fruits, such as apples, pears, pomegranates, bananas, hawthorn, grapes, etc., can stimulate the secretion of digestive juice and accelerate gastrointestinal motility.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203155.gif"></p><p><strong>Several types of people avoid spicy food</strong></p><p>Patients with cardiovascular and cerebrovascular diseases, gastrointestinal diseases, hyperthyroidism, constipation, eye diseases, oral ulcers, etc., should try to avoid spicy food.</p><p><strong>Two tricks to help you unwind</strong></p><p>If you are “spicy”, you can drink some milk. The casein in it can wrap up the capsaicin and take it away, which can have a good anti-spicy effect.</p><p>If there are too many peppers when cooking, you may wish to add some vinegar. When eating in a restaurant, if you feel that the dish is spicy, you can also have a small dish of vinegar dipped in it. The acetic acid in vinegar neutralizes the spiciness and reduces irritation.</p>]]></content>
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Eating walnuts has new evidence for longevity! Eat enough of this amount every week to benefit greatly</title>
    <link href="/Eating-walnuts-has-new-evidence-for-longevity-Eat-enough-of-this-amount-every-week-to-benefit-greatly/"/>
    <url>/Eating-walnuts-has-new-evidence-for-longevity-Eat-enough-of-this-amount-every-week-to-benefit-greatly/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The nut is known as the “longevity fruit” is _____? Without a doubt, the answer is “walnuts”.</p><p>High in protein, minerals, and vitamins, walnuts are the best among nuts. Several previous studies have found that eating walnuts in moderation can help reduce the risk of cardiovascular disease.</p><p>Recently, a Harvard research team gave new evidence that walnuts are good for health:</p><p>Consuming more than 5 servings (28 grams per serving) of walnuts per week was associated with a reduced risk of both all-cause mortality and cardiovascular disease and increased life expectancy by 1.3 years, compared with those who never ate walnuts.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203141.jpg"></p><p>Harvard University:</p><p>140 grams of walnuts per week can help prolong the life</p><p>For the study, researchers analyzed data from 93,340 adults, including 67,014 women in the American Nurses’ Health Study (NHS) cohort, and 26,326 men in the Health Professionals Follow-up Study (HPFS) cohort.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203142.png"></p><p>Participants were free of cancer, heart disease, and stroke when they participated in the study and were followed for about 20 years. The researchers examined their diets every 4 years, including overall dietary intake, frequency of eating walnuts and other nuts, and exercise and smoking status.</p><p>After adjusting for multivariate factors, the researchers found that walnut intake was inversely associated with all-cause mortality and mortality from cardiovascular disease.</p><p>Eating more than 5 servings of walnuts per week (a 28-gram serving, about two or three walnuts) may have the greatest benefit in reducing mortality and prolonging life, compared with people who do not eat walnuts, specifically, about the risk of all-cause mortality. A 14% reduction was associated with a 25% reduction in the risk of dying from cardiovascular disease and could increase life expectancy by about 1.3 years.</p><p>Eating 2-4 servings of walnuts per week was associated with a 13% lower risk of all-cause death, a 4% lower risk of death from cardiovascular disease, and an approximately 1-year increase in life expectancy.</p><p>Even eating just a few handfuls of walnuts a week may promote longevity, researchers say, especially in people whose diets are inherently low-quality.</p><p>However, the researchers also emphasized that, as an observational study, the conclusion still needs further research to confirm. Nonetheless, this finding is strong evidence that eating walnuts may help prolong life and be healthier in general.</p><p><strong>Nutritional advantages of a walnut</strong></p><p>In addition to helping prolong life, there has been researching on the health benefits of walnuts.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203143.gif"></p><p>Protects the heart and reduces inflammation levels</p><p>A study published in the Journal of the American College of Cardiology (JACC) involving 634 participants found that walnuts may help improve heart health and reduce the risk of inflammation.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203144.png"></p><p><strong>Helps prevent diabetes</strong></p><p>Research from Harvard University in the United States shows that eating walnuts twice a week can reduce the risk of type 2 diabetes by 24%, especially for women. The data is more positive.</p><p><strong>Improve gut health</strong></p><p>In 2020, a study published in the Journal of Nutrition pointed out that walnuts can promote the growth of beneficial bacteria in the gut, improve gut health, and help reduce the risk of cardiovascular disease in the long run.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203145.png"></p><p>According to nutrition experts, walnuts have the following advantages in food composition:</p><p><strong>Contains omega 3 fatty acids</strong></p><p>Namely alpha-linolenic acid, this fatty acid can be converted into DHA (docosahexaenoic acid) in the body.</p><p>The International Society for the Study of Fatty Acids and Lipids recommends that adults consume 500 mg of omega-3 fatty acids per day.</p><p>Two walnuts a day can meet the body’s need for omega 3 fatty acids.</p><p>It should be reminded that eating walnuts is beneficial but not equivalent to “brain-enhancing”. Human intelligence reaches its peak around the age of 20 to 30, and it is difficult to improve after that.</p><p><strong>sphingomyelin</strong></p><p>It is one of the structural substances that make up the nervous system and an essential raw material for the development of the nervous system.</p><p><strong>high in phytochemicals</strong></p><p>Walnuts are rich in antioxidants such as vitamin E, polyphenols, and minerals such as calcium, magnesium, and potassium, especially polyphenols.</p><p>The American Chemical Society is particularly optimistic about walnuts, thinking that the antioxidant effect of walnuts is nearly twice that of other nuts, and you can eat 7 per day.</p><p><strong>How to eat walnuts to benefit the most?</strong></p><p>Based on a balanced diet, eating a small number of walnuts every day is a simple, low-cost self-care measure.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203146.gif"></p><p><strong>Amount: 2~3 per day</strong></p><p>The protein content of walnut kernel is 12%<del>20%, the fat is about 60%</del>70%, and the dietary fiber is about 5%.</p><p>It is recommended to eat 10 grams of nut kernels as a snack every day, and there are about 10 grams of nut kernels in two or three walnuts.</p><p>It’s okay to eat up to 25~28 grams, but you need to reduce the intake of other foods accordingly, such as using walnuts to replace snacks such as biscuits and beef jerky, or using less oily steamed dishes instead of fried dishes when cooking.</p><p><strong>Flavor: Original</strong></p><p>To eat walnuts, the original flavor is preferred, no salt or sugar is added, and it is best to eat it together with the brown skin of the outer layer of the walnut kernel.</p><p><strong>Method: open and eat</strong></p><p>The opening of the walnut and the breaking of the walnut kernel will increase its exposure to oxygen, thereby promoting oxidative deterioration.</p><p>In oxidized walnut kernels, vitamin E is destroyed, antioxidants such as polyphenols are lost, and omega 3 fatty acids may also be destroyed.</p><p>Health is inseparable from a balanced diet. If you often overeat, even eating more walnuts will not help. Based on a healthy diet, taking walnuts as a healthy snack supplement is beneficial to health.</p>]]></content>
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>No one can escape the invasion of inflammation! 1 in 6 cancers are associated with it</title>
    <link href="/No-one-can-escape-the-invasion-of-inflammation-1-in-6-cancers-are-associated-with-it/"/>
    <url>/No-one-can-escape-the-invasion-of-inflammation-1-in-6-cancers-are-associated-with-it/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>“Inflammation” is a symptom that everyone has experienced, such as rhinitis, tonsillitis, gastroenteritis… Strictly speaking, inflammation is not a disease, but a common clinical-pathological process.</p><p>We live in a world full of bacteria, and arguably no one is immune to inflammation. Some people think that inflammation is a small problem, and it will go away after a while; some people regard it as a beast of a flood, and they start taking medicine at the slightest sign.</p><p> <img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203131.gif"></p><p><strong>1 in 6 cancers are caused by inflammation</strong></p><p>Inflammation belongs to the basic immune response and is a basic pathological process mainly based on defense response that occurs when the body is subjected to certain stimuli (such as trauma, infection, and other damage factors).</p><p>When tissue is damaged, an inflammatory response is triggered to prevent the spread of infection, remove necrotic tissue, and restore organ function. If the body does not have an inflammatory response, the body cannot control the infection and repair the damage.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203132.gif"></p><p>Leaving inflammation unattended can have serious consequences:<br>When the local lesions of inflammation are severe and the pathogenic microorganisms spread in the body, there will be systemic reactions, such as fever, increased heart rate, increased blood pressure, chills, anorexia, etc. Severe systemic infections can also lead to sepsis and even shock.</p><p>Inflammation is an important part of the development of some major diseases. According to a report by the International Cancer Research Center under the World Health Organization, one-sixth of the world’s cancers are caused by bacterial and viral infections, and most of these infections are what we commonly call “inflammation.”</p><p><strong>Inflammation is the source of many diseases</strong></p><p>It is generally believed that a controlled inflammatory response is beneficial. Once out of balance, some inflammatory factors will be produced, causing damage to normal organs and tissues.</p><p><strong>diabetes</strong></p><p>Inflammation causes insulin resistance; in addition, inflammation stimulates the abnormal metabolism of fat cells, secretes excessive inflammatory factors, further damages pancreatic islet cells, accelerates the development of diabetes, and forms a vicious circle.</p><p><strong>Nervous system disease</strong></p><p>Uncontrolled inflammation produces neurotoxicity that damages neuronal cells. For example, some cells in the brains of Alzheimer’s patients release inflammatory factors that exacerbate neuronal degeneration.</p><p><strong>obesity</strong></p><p>When adipose accumulation secretes excess adipocytokines, it causes systemic chronic inflammation, and adipose tissue macrophage infiltration exacerbates this chronic low-grade inflammatory state.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203133.gif"></p><p><strong>Cardiovascular diseases</strong></p><p>The root cause of common cardiovascular diseases is the intrusion of inflammatory factors into the blood vessel wall caused by immune disorders, thereby causing the onset of diseases such as atherosclerosis and coronary heart disease.</p><p><strong>cancer</strong></p><p>In chronic inflammation, repair and regeneration require cell proliferation, and the more cells divide, the greater the chance of errors in DNA replication, increasing the odds of producing cancer cells. If the tiny cancer cells accumulate over time, they will form a malignant tumor.</p><p><strong>depression</strong></p><p>Inflammation is one of the causes of depression, and even a slight increase in chronic inflammation increases the risk of depression. During the onset of depression, both inflammatory cytokine release and inflammatory responses are active.</p><p><strong>6 Eating Habits That Are ‘Pro-Inflammatory’</strong></p><p>The daily diet is closely related to the occurrence of inflammation. The following 6 eating habits may let inflammation sneak up on you.</p><p><strong>eat too finely</strong></p><p>Bread, rice, etc., these highly processed staples are rich in refined carbohydrates and have a high blood sugar response, which can lead to an elevated inflammatory response.</p><p><strong>High-sugar, high-salt diet</strong></p><p>High-sugar foods such as cakes, chocolates, and desserts will make blood sugar fluctuate greatly, leading to increased levels of insulin, adrenaline, and glucocorticoids; it will also consume a large number of B vitamins in the body, leading to increased inflammatory responses.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203134.gif"></p><p>The Institute of Medical Laboratory Animals of the Chinese Academy of Medical Sciences found that high salt can activate platelets and activate cells involved in inflammatory responses, thereby causing vascular inflammation.</p><p><strong>Eat processed meat</strong></p><p>Bacon, cured meat, ham, barbecue, etc., all bring pro-inflammatory substances, including polyaromatic hydrocarbons, heterocyclic amines, etc.</p><p>Beef, mutton, pork, and other red meats are rich in saturated fat, and long-term intake of too much can easily lead to obesity, which is also a special kind of inflammation.</p><p><strong>eat too many snacks</strong></p><p>When there are words such as margarine, margarine, non-dairy creamer, vegetable butter, hydrogenated vegetable oil, cocoa butter substitute, etc. on the package, there is a high probability that these foods contain trans fatty acids.</p><p>Trans fatty acids can increase the levels of various inflammatory factors, which may be related to the disturbance of lipid metabolism pathways.</p><p><strong>Eating fast food and fried food</strong></p><p>Common fast food and some fried foods are high in saturated fat, which not only promotes inflammation, but also has adverse effects on body weight, cardiovascular system, and immune system.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203135.gif"></p><p><strong>frequent drinking</strong></p><p>Not only does alcohol burden the liver, but it also kills normal healthy bacteria in the gut, disrupts the structure of the gut microbiome, and induces an inflammatory response.</p><p><strong>Do 4 things to “anti-inflammation” in the body</strong></p><p>The causes of the inflammation can be divided into endogenous factors and exogenous factors.</p><p>▶Endogenous factors: DNA damage, abnormal telomere function, epigenome damage, abnormal mitotic signaling and oxidative stress, etc.;</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203136.gif"></p><p>▶Exogenous factors: infection, external environment and poison stimuli, bad eating habits, etc.</p><p>Endogenous factors are difficult to change, but we can avoid or control inflammation by reducing the influence of exogenous factors.</p><p><strong>away from polluted environment</strong></p><p>Physical factors such as high temperature, low temperature, ultraviolet rays and radiation, biological factors such as viruses, bacteria, fungi, and parasites, chemical factors such as strong acids, strong bases, and formaldehyde, as well as the improper use of drugs and other biological agents, may all cause inflammation.</p><p>Avoid contact with harmful substances in life, clean your home frequently, ensure that the indoor environment is clean and tidy, do not use drugs indiscriminately, and try not to use pesticides, hair dyes, and other products.</p><p><strong>learn to deal with stress</strong></p><p>Continued psychological stress may disrupt the body’s ability to regulate inflammatory activity.</p><p>To maintain a positive and healthy attitude towards life, sleep 7-8 hours a day, learn to regulate your emotions when things go wrong, and seek help from a psychiatrist if necessary.</p><p><strong>form a habit of exercise</strong></p><p>When muscles contract, they can secrete some cytokines and actin with a smaller molecular weight. These substances enter the blood and can reduce the inflammatory response of the whole body to a certain extent.</p><p>When exercising, you should not only do aerobic exercise but also pay attention to enhancing muscle strength. It is recommended that physically able people do some weight-bearing exercises appropriately.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203137.gif"></p><p><strong>develop good eating habits</strong></p><p>Try to get rid of the “pro-inflammatory” diet mentioned earlier, and gradually develop good eating habits.</p><p>Dr. Andrew Weir, a professor of medicine at the University of Arizona in the United States, has a famous “anti-inflammatory food pyramid” theory.</p><p>Fruits and vegetables have the best anti-inflammatory effect, and consume at least 4 to 5 servings of vegetables every day, about 80 grams per serving;</p><p>Coarse grains, pasta, and beans are second, and should be eaten every day;</p><p>Organic canola oil, nuts, and other healthy fats rank third, and should consume 5-7 servings per day;</p><p>Fish and seafood can consume 2 to 6 servings per week (1 serving is about 113 grams).</p><p>In addition, it is necessary to reduce the consumption of instant noodles, biscuits, fast food, and other foods, and stay away from tobacco and alcohol.</p><p>If you suffer from severe acute inflammation or a disease caused by acute inflammation, it is difficult to control only by changing your lifestyle. You should seek medical treatment in time and receive treatment by the doctor’s advice to avoid various complications caused by worsening inflammation.</p>]]></content>
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>If you don&#39;t sleep well, you will gain weight! Fast fat accumulation in just 4 days</title>
    <link href="/If-you-dont-sleep-well-you-will-gain-weight-Fast-fat-accumulation-in-just-4-days/"/>
    <url>/If-you-dont-sleep-well-you-will-gain-weight-Fast-fat-accumulation-in-just-4-days/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Eating too many sweets will make you fat, eating too much-fried food will make you fat, drinking too much milk tea will make you fat… It is difficult for the body to be “thin”, and many people are used to throwing the pot to their cravings. In fact, in addition to eating, there are some unexpected factors for fat accumulation.</p><p> <img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203121.gif"></p><p><strong>After 4 days of not sleeping well, fat accumulates</strong></p><p>A study published in the American “Journal of Lipid Research” showed that 4 days without good sleep will lead to rapid accumulation of body fat and weight gain.</p><p>The researchers studied 15 healthy men in their 20s. For the week before the start, the participants got 10 hours of sleep each night at home. During the experiment, the participants ate high-fat, high-calorie food and slept less than 5 hours a night for 4 consecutive days.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203122.webp"></p><p>It was found that most of the participants said they were more likely to feel hungry when they were sleep-deprived than when they were getting enough sleep. Blood test results found that lack of sleep causes fat in the blood to be quickly removed after meals and stored by the body, which in turn leads to rapid weight gain.</p><p>When sleep deprivation occurs, people eat more (especially high-calorie foods) and store it as extra energy, the researchers said. This can lead to a spike in insulin, rapid fat storage, and rapid weight gain.</p><p>Therefore, to lose weight and lose fat, in addition to a reasonable diet and active exercise, you must also “sleep well”. The National Sleep Foundation recommends that adults get 7 to 9 hours of sleep each night.</p><p><strong>It’s so easy to gain weight</strong></p><p>It is often heard that people use “drinking cold water to gain weight” to describe how easy it is to gain weight. Some of the reasons that make people fat in life may surprise you.</p><p><strong>don’t like the sun</strong></p><p>Experts from the University of Southern California pointed out that the lack of vitamin D in the body can lead to the accumulation of fat in the muscles, but the vitamin D in the body can only be synthesized in sunlight. Those who like to live a “nightlife” are in danger of becoming big fat people.</p><p><strong>skip breakfast</strong></p><p>According to a survey published by the British “Daily Mail”, people who skip breakfast may gain 26 pounds a year.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203123.gif"></p><p><strong>eat too fast</strong></p><p>A joint study by the Graduate School of Okayama University and the Center for Health Management in Japan shows that eating too fast has a greater impact on weight than other eating habits such as being greasy and full.</p><p>The study showed that with little difference in calorie levels, fast eaters had a 4.4 times higher risk of gaining weight than those who ate at a normal pace, and men who ate fast were more affected than women.</p><p><strong>Eat two meals a day</strong></p><p>The result of long-term two meals a day is very likely: the weight loss effect is obvious at the beginning, and it will soon enter the plateau period; because this process does not make people lose too much fat, resulting in a lower metabolic rate, eat a little more, Or just resume three meals a day, and you will gain weight and gain weight.</p><p><strong>sleep on weekends</strong></p><p>A study by American scientists shows that sleeping on weekends can make you fat, damage your health, and even worse than lack of sleep.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203124.gif"></p><p>People who don’t get enough sleep on weekdays and catch up on weekends typically eat more snacks than those who don’t get enough sleep regularly, which not only makes people fat but also increases the risk of diabetes, the researchers said.</p><p><strong>Too much dust in the house</strong></p><p>A study in Environmental Science and Technology found that unclean and dusty homes can make people fat. Duke University researchers collected dust samples from 11 residences.</p><p>It was found that the dust in 9 of them stimulated cell division and produced a large number of fat cells; in 7 of them, the fat cells were transformed into mature fat cells and new fat cells were generated, and the transformation was irreversible.</p><p><strong>Often eat at these 4 locations</strong></p><p>An article published in the American “Healthy Living” magazine said that where you eat can also affect your weight, and eating in 4 places may make you fat.</p><p>In the kitchen: When you walk into the kitchen, you will be “surrounded” by food, and you will end up eating more than you expected. Especially eating standing in front of the refrigerator or cupboard, or eating right out of the bag, can make it difficult to remember how much you ate.</p><p>At your desk: Eating fast while working can make your brain “forget” what you’ve eaten, so you end up feeling hungry and eating more.</p><p>In the car: When eating while driving, to avoid holding the steering wheel with one hand for a long time, I often gobble and eat faster and more.</p><p>In front of the TV: On a hungry night, the food advertisements on TV can arouse the appetite even more.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203125.gif"></p><p><strong>Watching the screen for too long</strong></p><p>There is an important association between screen time and early childhood obesity. The study found that children aged 9 to 10 years old had an extra hour of screen time a day, and their body mass index (BMI) increased significantly a year later.</p><p><strong>less social</strong></p><p>Using data from the National Longitudinal Study on Aging, a research team from the University of British Columbia in Canada analyzed the social status of 28,000 adults aged 45 to 85 and how these social relationships affect waist circumference, body mass index, and the incidence of obesity. It turns out that women who lack social interaction are more likely to be obese.</p><p><strong>sleep with the lights on</strong></p><p>Exposure to artificial light while sleeping can cause weight gain in women, according to research in JAMA Internal Medicine. The results of the study showed that during a mean follow-up period of 5.7 years, women who slept with any light exposure at night had a 19% higher risk of obesity than those who had no light exposure.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203126.gif"></p><p><strong>Weight loss starts with lifestyle habits</strong></p><p>Nowadays, many people are excessively pursuing “thinness” and look at their bodies with harsh eyes. Many people do not need to lose weight.</p><p><strong>How can I tell if I need to lose weight?</strong></p><p>Body mass index (BMI): a body type judgment index commonly used in the medical community. Body mass index &#x3D; weight (kg) divided by height (m) squared, this value is between 18.5 and 23.9, which is normal. If it is higher than 23.9, you need to lose weight; if it is lower than 18.5, it is weight loss, and nutrition should be strengthened.</p><p>Body mass index does not reflect the fat distribution. Some people have a normal body mass index, but they accumulate a lot of abdominal fat and are at high risk of developing chronic diseases. Therefore, the body mass index should be combined with the waist circumference to determine whether to lose fat.</p><p>Waist circumference: It can reflect both the total amount of fat and the distribution of fat, and it is a good index for assessing the risk of chronic diseases. Waist circumference should be less than 85 cm for adult men and less than 80 cm for women.</p><p>Waist-to-hip ratio: The ratio of waist circumference to hip circumference is less than 0.9 for men and less than 0.8 for women.</p><p>Subcutaneous fat thickness: The subcutaneous fat thickness of the abdominal wall should be less than 15 mm for men and not more than 20 mm for women. This usually requires a professional sebum thickness gauge to measure.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203127.gif"></p><p>Losing weight can’t just be about speed, good living habits can help you lose weight healthily:</p><p><strong>have a good breakfast</strong></p><p>“Good” means fullness, that is, eating very satisfied, and at the same time ensuring adequate intake of calories and nutrients. Specifically, breakfast calories and nutrient intake should preferably account for 40% of the total daily intake, and at least 30%.</p><p>A healthy and qualified breakfast should include at least three types of food: cereals, such as oatmeal, bread, etc.; animal foods, such as meat, eggs, dairy products, etc.; and vegetables and fruits rich in vitamin C and supplementary dietary fiber ; If you eat more nuts such as pine nuts and almonds, it will be better.</p><p>As long as the collocation is reasonable, the protein is sufficient, the vitamin and mineral content is rich, and the amount of dinner is reduced accordingly, it is no problem to eat enough.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203128.gif"></p><p><strong>light diet</strong></p><p>Appropriately reduce sodium intake when losing weight, and avoid pickled foods. The total intake of salt throughout the day is less than or equal to 5 grams.</p><p><strong>Active drinking</strong></p><p>Drink more boiled water, less or no beverages, etc.</p><p><strong>Insist on moderate exercise</strong></p><p>Those who want to lose weight healthily should participate in more outdoor activities, and should accumulate more than 30 to 60 minutes of activity every day. Prepare for activities before exercising, take protective measures and bask in the sun as appropriate.</p><p>Note that the amount of exercise at the beginning should be less, let the body adapt slowly, and then increase the amount of exercise appropriately. If there is discomfort during the exercise, or if you feel exhausted, you must stop exercising in time.</p><p><strong>Don’t lose weight too fast</strong></p><p>It is generally safe to lose 0.5 kg per week, and it is easy to accept and stick to it. If you lose weight too quickly, it may cause problems such as weakness, hair loss, depression, and arrhythmia.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203129.gif">)</p><p>In addition, due to the rapid decomposition of fat, it will lead to an increase in ketone bodies, the metabolites of fat decomposition in the blood, causing acidosis and serious consequences.</p><p>A moderate diet and moderate exercise are the healthiest ways to lose weight. If there are no special circumstances or diseases, the use of drugs, surgery, and other methods is not recommended.</p>]]></content>
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Exercise during this time of night can help you sleep</title>
    <link href="/Exercise-during-this-time-of-night-can-help-you-sleep/"/>
    <url>/Exercise-during-this-time-of-night-can-help-you-sleep/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Nowadays, many people have a heart that wants to exercise, but helplessly, it is difficult to spare a complete period of time to exercise from morning to night. Some people worry that exercising at night is too exciting to fall asleep, and there are even claims that exercising at night is equivalent to chronic suicide…</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203111.gif"></p><p>However, according to a study published in the Swiss scientific journal “Sports Medicine”, exercising at night not only does not impair sleep quality, but it also increases the duration of deep sleep.</p><p>A study published in the top scientific journal “Sports Medicine” in Switzerland showed that moderate exercise at night basically does not hurt sleep, and it also has a certain effect on improving sleep.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203112.webp"></p><p>The researchers analyzed 11,717 papers and finally screened out 23 really valuable papers, and conducted a meta-analysis of their data to conclude that moderate exercise, such as endurance running or cycling before bedtime, did not negatively affect sleep. , but will increase the time of deep sleep.</p><p>The researchers found that among those who exercised for several nights, 21.2 percent of their sleep time was in deep sleep; if one night without exercising, deep sleep dropped to 19.9 percent.</p><p><strong>What is the best time to exercise at night?</strong></p><p>An experiment conducted by Charles Stewart University in Australia found that exercising for 30 minutes in the evening not only did not affect sleep, but also reduced hunger.</p><p>The researchers tested 11 participants three times, testing their sleep and appetite status after exercise in the morning (6-7 pm), afternoon (2-4 pm), and evening (7-9 pm).</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203113.webp"></p><p>The researchers found that exercising at 7-9 p.m. not only had no adverse effect on sleep, but also had lower blood ghrelin concentrations. The study also emphasized that short-term single exercise may not be associated with reduced hunger, but exercise at 7-9 p.m. did not impair sleep quality.</p><p><strong>Exercise can counteract the damage of poor sleep</strong></p><p>Not only does exercise improve sleep quality, but it also reduces the negative effects of poor sleep on your body.</p><p>A study published in the British Journal of Sports Medicine suggests that weekly physical activity at or above the recommended amount may offset the serious health risks of poor sleep quality.</p><p>The findings showed that those who slept the worst and exercised the least had the greatest risk of dying from heart disease, stroke, and cancer. The researchers, therefore, believe that there may be some connection between the two activities.</p><p>To delve deeper into the question, the researchers extracted health information from volunteers participating in the UK Biobank study. Using the data, they looked at participants’ normal weekly physical activity levels.</p><p>The WHO exercise guidelines suggest that the optimal amount of physical activity per week is 150 minutes of moderate-intensity activity, or more than 75 minutes of vigorous-intensity physical activity. Participants were divided into three groups according to the intensity of physical activity: high-intensity group, moderate-intensity group, and low-intensity group; then the researchers evaluated their sleep quality according to sleep type, sleep duration, insomnia, snoring, and daytime sleepiness. to evaluate.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203114.gif"></p><p>After 11 years of follow-up monitoring, it was found that people who did not have moderate or more physical activity and did not sleep well had a 57% higher risk of all-cause death than those who were more physically active and had higher sleep scores. And these people also have a much higher risk of dying from various cardiovascular diseases, cancer, and lung cancer. Happily, for those with low sleep scores but high physical activity scores, this risk all but disappeared.</p><p>The researchers concluded: “Physical activity levels at or above the WHO-recommended amount of physical activity may undo the harm caused by poor sleep quality.”</p><p><strong>Five sports squares are suitable for different groups of people</strong></p><p>Long-term adherence to moderate exercise has many benefits such as weight control, improved sleep, improved physical function, and longevity.</p><p><strong>strength training: weight control</strong></p><p>When it comes to losing weight, many people think that just doing more exercise is enough, but that’s not the case. Scientific weight loss, although exercise is the first choice, but the key depends on how to move. Gou Bo said that strength training is the best way to lose weight.</p><p>Strength training can build muscle, muscle development, and basal metabolic rate.</p><p>Basal metabolic rate refers to the number of calories that a person needs to consume the minimum calories needed to maintain life when a person is stationary. If a person’s basal metabolic rate is 1000 kcal, then even if he does not move all day , will consume 1000 kcal. Weightlifting, barbell lifting, etc. are relatively simple strength training.</p><p>The American Heart Association recommends that healthy adults do 30 to 45 minutes of strength training at least twice a week.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203115.gif"></p><p>Strength training can also be paired with some foods, which not only provide the necessary nutrients during exercise and help the body recover but also reduce the risk of muscle cramps. Gou Bo suggested that it is a good choice to eat some almonds, bananas, whole-wheat bread, yogurt, apples, and other foods before exercise.</p><p>Reminder: strength training should also have a degree, the elderly and minors are not suitable for strength training with a large amount of exercise.</p><p><strong>Competitive Sports: Sleep Well</strong></p><p>Sleep is a protective mechanism for the cerebral cortex cells, that is, when the nerves are “tired”, they need a transformational rest. The key to “stimulating” neural transformation is movement.</p><p>Appropriate exercise can make people sleep better, especially competitive exercise, which can make people feel fatigued and can make nerve excitation and inhibition processes alternate, thus helping sleep.</p><p>Young and middle-aged people can choose football, basketball, volleyball, and other competitive ball games that consume a lot of physical strength;</p><p>Middle-aged and elderly people can walk, do yoga, etc.;</p><p>Children can participate in more sports such as swimming and mountain climbing.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203116.gif"></p><p>Reminder: exercise intensity should be well controlled. People with good physical strength can do about 2 hours of exercise every day; people with average physical strength can arrange 45 minutes.</p><p><strong>Fragmentation exercise: strengthen the heart and brain</strong></p><p>Many people are busy with work and have no time to exercise, and most of these jobs are inseparable from “sedentary”. The World Health Organization’s Behavioural Risk Factor Study shows that prolonged sitting is one of the leading causes of death and disability.</p><p>Gou Bo suggested that you might as well make good use of the rest time after work. Try 5-7 minutes of fragmented exercise every day, which will make the body regain its “vigor”. Such as push-ups, squats, high leg raises, front lunges, etc. are all good choices. Do 1-2 sets of 20-30 times each time.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203117.gif"></p><p>These fragmented movements can not only speed up blood circulation, improve cardiopulmonary function, but also stimulate the brain, which will be more efficient when it is put back into work.</p><p>Reminder: Those who are doing these exercises for the first time and middle-aged and elderly people can do it gradually.</p><p><strong>Cardio: Brighten the mood</strong></p><p>A study by Florida State University and the University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign shows that aerobic exercise can improve people’s mood, help relieve mental stress, and thus maintain health.</p><p>Restless walking: Strenuous exercise can easily cause injury, which can be relieved by walking. The scenery along the way and the chirping of cicadas on the trees will make people feel comfortable and help release bad emotions.</p><p>Depressed mood can swim: in the water, there will be a feeling of soothing, relaxation and freedom, and the depressed mood will “go away”.</p><p>Too much pressure to do yoga: the coordination between the stretching of the body and the breathing can fully stretch and relax the body and mind.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203118.gif"></p><p><strong>Skilled Movements: Improve Flexibility</strong></p><p>Statistics show that falls have become the number one “killer” of disability for the elderly. To prevent falls, the ability to react, balance, and coordinate are very important. Lu Yifan believes that some technical exercises can not only achieve the purpose of improving physical fitness but also improve the sense of balance, reaction level and coordination, to keep the elderly away from falling.</p><p><strong>small ball exercise reaction</strong></p><p>Responsiveness is the brain’s response to external stimuli and the body’s response to brain commands. The small ball movement is relatively weak, but the rhythm is fast, requiring a high degree of consistency between the hand and the brain, and frequent participation can improve the reaction speed. Badminton and table tennis are good choices.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203119.gif"></p><p><strong>Dance balance and coordination</strong></p><p>The hands and feet “swing” together with the rhythm of the music, is a comprehensive “interpretation” of balance and coordination. In addition, standing on one leg every day can also achieve the same effect: when doing this action, there must be support around, in case the standing is unstable, you can help it to avoid falling.</p><p>You can also practice the transfer of the center of gravity, first transfer the center of gravity to the left, restore the upright after a while, and then transfer the center of gravity to the right, which is conducive to gait coordination and balance.</p>]]></content>
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Eating dinner early can help lower blood sugar! Those who eat late, please reflect consciously</title>
    <link href="/Eating-dinner-early-can-help-lower-blood-sugar-Those-who-eat%20late-please-reflect-consciously/"/>
    <url>/Eating-dinner-early-can-help-lower-blood-sugar-Those-who-eat%20late-please-reflect-consciously/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>People with high blood sugar are more prone to obesity, cardiovascular and cerebrovascular diseases, and cancer than normal people.</p><p>Many people work very hard to control staple foods and design recipes, but they are likely to ignore the important accomplice of high blood sugar - eating too late for dinner.</p><p> Recently, a study published in the authoritative medical journal “Diabetes Care” showed that:</p><p>Eating late dinner is a blood sugar disaster; for the average person, it is wise to fast within 4 hours of bedtime.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203101.webp"></p><p><strong>Change your dinner time to lower your blood sugar</strong></p><p>To explore whether refeeding in the presence of elevated endogenous melatonin levels, such as before bedtime, could lead to disturbances in blood sugar control, researchers from the United States and Spain set up the study.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203102.webp"></p><p>A total of 845 Spanish adults aged 18-70 were included in the study, divided into two mealtimes:</p><p>Early dinner group - eat dinner 4 hours before regular bedtime;</p><p>Late dinner group - Eat dinner 1 hour before your regular bedtime.</p><p>All subjects were randomly assigned to one group and then switched to another group to repeat the test on another night.</p><p>In the end, the research team found that late dinner led to a 6.7% decrease in insulin AUC and an 8.3% increase in glucose AUC.</p><p>Simply put, the later dinner time is, the lower the insulin level and the higher the blood sugar level.</p><p>The researchers say the association is plausible because insulin works by lowering blood sugar levels.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203103.gif"></p><p>“Our findings may be important for strategies to prevent type 2 diabetes,” said Dr. Frank A.J.L. Scheer, director of the biology program at Brigham and Women’s Hospital.</p><p>He further added: “The findings apply to people who eat close to bedtime, others who eat at night (including those with jet lag and eating disorders), and people who use melatonin supplements heavily.”</p><p>For most people, it’s wise to fast for at least four hours before bed, the researchers said. That is, if you fall asleep at 23:00, it is best to have dinner around 7:00 pm.</p><p><strong>Two keys to blood sugar around dinner</strong></p><p>More and more studies have shown that eating the wrong dinner not only affects blood sugar but also increases the risk of obesity, heart disease, indigestion, and other diseases.</p><p>How to eat dinner is more friendly to blood sugar, intestines, etc.? Here are two key figures summarised:</p><p><strong>Dinner time: preferably no later than 8:00</strong></p><p>Combining with modern people’s work and rest habits, 5-7 pm is the best time for dinner. Overeating or eating too late is not good for digestion and blood sugar.</p><p>It is best to eat before 7 pm, but no later than 8 pm.</p><p>If you don’t have time, don’t eat dinner too close to bedtime, and, at the same time, eat less often the later you eat.</p><p><strong>Fasting time: 3-4 hours before bedtime</strong></p><p>The time from dinner to sleep is preferably no less than 3 hours, to allow enough time for the stomach to absorb, but no more than 8 o’clock at the latest.</p><p>If you sleep late at night and feel hungry, you can drink a cup of soy milk or milk between 9 and 10 o’clock, and if it is not enough, you can add some fruit. These foods are more satiety, easy to digest, and have less impact on sleep and blood sugar.</p><p><em><strong>10 Diet Tips for Sugar Control</strong></em></p><p>Sugar control depends largely on diet, including eating time, diet structure, and amount of food.</p><p><strong>Have breakfast before 8:30</strong></p><p>People who eat before 8:30 a.m. have lower blood sugar levels and insulin resistance, which can help reduce the risk of type 2 diabetes, according to a report presented at the 2021 American Society of Endocrinology Annual Meeting.</p><p><strong>Adjust the breakfast structure</strong></p><p>Breakfast must have more than 2 kinds of meat, eggs, milk, beans, nuts, vegetables, and fruits.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203104.webp"></p><p><strong>change the order of meals</strong></p><p>When eating, some people come up to eat steamed bread and rice first, and then eat vegetables. As a result, they eat more of the staple food and less of the vegetables.</p><p>For most people, the eating order of “fiber→protein&#x2F;fat→carbohydrate” is more blood sugar friendly.</p><p><strong>The same kind of food, choose coarsely processed</strong></p><p>The finer the food, the softer it is cooked, the faster the sugar rises; and those foods that are not soft enough and need to be chewed carefully will help stabilize blood sugar after a meal.</p><p><strong>Choose simple cooking methods</strong></p><p>The glycemic index (GI) of a food refers to the relative speed at which carbohydrates in a certain food enter the human body within 2 hours under a standard quantitative (usually 50 grams), causing blood sugar to rise.</p><p>The simpler the cooking method, the slower the sugar rise. For example, the GI of instant oatmeal is 83, while the GI of oatmeal that traditionally needs to be cooked by itself is only 59.</p><p><strong>slow down eating</strong></p><p>Eating too fast will make people unconsciously eat more than usual, which is not conducive to the control of total calories; in addition, the rapid entry of food into the gastrointestinal tract is not conducive to full absorption, but also causes a rapid rise in blood sugar.</p><p>The slower you eat, the easier it is to feel full, and the slower your sugar rises. Breakfast should be no less than 15 minutes, and lunch and dinner can be controlled within half an hour.</p><p><strong>“Neutralizes” the glycemic index by combining</strong></p><p>For example, the GI of rice is 83, the GI of fried pork with celery is ≤15, and the fried pork with rice + celery becomes a low glycemic index (49.9). Click to view the glycemic index (GI) of common foods</p><p><strong>eat small meals often</strong></p><p>Eating small and frequent meals can not only avoid high blood sugar caused by eating too much at each meal, but also avoid preprandial hypoglycemia caused by too long intervals between meals.</p><p>Diabetic patients must eat three meals a day. The ideal is to add a little meal in the morning and afternoon. Of course, the calories should be removed from the main meal.</p><p><strong>Add coarse grains to staple food</strong></p><p>The greater the total carbohydrate, the greater the glycemic potential. Try not to eat too many sweets and staple foods.</p><p>For diabetics and overweight people, the amount of staple food can be appropriately reduced to 30% to 50% of the total food, of which coarse grains account for half of the staple food. The reduced main consumption of vegetables, meat, eggs, milk, and nuts is replaced.</p><p><strong>Cook as much as possible at home</strong></p><p>Eating out dishes are often high in oil, sugar, and salt, which is not conducive to keeping blood sugar stable.</p><p>If you must go out to eat, you can eat more vegetables, especially green vegetables, and high-fat, high-calorie dishes such as braised pork, braised prawns, and lion head are fine.</p><p>For various staple foods, such as various puff pastries, be careful not to be greedy. When ordering soup, do not choose a thick soup with a lot of starch, so as not to increase the intake of sugar.</p>]]></content>
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Anxious people are at higher risk of dementia</title>
    <link href="/Anxious-people-are-at-higher-risk-of-dementi/"/>
    <url>/Anxious-people-are-at-higher-risk-of-dementi/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Assessing a person’s health, people may pay more attention to physical performance, while ignoring emotional and psychological aspects.</p><p>Compared with the pain of physical illness, mental trauma is like a chronic poison, which will eat away the health of the whole person step by step.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203091.webp"></p><p>A 30-year study by an international research team led by Duke University in the United States found that people with early mental disorders (anxiety, depression, schizophrenia, personality disorders, etc.) higher risk of developing dementia. Focusing on mental health at a young age may reduce or delay the burden of dementia later in life.</p><p>The research was recently published in JAMA Psychiatry, the top journal in the field of psychiatry.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203092.webp"></p><p><strong>Anxiety, depression increase the risk of dementia</strong></p><p>The researchers investigated a 30-year follow-up study (1988-2018) involving 1,711,386 New Zealanders aged 21 to 60 at baseline, 50.6% male.</p><p>During the follow-up period, 64,857 people were identified as having a mental disorder and 34,029 people were identified as having dementia. Similar proportions of men and women are diagnosed with a mental disorder, but more are younger.</p><p>Dementia was diagnosed in 3957 (6.1%) of those diagnosed with a mental disorder during the observation period; only 1.8% of those without a mental disorder. Dementia rates are high among men, women, and people with mental disorders of all ages.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203093.webp"></p><p>The link between mental health problems and dementia was observed in both men and women with both early-onset and late-onset dementia. Thus, mental disorders are significant early warning signs of subsequent dementia.</p><p>The lead author of the study said that mental health issues are not the “final verdict” of dementia, and that mental health needs to be taken care of as well as physical health to reduce the risk of developing the disease later on.</p><p><strong>How Negative Emotions Affect the Body</strong></p><p>If mental disorders such as anxiety and depression have affected daily life, you need to seek medical attention in time and follow the doctor’s advice.</p><p>Poor mood and mental health are one of the reasons for mental disorders. In psychology, anxiety, tension, anger, depression, sadness, pain, and other emotions are collectively referred to as negative emotions.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203094.webp"></p><p>Clinically, many digestive system diseases, skin diseases, endocrine diseases, etc. are closely related to emotions and psychology.</p><p><strong>stomach</strong></p><p>The gastrointestinal tract is called the “second brain”, and its functional state is influenced to some extent by emotions. Long-term negative emotions can easily lead to gastrointestinal dysfunction, leading to indigestion, constipation, diarrhea, gastritis, intestinal inflammation, and unexplained abdominal pain.</p><p><strong>cardiovascular</strong></p><p>Excited emotions such as anxiety and anger can damage blood vessels and lead to cardiovascular diseases such as hypertension and coronary heart disease.</p><p>The risk of acute myocardial infarction within 2 hours increased by 2.44 times when people were extremely angry; even mild depression, anxiety, or stress doubled the risk of heart disease.</p><p><strong>skin</strong></p><p>Skin diseases such as urticaria, psoriasis, eczema, and itchy skin are closely related to their etiology and pathogenesis.</p><p><strong>Endocrine System</strong></p><p>People who are stressed and anxious for a long time are prone to thyroid disease; women who are prone to anxiety and anger are more likely to have endocrine disorders, and even increase the risk of breast cancer and ovarian cancer.</p><p>The following 3 types of people are more susceptible to negative emotions and need to pay attention to mental health issues.</p><p><strong>◎ Adolescents</strong>: With the rapid development of body, self-awareness, and personality, adolescents are prone to problems in interpersonal relationships, emotional stability, and learning adaptation. Teens with psychological problems transition into adulthood with higher rates of crime and antisocial personality disorder.</p><p><strong>◎ Women</strong>: Women are more delicate in their minds, their frequency of emotional rumination is higher than that of men, and they have more troubles, especially women who are emotional, over-accommodating, worrying, and over-dependent, and are more prone to depression, neurasthenia, anxiety disorders, and other problems.</p><p><strong>◎ The elderly:</strong> organ aging, functional decline, and various diseases appear one after another, which makes the elderly prone to mental and psychological disorders. The most common is depression in old age, in addition to dementia, post-traumatic stress disorder in old age, sleep disorders, etc.</p><p><strong>6 Ways to Make Peace with Bad Emotions</strong></p><p>Everyone will inevitably encounter negative emotions. Learning how to accept and deal with these problems is the most important thing. The following 6 methods may help you.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203095.webp"></p><p><strong>Try box breathing</strong></p><p>“Box Breathing” allows us to quickly activate the parasympathetic nerves to achieve a calming, relaxing effect, helping to instantly soothe our emotions.</p><p>How to do it: Inhale through your nose for 4 seconds, hold your breath for 4 seconds, then exhale through your mouth for 4 seconds, hold for 4 seconds. Repeat 4-5 cycles or more until you feel calm.</p><p><strong>Avoid “future anxiety”</strong></p><p>Many people’s anxiety comes from “future-oriented” emotions, repeating “bad things that may happen in the future” in their minds and mistakenly taking it as reality.</p><p>Try to describe the anxious thought: “I have a thought… (the content of the thought), but it’s just a thought, it doesn’t necessarily happen.” You will realize that it is the “imagination” in your mind that is making you anxious, not the the inevitable reality.</p><p><strong>Recognize and accept bad emotions</strong></p><p>Trying to suppress and deny emotions can make it even harder for us. At this point, try to accept your emotions and admit that “this thing really bothers me.” Avoid emotional rumination afterward, and don’t repeatedly recall scenes or experiences that make you sad.</p><p>In addition, you can also talk to relatives and friends about the difficulties you have encountered. Talking is a good way to relieve bad emotions.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203096.gif"></p><p><strong>Don’t “self-concept”</strong></p><p>Many people subconsciously label themselves: “I’m a girl so I can’t”, “I’m a mentally ill person”, “I’m an unwanted person” and so on.</p><p>No matter what happens to you, it is only a state at a certain moment or period, a small part of yourself, and accepting that people are constantly changing can reduce anxiety or depression.</p><p><strong>Find meaning for your “suffering”</strong></p><p>Do not deny the negative side of suffering, and do not deny and suppress your own feelings.</p><p>Strive to accept the fact that the “negative event has happened”, stop trying to change it, and after adjusting yourself, try to study this unique experience to see if you can learn from it and make us live better in the future .</p><p><strong>try sports or other hobbies</strong></p><p>It’s a good idea to get moving when you’re in a bad mood, and exercise can release dopamine that makes you feel happy. Aerobic exercise has great antidepressant and anxiety effects, as well as great benefits for stress relief. Besides exercising, try doing something you enjoy.</p><p>In addition, a hot bath is also a good idea. Within the normal range, people with higher body temperature are more likely to feel pleasant.</p>]]></content>
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>In the matter of sleep aid, aerobic exercise actually lost</title>
    <link href="/In-the%20matter-of-sleep-aid-aerobic-exercise-actually-lost/"/>
    <url>/In-the%20matter-of-sleep-aid-aerobic-exercise-actually-lost/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Recently, a large-scale study presented at the American Heart Association’s 2022 Annual Meeting on Epidemiology, Prevention, Lifestyle, and Cardiometabolic Health found:</p><p>Resistance exercise is more effective than aerobic exercise in improving sleep quality.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203081.webp"></p><p>The study recruited 386 sedentary overweight or obese people, all of whom were randomized into four groups:</p><p>One group did not exercise at all (control group), and the other three groups were aerobic exercise group, resistance exercise group, and aerobic + resistance exercise group.</p><p>Each participant in the exercise group was required to participate in 60 minutes of training three times a week, of which the “aerobic + resistance exercise group” performed 30 minutes of aerobic exercise + 30 minutes of resistance each time sports. The trial lasted a total of 12 months.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203082.webp"></p><p><strong>Resistance exercise is good for sleep aid</strong></p><p>At the beginning of the study and after 12 months, the researchers conducted a variety of assessments, including measures of sleep efficiency, sleep duration, sleep latency, and sleep-disrupting factors such as snoring, coughing, waking up at night, and the presence or absence of pain. Wait).</p><p>After taking into account several factors, the researchers found: At the end of the study, sleep duration increased in all three exercise groups, with an average increase of 40 minutes in the resistance exercise group; and an increase in the aerobic exercise group. About 23 minutes; the aerobic + resistance exercise group added about 17 minutes.</p><p>In terms of sleep efficiency and sleep latency, participants in the resistance exercise group were also in the lead:</p><p>The sleep efficiency of the resistance exercise group and the aerobic + resistance exercise group increased, but the aerobic exercise group and the control group did not improve;</p><p>Only the resistance exercise group decreased the sleep latency by 3 minutes, and there was no significant change in other participating groups;</p><p>Sleep quality and sleep disturbance improved in all groups, including the inactive group.</p><p>Research suggests that both aerobic and resistance exercise can help improve health, but when it comes to getting better sleep, resistance may be better.</p><p>People with frequent insomnia or poor sleep quality may wish to consider adding two or more resistance exercises to their exercise routine.</p><p><strong>4 principles of resistance exercise</strong></p><p>Resistance training, also known as strength training, refers to the exercise of a certain part of the body against resistance. Generally, muscle strength is improved through multiple, multiple sets of rhythmic weight-bearing.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203083.webp"></p><p>There are certain skills in resistance training, and the daily exercise should follow the following principles:</p><p><strong>2-3 times a week</strong></p><p>Resistance training is generally performed 2-3 times a week, with an interval of no less than 48 hours between each time, to avoid fatigue and injury caused by insufficient recovery. The weight of the equipment should be stopped after 8 to 12 repetitions of the action.</p><p>Sometimes there will be a feeling of soreness after exercise, which can be relieved within two or three days. This is a normal phenomenon. If you cannot distinguish pain and soreness by yourself, you can ask a professional such as a doctor to determine whether you can continue exercising.</p><p><strong>Balanced exercise, targeted</strong></p><p>A complete training should have 8-10 different movements, involving the main muscle groups of the human body and covering different parts.</p><p>You can’t just train your legs or just your arms, you have to train each part in place, and then start the next part, you can’t “grab your eyebrows and beards”.</p><p><strong>Action to be standardized</strong></p><p>No matter which forms, the action specification is the most important. On this basis, you can gradually increase the number of times and weight, and finally, try to increase the speed. Don’t put the cart before the horse.</p><p>Pain is an important warning sign. If you experience pain during training, it may be a strain or sprain caused by incorrect posture. Stop exercising and seek medical attention in time.</p><p><strong>Work the big muscles first, then the small ones</strong></p><p>Large muscle group training refers to movements that involve more than two joints, such as the bench press; small muscle group training refers to movements that engage less than two joints, such as forearm curls with dumbbells.</p><p>Many elderly people think that square dancing is a sufficient exercise every day. Square dancing is just an “activity”, which is less effective for muscle training. Dancing in one night may not be comparable to doing 20 single-leg squats.</p><p>If the elderly want to gain muscle, they can do some simple bodyweight training or light equipment training at home, such as push-ups, squats, dumbbells, etc.</p><p><strong>Resistance training you can do at home</strong></p><p>Many people don’t have a lot of time to go to the health room. They can practice with the help of the body’s weight, or tools such as elastic bands. For the main muscle groups of the body, bodyweight training has its most suitable movements.</p><p><strong>resistance band</strong></p><p>The elastic band is easy to use, easy to carry, and suitable for building the endurance of large muscle groups.</p><p>Exercise the gluteus maximus, standing or leaning over, fix one end of the rope in a lower position, and fix the other end on one foot with an ankle strap, exhale to lift the leg back and up, hold for 1 to 2 seconds , inhale to restore, and switch legs.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203084.gif"></p><p>To practice the pectoralis major, wrap the elastic band behind the shoulder blades and hold it with both hands to do push-ups.</p><p>Each muscle completes the action 12-20 times&#x2F;group, 2-3 groups&#x2F;time, 2-3 times a week.</p><p><strong>plank</strong></p><p>Plank support is a static exercise, which can exercise the muscles of the abdomen and buttocks of the body to some extent.</p><p>Lie on your stomach, with your elbows shoulder-width apart, your elbows supported on the ground, and your upper arms and torso should be kept at 90 degrees as much as possible. Put your toes together to reduce the support area. Straighten the neck naturally, look forward and downward with the eyes, keep the chest straight, keep the head, shoulders, hips, and lower limbs on the same plane, and tighten the abdominal muscles and pelvic floor muscles.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203085.gif"></p><p>Breathe naturally, do not hold your breath, and do not drop your hips or lean to your sides.</p><p><strong>hip bridge</strong></p><p>This move primarily works the glutes, but also works the core, hamstrings, quads, and hip flexors.</p><p>Lie on your back with your knees bent at a right angle; pedal hard on the ground with your heels, contract your hamstrings and glutes hard, and lift your hips off the ground as high as possible.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203086.gif"></p><p>At the top of the movement, hold this position for 3 seconds, then lower your body back to the starting position. 10 times for 1 set, do 3 sets each time.</p><p><strong>squat</strong></p><p>Squats work the muscles of the thighs and buttocks.</p><p>Keep your head up high and your feet shoulder-width apart. With your feet parallel, keep your knees in the same direction as your toes when you squat.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203087.gif"></p><p>Squat down slowly until the angle between the thigh and the calf is less than 90 degrees, but not close, about 70 to 80 degrees, and then stand up with the thighs forward until you stand straight.</p><p><strong>push-ups</strong></p><p>Push-ups are a training method that mainly exercises the upper limbs, waist, and abdominal muscles. When doing push-ups, keep your hands naturally shoulder-width apart and keep your abs tight at all times.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203088.gif"></p><p>Before doing push-ups, you need to do a detail of adducting the elbows; at the highest point, bending the elbows properly can keep the shoulder joints retracted well, and the purpose is to better exercise and stimulate the chest muscles.</p>]]></content>
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>It&#39;s true that if you&#39;re in a bad mood, you will become &quot;ugly&quot;! 7 Skin Conditions Affected by Emotions</title>
    <link href="/Its-true-that-if-youre-in-a-bad-mood-you-will-become-ugly-7-Skin-Conditions-Affected-by-Emotions/"/>
    <url>/Its-true-that-if-youre-in-a-bad-mood-you-will-become-ugly-7-Skin-Conditions-Affected-by-Emotions/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>You may have discovered that when you are in a bad mood, your complexion will become dark yellow and rough, and your whole person’s state is not right.</p><p>A large number of scientific studies have found that 70% of people will digest bad emotions in a way that damages their physical health, and “skin” is an outlet for emotions such as anger, fear, and sadness.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203071.webp"></p><p>A good mood will make the skin radiant, and a bad mood will reduce the appearance of the skin by affecting the skin.</p><p><strong>Skin condition is linked to mood</strong></p><p>Human emotional behavior and hormone secretion are governed by the hypothalamus. The hypothalamus communicates with the cerebral cortex and the pituitary gland and other nervous tissues. It is the center that regulates nerves, humor, and the endocrine.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203072.gif"></p><p>When people are happy, the secretion of the neuroregulatory substance acetylcholine in the brain increases, the blood is smooth, the subcutaneous blood vessels dilate, and the blood flow to the skin. Look radiant, radiant, and full of energy.</p><p>If you are depressed and anxious for a long time, excessive melanin synthesis by epithelial cells will be deposited on the skin surface, making the skin dull and dull, and even the formation of chloasma.</p><p>Depressed mood can also lead to neurasthenia, insomnia, affecting the blood supply of the skin, making the face haggard and dark circles under the eyes.</p><p>Skin allergies are also affected by mood changes. When the mood changes suddenly, the nerve endings will release a large amount of acetylcholine, and acetylcholine can directly act on the blood vessels of the skin, causing vasodilation, prompting the release of histamine, and then causing allergic reactions.</p><p><strong>7 skin diseases implicated in bad moods</strong></p><p>Long-term mental stress often makes it difficult to breathe, and 7 skin diseases are particularly susceptible to bad moods.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203073.gif"></p><p><strong>Acne</strong></p><p>Mental stress will promote the secretion of adrenal cortex hormones and male hormones, induce acne, and also increase the secretion of neuropeptides at the site of skin lesions, aggravating the inflammatory response.</p><p><strong>Alopecia areata</strong></p><p>People who are anxious, impatient or pessimistic, and emotionally sensitive area prone to alopecia areata. The psychological state of the patients with alopecia areata is the basis of the disease. With the improvement of the state of mind, the symptoms of most patients will also improve.</p><p><strong>Atopic dermatitis (eczema)</strong></p><p>Studies have shown that nearly 67% of patients have more stressful life events before and during the disease. Stress, insomnia, fatigue, mood changes, and other factors can induce or aggravate eczema.</p><p>In addition to following doctor’s orders, patients should also pay attention to their mental health and avoid excessive stress.</p><p><strong>Neurodermatitis</strong></p><p>Neurodermatitis, also known as lichen simplex chronicus, is a lichen-like degeneration of the skin caused by repeated scratching, accompanied by severe or paroxysmal itching.</p><p>In addition to medication, patients may consider psychiatric or behavioral therapy to interrupt the vicious cycle of “itch-scratch-itch”.</p><p><strong>Psoriasis</strong></p><p>Psoriasis, commonly known as psoriasis, is a chronic, recurrent, inflammatory, systemic disease. It is also a typical physical and mental skin disease, and mental stress is one of the factors that trigger and aggravate the disease.</p><p>Although psoriasis cannot be cured, it can be alleviated, controlled, or even stopped by standard treatment. During the treatment, the patient should maintain a good mood and receive psychotherapy if necessary.</p><p><strong>Vitiligo</strong></p><p>Vitiligo is a localized or generalized depigmented spot caused by the destruction of melanocytes or a disorder of melanin synthesis.</p><p>Several clinical observations have found that psychological stress such as stress, anxiety, and depression are closely related to vitiligo. Anxiety and depression can aggravate the disease, and if the disease persists, it will in turn increase the negative emotions of patients.</p><p><strong>Systemic lupus erythematosus</strong></p><p>Systemic lupus erythematosus is an autoimmune disease that invades multiple systems. In mild cases, it only affects the skin, and in severe cases, it affects multiple organs and is even life-threatening.</p><p>Emotional stimulation is one of the predisposing factors for lupus erythematosus. Clinical findings showed that most patients had significant depression in childhood, or had an obvious interpersonal crisis before the onset.</p><p><em><strong>Prevention advise from a dermatologist</strong></em></p><p>Long-term mental stress will cause problems in sweat gland secretion, skin microvascular relaxation, and hair nutrition. To avoid the impact of skin diseases, it is necessary to resolve negative emotions in time in life, and dermatologists give preventive advice on this.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203074.gif"></p><p><strong>Improve unhealthy living habits</strong></p><p>In life, pay attention to a balanced diet, regular work and rest, ensure adequate sleep, and avoid staying up late for a long time, overwork, etc.</p><p><strong>Increase outdoor sports</strong></p><p>Go outdoors often, breathe fresh air, enhance physical fitness, pay attention to psychological adjustment, and resolve negative emotions in time.</p><p><strong>Pay attention to indoor hygiene</strong></p><p>During the virus epidemic season, it is also necessary to pay attention to frequent indoor ventilation to promote air circulation, frequent cleaning of the environment, and frequent drying of clothes and bedding.</p><p><strong>Virus rash patients pay attention to isolation and disinfection</strong></p><p>Patients with viral rash at home (mainly manifested by rash and fever all over the body) should be isolated in time, take antiviral drugs reasonably, and disinfect the items and rooms they use.</p><p>Experts remind that in addition to physical pain, many patients feel inferior because of their appearance damage or strange vision, and fall into a vicious circle of mutual influence between a bad mood and skin disease.</p><p>After skin problems, everyone must go to a regular hospital for treatment as soon as possible.</p>]]></content>
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Men in this age group should control their weight the most</title>
    <link href="/Men-in-this-age-group-should-control-their-weight-the-most/"/>
    <url>/Men-in-this-age-group-should-control-their-weight-the-most/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Some people’s obsession with the figure is that if they weigh more than 100, they are fat; some people are fearless and let themselves become “balloons”.</p><p>According to the World Health Organization, at least two out of every five adults in the world are overweight or obese.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203061.gif"></p><p><strong>Men in this age group are the fattest</strong></p><p>In 2021, a research team led by the Chinese Center for Disease Control and Prevention will publish data on BMI and obesity in urban and rural areas in China from 2004 to 2018 in The Lancet.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203062.webp"></p><p>Data for this study were derived from six nationally representative health surveys completed by the China Chronic Disease and Risk Factor Surveillance Project between 2004 and 2018. A total of 645,223 people aged 18-69 were included in this analysis. The results show that:</p><p>Chinese people are getting fatter</p><p>The normalized mean BMI of Chinese adults increased from 22.7 kg&#x2F;m² in 2004 to 24.4 kg&#x2F;m² in 2018, mainly driven by weight gain rather than height change.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203063.gif"></p><p><strong>Where does fat grow most harmful to the body?</strong></p><p>When the human body stores subcutaneous fat, it also stores visceral fat.</p><p>A certain amount of visceral fat is necessary for the human body to support, stabilize and protect the internal organs.</p><p>However, when there is excess nutrition in the body, fat will continue to accumulate in the internal organs, which will lead to cardiovascular and cerebrovascular diseases such as hyperlipidemia, hypertension, diabetes, arteriosclerosis, heart disease, and metabolic syndrome.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203064.gif"></p><p>Visceral fat mainly exists in the abdominal cavity, such as the liver, pancreas, stomach, intestines, and other organs around and inside, and its obvious manifestation is abdominal obesity.</p><p><strong>Is your visceral fat excess?</strong></p><p>The easiest way to determine whether your visceral fat exceeds the standard is to calculate the ratio of waist circumference to hip circumference.</p><p>Test 1: Use a tape measure to measure the waist-to-hip ratio (waist-to-hip ratio &#x3D; waist circumference ÷ hip circumference).</p><p>Method: Stand upright, inhale gently, and measure the waist circumference above the navel and the most protruding hip circumference with a tape measure.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203065.webp"></p><p>If the waist-to-hip ratio is greater than 0.9 for men and greater than 0.8 for women, it indicates a high-risk group with excess visceral fat, and the second step test needs to be performed immediately.</p><p>Test 2: Test the subcutaneous fat on the waist and abdomen.</p><p>Method: Try pinching around the belly button. If you can easily pinch up 2 cm, it means that the accumulation of subcutaneous fat;</p><p><strong>How to lose weight if you are already fat?</strong></p><p>Regarding weight loss, the World Health Organization’s recommendation is to lose 0.5 to 1 kilogram per week and 1 to 3 kilograms per month. This “uniform” weight-loss method has little damage to the body and is not easy to rebound.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203066.gif"></p><p>Weight loss is about fat loss, and fat is also a whole body. It can only be reduced in proportion to the whole body. Partial fat loss is unscientific. Only a combination of diet, aerobic, and strength training will slowly lose weight throughout the body. The specific methods are as follows:</p><ol><li><strong>Eat less high-sugar and high-fat foods</strong></li></ol><p>In terms of diet, control the intake of carbohydrates and fats, and eat less polished rice, noodles, and sweets.</p><p>Low-quality carbohydrates (that is, foods with a high glycemic index) may be less healthy than most dietary fats.</p><p>The most conducive to weight control staple food: oats, brown rice, quinoa, buckwheat, etc. These whole grains have a strong sense of satiety and are cooked with rice in a 1:3 ratio, which is great for weight control.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203067.gif"></p><p>Eat more fiber, eat more whole grains, vegetables, fruits, beans, etc., and increase high-quality protein, such as fish, chicken, eggs, milk, and soy products.</p><ol start="2"><li><strong>Eat three meals regularly</strong></li></ol><p>People who often skip dinner will lead to weight gain.</p><p>The reason is that fasting at night may lead to retaliatory eating at breakfast and lunch the next day, and the intake of calories exceeds the standard, which is not conducive to weight control. So if you want to lose weight, eating regularly is the key.</p><ol start="3"><li><strong>Do more aerobic exercise</strong></li></ol><p>People with a good physique can do moderate-intensity exercises, such as brisk walking, jogging, cycling, and Tai Chi. Fitness experts can participate in sports such as running, fast mountain climbing, stair climbing, and tennis.</p><p>The best exercise intensity is more than 60% of your maximum heart rate (maximum heart rate is 220 minus your age). The exercise time for each exercise should be at least 20 minutes, and 40 to 60 minutes is recommended.</p><ol start="4"><li><strong>High-intensity interval training</strong></li></ol><p>High-intensity interval training is a combination of high-intensity exercise, low-intensity relaxation, and rest. For example, use a faster pace or climb for 3 minutes, then walk slowly on flat terrain for 2 minutes, repeating 6 times in 30 minutes.</p><p>In this way, the stimulation to the body is small, so that the human body is in a more stable and comfortable exercise state, thereby increasing the speed of fat burning.</p><ol start="5"><li><strong>Guaranteed 7-9 hours of sleep</strong></li></ol><p>People who slept 7 to 9 hours per night had a 28% to 35% lower risk of abdominal obesity than those who slept less than 5 hours per night.</p><p>The last thing to note is: weight loss needs to be gradual. If you lose weight too quickly, it may cause problems such as weakness, hair loss, depression, and arrhythmia.</p>]]></content>
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>How can short videos be addictive? Scientists &#39;scan&#39; the brain and found...</title>
    <link href="/How-can-short-videos-be-addictive-Scientists-scan-the-brain-and-found/"/>
    <url>/How-can-short-videos-be-addictive-Scientists-scan-the-brain-and-found/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>If you ask what is the favorite pastime of contemporary people, it is estimated that many people will say: watching videos. On the way to work, while eating, lying in bed before going to bed… Short videos are more and more deeply involved in our lives.</p><p>How much time do you spend watching short videos every day?</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203051.gif"></p><p>What is your brain doing when you watch short videos?</p><p>People who often watch short videos will have a feeling that after watching one video one by one, inertia will gradually form, and if you want to keep scrolling down, you can’t stop at all.</p><p>Have you ever wondered what happened to our brain at this time?</p><p>NeuroImage published a study from Zhejiang University in China that used a functional MRI to reveal the brain while watching short videos.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203052.webp"></p><p>The researchers invited subjects to watch normally recommended videos for new users and personalized recommended videos for old users and found that some components of the brain’s default mode network were more active when watching personalized recommended videos, specifically including bilateral Superior and middle temporal gyrus, temporal pole, ventral posterior cingulate cortex, medial prefrontal cortex, and angular gyrus.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203053.webp"></p><p>In addition, the ventral tegmental area of the midbrain and other discrete brain areas such as the lateral prefrontal lobe, the anterior thalamus, and the cerebellum, which are related to the reward system, also showed higher activation states. And the coupling of regions of the brain’s default mode network to visual and auditory pathways has also been enhanced, which may lead to greater video addiction by up-regulating attention and higher-level perception.</p><p>The default mode network is mainly composed of the medial prefrontal cortex, the posterior cingulate cortex, and the angular gyrus, and is a large neural network spanning the entire brain.</p><p>Decreased activity in the default mode network is the brain’s most visible signal when it comes to paying attention.</p><p>The default mode network becomes very active when people have nothing to do and think about.</p><p><strong>Which nerve does the short video tease?</strong></p><p>Adam Alter, Ph.D. of Psychology at Princeton University, in his book “Can’t Stop: How to Get Rid of Behavioral Addiction in the Age of Swiping” lists six elements of behavioral addiction: tempting goals, irresistible and unpredictable positive feedback, A sense of incremental improvement, increasingly difficult tasks, unresolved tensions that need to be resolved, strong social connections.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203054.gif"></p><p><strong>Irresistible and unpredictable positive feedback</strong></p><p>When you open the short video software, there is almost no operation required, and the software will scroll to show you interesting and interesting short videos of more than ten seconds.</p><p>The background of the short video software can analyze everyone’s preferences based on big data, and make targeted pushes, so that people can’t help but wonder what the next one will be after watching one.</p><p>These surprises and surprises will prompt the brain to continuously secrete the “happy hormone” dopamine, which makes people feel joy and can’t help repeating a behavior.</p><p><strong>Unresolved tension that needs to be resolved</strong></p><p>Most of the short videos are only 15 seconds long and are accompanied by a climax of the music, which means that each short video must quickly show the main point of the story of the development, and it is incomplete, giving a feeling of unfinished business.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203055.gif"></p><p>It is this kind of expectation of “unfinished” and “is there still” that will provoke the nerves of users, making people want to watch more and longer.</p><p><strong>Have immediate goals</strong></p><p>Short videos are mostly short, light-hearted, and can be watched quickly without much effort, which is very attractive in itself, and for people who take a long time in real life to feel that “one thing is done” is attractive. especially powerful.</p><p><strong>Create difficult tasks</strong></p><p>The short video software will also release some new, difficult, and interesting tasks from time to time for everyone to challenge.</p><p><strong>Strong social connections</strong></p><p>Many times we can see similar experiences to ourselves in videos and comment areas, hear the words that come into our hearts, and find things that we can empathize with… These are very important to loneliness, incomprehension, self-doubt, or being malicious and attacked. It’s a very safe “habitat” for people who are not alone, and it makes people feel like they’re not alone.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203056.gif"></p><p><strong>How to watch short videos in moderation</strong></p><p>Nothing is absolutely good or bad, and the same is true for short videos:</p><p>A short video is a tool that allows people to contact more new things in a short period, and the transmission of any information in life needs this kind of short and smooth way.</p><p>For example, an advertisement introducing a product, an advanced technology that needs to be promoted and popularized to everyone, teaching everyone a small life skill in a short way, or leading everyone to appreciate the beauty of a tourist destination, etc.</p><p>On the one hand, a short video liberates the viewer’s nature and relieves pressure; on the other hand, it adds happiness and fun and makes life no longer dull.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203057.gif"></p><p>Modern people are busy with work, and free time has become very precious, and short video is a very typical pastime and information sharing using fragmented time.</p><p>This kind of dissemination seems to improve efficiency, but in fact, the information obtained in a short period is not systematic, and because the video is short, it does not require people to concentrate for a long time, making it difficult for people to form effective memory.</p><p>Once we get used to this way of getting information, the attention span becomes shorter and shorter.</p><p>A short video is just a tool and platform. We can become its masters to improve ourselves and enrich our lives, instead of being led by tools.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203058.gif"></p><p>When watching short videos, it is recommended to do:</p><p><strong>Control time</strong></p><p>Watching for a few hours is not only a waste of time, but also affects your eyesight. You must also pay attention to your priorities in life, and don’t miss the important things in reality by watching short videos.</p><p><strong>Classified treatment</strong></p><p>For some practical information that can increase your knowledge or make use of it, you can refer to it, but choose to ignore some vulgar and sensational content to avoid adverse effects.</p><p>For people who are not so addicted and just regret spending a lot of time watching videos, improving self-control is the key. Scheduling a regular viewing time, setting a good time, asking a friend to supervise interruptions, and putting your phone away before bed can all help to “break the brakes.”</p>]]></content>
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Mild fatty liver also increases the risk of death, and doing these 3 points can reverse</title>
    <link href="/Mild-fatty-liver-also-increases-the-risk-of-death-and-doing-these-3-points-can-reverse/"/>
    <url>/Mild-fatty-liver-also-increases-the-risk-of-death-and-doing-these-3-points-can-reverse/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>When you see the medical report showing fatty liver, what is your first reaction? Mild fatty liver is “not a problem” in the eyes of many people.</p><p>Most patients with fatty liver have no obvious symptoms in the early stage. When symptoms such as pain and nausea appear, fatty liver is already more serious.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203041.gif"></p><p><strong>Does mild fatty liver matter?</strong></p><p>Fatty liver is not an independent disease, it often indicates the existence of other metabolic abnormalities in the body, and it is likely to be complicated by metabolic-related diseases.</p><p>In 2020, the internationally renowned medical journal “GUT” published a study from Sweden online. The study found that even mild fatty liver disease (simple fatty liver) was associated with a 71% increased risk of death.</p><p>Researchers from Massachusetts General Hospital and Karolinska Institutet in Sweden studied the pathological data of 10,568 patients with fatty liver during 51 years from 1966 to 2017 and found that:</p><p>Compared with the control group, the risk of all-cause mortality increased by 71%, 114%, 144%, and 279% in patients with simple steatosis (ie, mild fatty liver), non-fibrotic steatohepatitis, liver fibrosis, and liver cirrhosis, respectively.</p><p>Fatty liver is a component of metabolic syndrome. It is associated with type 2 diabetes, cardiovascular disease, chronic kidney disease, and certain extrahepatic malignancies. Cardiovascular disease, extrahepatic cancer, and related complications were the main causes of death in patients.</p><p><strong>Type 2 diabetes</strong></p><p>After the formation of fatty liver, the ability of the liver to process blood sugar is significantly reduced, so it cannot keep blood sugar stable, which promotes the occurrence and development of diabetes.</p><p><strong>Cardiovascular diseases</strong></p><p>There are too many vicious lipids in the blood, which accumulate on the blood vessel wall and cause systemic blood vessel damage.</p><p>If it is attached to the blood vessels of the heart, a little blockage will cause coronary heart disease; if it is attached to the cerebral blood vessels, it will cause stroke and other cerebrovascular diseases in severe cases.</p><p><strong>Chronic kidney disease</strong></p><p>Fatty liver can cause blood sugar, blood pressure, blood lipids to rise, and high blood pressure, high blood sugar, etc. can cause glomerulosclerosis, and then develop into nephritis, weakening renal function, and serious renal failure.</p><p><strong>Extrahepatic cancer</strong></p><p>When the liver accumulates a lot of fat, chronic inflammation occurs, the bile excreted is abnormal, and the intestinal flora is disturbed. Over time, the immune function of the body will decline, and cancer cells are more likely to proliferate in the body, leading to the occurrence of non-liver cancers such as colorectal cancer and breast cancer.</p><p><strong>I’m obviously not fat, so why do I have fatty liver?</strong></p><p>In the impression of many people, those with fatty livers are usually fat people.</p><p>Excessive nutrition will indeed cause excessive accumulation of fat in the body, and a large amount of fat accumulates in the liver, resulting in fatty liver. But the fatty liver is not all caused by obesity, there are the following major causes:</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203042.webp"></p><ol><li><strong>Malnutrition</strong></li></ol><p>When insufficient food intake, digestive disorders, etc. cause malnutrition, there is not enough apolipoprotein in the body to transport triglycerides, and a lanumberount of triglycerides are deposited in the liver, resulting in fatty liver.</p><p>Studies have shown that, compared with obese people, lean people with fatty liver have more serious liver damage once they have liver diseases such as hepatitis.</p><ol start="2"><li><strong>Lose weight too fast</strong></li></ol><p>Excessive dieting, vegetarianism, crazy exercise, or other measures to lose weight quickly often lead to a stronger desire to eat, easily induce overeating after dieting, and accelerate the development of fatty liver.</p><p>Today, the incidence of fatty liver in young women is increasing rapidly, most of which are related to excessive weight loss.</p><ol start="3"><li><strong>Malnutrition</strong></li></ol><p>People who drink for a long time are prone to develop alcoholic fatty liver disease, and their livers have fatty infiltration. According to statistical analysis, people who drink more than 80 to 160 grams per day have a 5 to 25-fold increase in the incidence of alcoholic fatty liver disease.</p><p>If you are a person who has been drinking for a long time, is obese, or has hepatitis B, after the diagnosis of fatty liver, it is necessary to further check related indicators such as inflammation, and regularly monitor the liver condition.</p><ol start="4"><li><strong>Diabetes</strong></li></ol><p>As a metabolic syndrome, it causes abnormal metabolism of carbohydrates, proteins, and fats in the body, about 50% of diabetic patients may suffer from fatty liver.</p><ol start="5"><li><strong>Drug abuse</strong></li></ol><p>Drugs entering the body need to be detoxified by the liver. Some drugs or chemical poisons such as tetracycline, lipid-lowering drugs, health products, arsenic, lead, silver, mercury, etc. will damage the liver and interfere with lipoprotein metabolism. Long-term abuse will increase the risk of drug-induced fatty liver. probability.</p><p><em><strong>To reverse do the following:</strong></em></p><p>Generally speaking, fatty liver is a reversible disease, and early diagnosis and timely treatment can return to normal.</p><p>Being overweight and obese due to a poor lifestyle are major risk factors for fatty liver. To prevent and improve fatty liver, you must start with diet, weight, and exercise:</p><p><strong>No.1 Balanced diet</strong></p><p>Make sure to eat three meals a day. Avoid high-fat, high-cholesterol, high-calorie diets. Reduce the intake of carbohydrates and sweets such as sugar, honey, jam, etc. Eat less animal offal, fried or fried food, quit smoking and drinking.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203043.gif"></p><p>Properly increase protein intake, prefer lean meat, fish, eggs, and other foods rich in high-quality protein. Get enough vitamins, minerals, and dietary fiber, and eat plenty of fresh vegetables, fruits, and algae.</p><p><strong>No.2 Weight Control</strong></p><p>The primary goal of treatment for fatty liver disease is weight loss. A 52-week study in the journal Gastroenterology showed:</p><p>58% of patients with fatty liver had their symptoms reduced if they lost more than 5% of their body weight;</p><p>If the body weight is reduced by more than 10%, the fatty liver remission rate reaches 90%, and the fibrosis reversal rate reaches 45%.</p><p>It is recommended that patients with fatty liver lose 0.5 to 1 kg of weight per week, and lose more than 5% of their body weight within one year until they reach a healthy weight.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203044.gif"></p><p><strong>No.3 Exercise 3 hours a week</strong></p><p>A Stanford University study found that 3 hours of recreational exercise per week significantly reduced the risk of non-alcoholic fatty liver disease, liver fibrosis, and cirrhosis.</p><p>The researchers’ segmented analysis of participants’ exercise time found:</p><p>Exercise 150-299 minutes or more than 300 minutes per week can reduce the incidence of NAFLD by 40% and 49%, respectively.</p><p>At least 300 minutes of physical activity per week was associated with a 59% and 63% reduction in the risk of liver fibrosis and cirrhosis, respectively.</p><p>Try to choose an exercise method that you like and can persist for a long time, such as swimming, jogging, brisk walking. You can also take a walk after dinner and exercise outdoors on weekends.</p>]]></content>
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Banana is the most radioactive fruit, why do I recommend you to eat more?</title>
    <link href="/Banana-is-the-most-radioactive-fruit-why-do-I-recommend-you-to-eat-more/"/>
    <url>/Banana-is-the-most-radioactive-fruit-why-do-I-recommend-you-to-eat-more/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Banana, sweet and soft, is a fruit suitable for all ages. After eating bananas for so many years, did you know that they actually have radiation?</p><p>German physicist Derek Muller once experimented on how much radiation is around us. Experiments found that eating a banana will receive 0.1μSv of radiation.</p><p>Since bananas have radiation, can we still eat them with confidence? You can’t just eat it, I also advise you to eat more.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203035.gif"></p><p><strong>Eating bananas, will radiation accumulate in the body?</strong></p><p>The radiation of bananas is related to the element potassium. The potassium content of bananas is abundant in the fruit, and the content of potassium-40 is relatively high. Therefore, bananas have also become the most radiant variety of fruits.</p><p>As the most radioactive food in the fruit world, the radiation dose of bananas is actually very small. Eating 80,000 bananas is equivalent to taking a chest CT.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203031.webp"></p><p>An hour near the Chernobyl nuclear power plant is equivalent to eating 50 bananas</p><p>After we eat a banana, the potassium content in the body will increase by 0.4%, but this is only temporary. Our metabolism controls the amount of potassium in the body, and excess potassium is excreted by the kidneys.</p><p>That is, the radiation produced by bananas does not accumulate in the body.</p><p><em><strong>8 hidden benefits of bananas</strong></em></p><p>Bananas are a good source of vitamins and minerals. The data shows that every 100 grams of bananas contain 60 micrograms of carotene, as well as B vitamins such as thiamine, riboflavin, and niacin, as well as vitamin C.</p><p>Along with being delicious, bananas have many health benefits:</p><ol><li><strong>Protect blood vessels</strong></li></ol><p>Bananas are rich in potassium (256 mg of potassium per 100 grams, 0.8 mg of sodium), which can inhibit the rise of blood pressure and damage to blood vessels caused by sodium. Therefore, people with high blood pressure and heart disease should eat bananas.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203032.gif"></p><ol start="2"><li><strong>Get rid of fatigue</strong></li></ol><p>Bananas are high-potassium foods and rich in magnesium. Modern medicine has confirmed that potassium can maintain normal blood pressure and heartbeat, prevent blood pressure from rising and muscle spasms, while magnesium has the effect of eliminating fatigue.</p><p>In addition, the sugar in bananas can be quickly converted into glucose, which is immediately absorbed by the body and is a fast source of energy, so eating a banana after exhaustion can replenish physical strength.</p><ol start="3"><li><strong>Improve brain power</strong></li></ol><p>A British study of 200 students found that eating bananas and other fruits high in potassium can help improve students’ concentration, learning efficiency, and performance.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203033.gif"></p><ol start="4"><li><strong>Improve skin</strong></li></ol><p>For people with bad skin, it is recommended to eat bananas with yellowed skin. Bananas of this color are ripe and contain more vitamin B2 and vitamin B6, which have a better effect on preventing and treating skin problems.</p><ol start="5"><li><strong>Suppress gastric ulcer</strong></li></ol><p>Bananas have a soft texture and help relieve gastrointestinal disturbances. Bananas can also neutralize excess stomach acid and protect the gastric mucosa.</p><p>Ripe bananas often have black spots or brownish skin on the skin. Studies have shown that this brown-skinned banana contains phospholipids, which are rare in fruits, and has the effect of inhibiting gastric ulcers.</p><ol start="6"><li><strong>Reduce eye disease</strong></li></ol><p>Bananas are rich in carotenoids, which can be converted into vitamin A by the human liver, which is especially beneficial for eye health.</p><p>A study published in the American Journal of Agricultural and Food Chemistry found that eating a banana a day can improve eye health, reduce eye diseases, and reduce the risk of blindness.</p><ol start="7"><li><strong>Good for bone growth</strong></li></ol><p>Calcium, phosphorus, and magnesium in bananas are beneficial to bone growth, and also contain essential trace elements such as zinc, selenium, and copper.</p><ol start="8"><li><strong>Regulate emotions</strong></li></ol><p>The tryptophan contained in bananas can be converted into serotonin, which is an inhibitory neurotransmitter that promotes peace of mind, reduces pessimism and depression, and even reduces pain.</p><p>Bananas are delicious and nutritious, but they are not suitable for everyone.</p><p>The potassium content in bananas is high, and people with acute and chronic nephritis and renal insufficiency should not eat more. The glycemic index of bananas is 52, which is a low-glycemic index food, so diabetics can eat bananas in small amounts, but pay attention to reducing the intake of staple foods.</p><p>In this way, the bananas are not easy to grow spots and turn black</p><p>What causes banana skins to turn black is a gas called ethylene. As bananas ripen, more and more ethylene is released. So, by controlling the ethylene around the banana, you can control how quickly it ripens. Specifically, you can do this:</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203034.gif"></p><p><strong>Wrap banana rhizomes</strong></p><p>Most of the ethylene gas comes from the rhizomes of bananas, and wrapping the rhizomes of bananas can slow down the ripening process of bananas and prolong the preservation time.</p><p>If you want to keep bananas fresh for a week, take the whole banana apart and wrap the roots of each banana tightly with plastic wrap.</p><p><strong>Store at room temperature 13°C</strong></p><p>Experiments show that 13°C is the best storage temperature for bananas. At this temperature, bananas will ripen more slowly.</p><p><strong>Hang up bananas</strong></p><p>Hanging bananas with good ventilation allows the ethylene produced to travel with the wind, thereby slowing the aging of the bananas. In some supermarkets, you can see racks dedicated to hanging bananas. </p>]]></content>
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>This intestinal bacteria is on the &quot;carcinogenic&quot; blacklist! People with frequent diarrhea should be careful</title>
    <link href="/This-intestinal-bacteria-is-on-the-carcinogenic-blacklist-People-with-frequent-diarrhea-should-be-careful/"/>
    <url>/This-intestinal-bacteria-is-on-the-carcinogenic-blacklist-People-with-frequent-diarrhea-should-be-careful/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Intestinal flora is the general term for the microbiota that resides in the human gut, which is related to the immune system, endocrine system, and other metabolic pathways of the human body.</p><p>If the balance of flora is destroyed, the health status of the human body will also change, and constipation, diarrhea, enteritis, etc. may occur, which may even affect life expectancy.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203021.gif"></p><p><strong>This gut bacteria is on the ‘carcinogenic’ blacklist</strong></p><p>In a recent study published in the prestigious journal Cancer Discovery, researchers used enteropathogenic Escherichia coli and enterohemorrhagic Escherichia coli to assess the ability of adherent pathogens to induce bowel cancer.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203022.webp"></p><p>They found that adherent pathogens in the gut can connect to intestinal epithelial cells through their type 3 secretion system (T3SS) and inject genotoxins to damage the DNA in the host intestinal epithelial cells, leading to cell carcinogenesis and colon cancer.</p><p>In 2020, the international authoritative journal “Nature” published an important study on colorectal cancer, and scientists put forward evidence that infection with specific intestinal bacteria can cause cancer mutations.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203023.webp"></p><p>Escherichia coli are mainly epiphytes in the intestines of humans or animals, and most of them will not cause harm to the body, but can inhibit the reproduction of intestinal pathogens and other pathogens.</p><p>Some pathogenic Escherichia coli can cause diarrhea, hemorrhagic colitis, and other symptoms; and diarrhea, alternating constipation, defecation habits and changes in stool characteristics are important indicators for early detection of colorectal cancer</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203024.gif"></p><p>Therefore, when diarrhea occurs, don’t attribute it to excessive consumption of cold drinks, food deterioration, and other reasons. If you generalize, some diseases will become “fish that slip through the net”.</p><p><strong>For the following 5 kinds of diarrhea, it is recommended to seek medical attention</strong></p><ol><li><p>Acute diarrhea, accompanied by frequent vomiting, fever, severe abdominal pain, or accompanied by dizziness, palpitation, dry mouth, oliguria, and other symptoms of dehydration.</p></li><li><p>Acute diarrhea, no relief within 48 hours.</p></li><li><p>Diarrhea with bloody mucus or melena.</p></li><li><p>Patients with chronic diarrhea, but also with a history of colorectal polyps or cholecystectomy, or a family history of colorectal cancer need to be vigilant.</p></li><li><p>Patients with long-term constipation in the past have recently had changes in bowel habits or traits, and diarrhea.</p></li></ol><p><strong>5 types of Escherichia coli can cause disease</strong></p><p>Coliform is an indicator of food hygiene, including Escherichia coli, Citrobacter, Klebsiella aerogenes, and Clorox. Coliforms detected in food do not necessarily cause harm. However, the presence of pathogenic E. coli bacteria in the coliform flora can lead to foodborne illness.</p><p>There were three outbreaks of Escherichia coli in the United States in 1991, 1993, and 1996.</p><p>In 2014, there were more than 400 patients in the E. coli poisoning incident in Japan.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203025.gif"></p><p><strong>Pathogenic Escherichia coli are generally divided into 5 categories</strong></p><p>Enteropathogenic Escherichia coli: Water or egg drop soup in infants and young children.</p><p>Enterotoxigenic Escherichia coli: Most of them have no obvious abdominal pain, and discharge watery stools more than ten times a day.</p><p>Enteroinvasive Escherichia coli: Fever, abdominal pain, diarrhea, mucus, and blood in the stool.</p><p>Enterohemorrhagic Escherichia coli: early watery stools, later bloody stools.</p><p>Enteroaggregative Escherichia coli: associated with intractable diarrhea in children.</p><p>Children, the elderly, pregnant women, and those with weakened immunity are at high risk of pathogenic E. coli infection. Although most patients can recover in a short time, the harm of some pathogenic Escherichia coli should not be underestimated.</p><p>For example, the main pathogenic strain O157:H7 in Enterohemorrhagic Escherichia coli has strong acid resistance and can resist the digestive effect of gastric acid, and it is easy for people to be poisoned when eaten.</p><p>It not only produces Shiga toxin (causing dysentery symptoms), but also attaches to the intestinal wall, causing damage to the intestinal mucosa, causing bloody diarrhea and hemolysis characterized by acute renal failure, hemolytic anemia, and thrombocytopenia Sexual uremia.</p><p><em><strong>5 points to prevent pathogenic bacteria</strong></em></p><p>Escherichia coli poisoning is a typical “disease from the mouth”. Following the five key points of food safety recommended by the World Health Organization can effectively prevent foodborne diseases such as Escherichia coli food poisoning.</p><ol><li><strong>Keep your hands clean</strong></li></ol><p>Wash hands frequently, keep kitchen utensils clean; keep animals away from food.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203026.gif"></p><ol start="2"><li><strong>Raw and cooked food separation</strong></li></ol><p>Raw and cooked food are separated, and special kitchen utensils are used for handling raw food.</p><ol start="3"><li><strong>Fully cooked food</strong></li></ol><p>The meat, poultry, and seafood are thoroughly cooked, and the soup is boiled; cooked food should be thoroughly reheated.</p><ol start="4"><li><strong>Keep food at a safe temperature</strong></li></ol><p>Cooked and perishable foods are cooled promptly; refrigerators do not store foods for long; frozen foods are not thawed at room temperature.</p><ol start="5"><li><strong>Use safe water and raw materials</strong></li></ol><p>Choose a reputable business place to buy food; wash fruits and vegetables; do not eat spoiled food.</p>]]></content>
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>The most &quot;powerful&quot; muscle in the cheek, everyone should practice</title>
    <link href="/The-most-powerful-muscle-in-the-cheek-everyone-should-practice/"/>
    <url>/The-most-powerful-muscle-in-the-cheek-everyone-should-practice/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>As we age, many people find their faces become larger and more square.</p><p>This phenomenon is a plus when it happens to cats, but if it happens to people…</p><p>In fact, it has something to do with a muscle in the cheek.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203011.webp"></p><p><strong>Masseter muscle, the most powerful masticatory muscle in the human body</strong></p><p>When we say that people “Chubby Cheeks”, we often mean that the sides of the chin have become fatter, or the chin itself has changed. One of the common types is the masseter-type Chubby Cheeks.</p><p> <img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203012.webp"></p><p>The masseter muscle is the most powerful masticatory muscle in the human body and is the main performer of the bite action. Under the innervation of the trigeminal nerve, when the masseter muscle contracts, the mandible is pulled upward, and the upper and lower teeth are clenched to crush hard food.</p><p>The muscle fibers of the masseter muscle are relatively thick and have a certain facial support function. The appearance of the middle and lower part of the face will be affected by it.</p><p>Many people feel that their faces have become larger, squared, and “Chubby Cheeks”, and it may be that their masseter muscles have become “stronger”.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203013.gif"></p><p>The largest of the muscle groups attached to the jawbone is the masseter muscle, also known as the masseter muscle.</p><p>The mandible is the bone that supports the jaw. It connects with the temporal bones on both sides to form the temporomandibular joint, where our teeth grow.</p><p>If you want to judge whether your masseter muscles have become “strong”, you can test yourself according to the following methods:</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203014.gif"></p><p>If you’re not gaining weight and you can feel a raised, tight muscle when you bite your back teeth, you’re more likely to have a masseter hypertrophy.</p><p><strong>Masseter muscles are strong, people can live longer</strong></p><p>The masseter muscle is one of the most critical muscles in the human body, and regular exercise can help delay aging and prolong life.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203015.gif"></p><p>Recently, in a study published in the “Annals of Anatomy”, researchers at the University of Basel in Switzerland found that there is a third layer of muscle tissue in the masseter muscle, known as the “masseter coronoid muscle”.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203016.webp"></p><p>This new layer of muscle may help stabilize the jaw by elevating and contracting the coronoid process, the only part of the masseter muscle that pulls the jaw back and is essential for chewing.</p><p>The masseter muscle is key to longevity, stronger masseter muscle, younger brain. Some people can bite hard fruits when they are young, but as they get older, they can’t even eat some glutenous things, which also affects their nutritional intake and mood.</p><p>In 2017, a study in the American Journal of Geriatrics pointed out that the strength of chewing can also predict the risk of Alzheimer’s disease. The stronger the brain, the younger the brain, and the lower the risk.</p><p><strong>Bad habits can “injure” the masseter muscles</strong></p><p>The so-called “use it and lose it”, many wrong usages will lead to “injury” of the masseter muscle.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/2203017.gif"></p><p><strong>Bad chewing habits</strong></p><p>People who usually like to bite hard objects, chew for a long time, and have a lot of times will have a stronger masseter muscle, which will lead to a wider jaw. In severe cases, it can cause dysfunction of the jaw joint.</p><p>Unilateral chewing will make the burden on one side heavier, while the masseter muscle on the other side cannot be functionally stimulated, and unilateral masseter muscle hypertrophy may occur, and the corresponding joints will be heavily stressed and damaged.</p><p><strong>Nerve problems</strong></p><p>Trigeminal nerve problems, trauma, mental stress, cold stimulation, night grinding, etc. may damage the masseter muscle, resulting in masseter muscle disorders, such as fascia pain, muscle spasm, etc.</p><p><strong>Aging</strong></p><p>People’s masseter muscle thickness increases by around 2mm during puberty and stops growing naturally after age 20 (women) and 22 (men).</p><p>With age, collagen is lost, muscle elastic fibers are aged and broken, the strength and support of masseter muscles will be relatively weakened, and facial relaxation or sagging may occur, and chewing ability will decrease.</p><p><strong>Masseter weakness</strong></p><p>When the masseter muscle is weak, it can be manifested as being tired from chewing, not chewing, and unable to eat hard food, etc., and the risk of malnutrition, aspiration, difficulty swallowing, and slurred speech is greatly increased.</p><p><em><strong>3 ways to train chewing power</strong></em></p><p>The strength of the masseter muscle is often referred to as masticatory power, and masticatory power weakens with age. Experts recommend the following three ways to exercise the masseter muscle.</p><p><strong>Bulging cheeks</strong></p><p>To train chewing force, you can use the method of “Bulging cheeks”, that is, let the cheeks move back and forth like a mouthwash, and do it 30 times quickly, which can stimulate the muscles of the cheeks and increase the chewing force.</p><p><strong>Pull battle</strong></p><p>Use your big molars to bite one end of tough food such as gummy candy and shredded squid, and gently pull the other end with your hand to feel the force of the masseter muscle.</p><p><strong>Practice knocking teeth</strong></p><p>When tapping the teeth, tap lightly first, the upper and lower teeth collide gently, and the speed is slightly faster; then bite and tap, the upper and lower teeth are like biting something, but the speed is slightly slower, and do it three or four times a day.</p><p><em><strong>What should I do if I don’t want the masseter muscle to become “strong”?</strong></em></p><p>For the sake of beauty, some people hope to reduce the masseter muscle to achieve the purpose of a thin face. Some opt for medical treatment, such as surgery to remove part of the muscle fibers or a “face-lift” (local injection of botulinum toxin).</p><p>Reminder: If you choose to inject face-lifting needles in irregular institutions, it is likely to cause the facial expression to be stiff after surgery, so that the masseter muscle loses part of its normal function and affects chewing function.</p><p>It can be achieved through some daily habits: reducing chewing, not eating too much hard food (nuts), etc. After a long time, the masseter muscle will naturally atrophy.</p>]]></content>
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>The more you lick your lips, the drier your lips become! Dermatologist&#39;s Essentials for Lip Moisture</title>
    <link href="/The-more-you-lick-your-lips-the-drier-your-lips-become-Dermatologists-Essentials-for-Lip-Moisture/"/>
    <url>/The-more-you-lick-your-lips-the-drier-your-lips-become-Dermatologists-Essentials-for-Lip-Moisture/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>For chapped lips, do not apply lip balm directly</p><p>Compared with other parts of the body, the lips are a thin layer of mucosal tissue, without sweat glands and sebaceous glands, and cannot secrete sweat and oil, so they are easily affected by the external environment.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202281.gif"></p><p>When the weather is dry, the lips are prone to dryness and peeling. When the lips appear erythema, dryness, scaling, chapped, edema, itching, or even burning, they may be suffering from cheilitis.</p><p>At this time, lip balm comes in handy.</p><p><strong>Clean your lips before applying lip balm</strong></p><p>Eat and drink water during the day, even if you apply lip balm, it will fall off, so it is recommended to apply it at night. Apply a lip balm before bed to moisturize overnight until the next morning, and your lips won’t be less prone to dryness.</p><p><strong>If it is dry and cracked, apply water first, then apply lip balm</strong></p><p>When the lips are already chapped, applying lipstick directly may not be effective, it is best to apply it with water first.</p><p>If there is chapped bleeding, it is best to pour cool pure water on a cotton pad and apply it on the lips to effectively stop the bleeding.</p><p>If it is only dry and there is no chapped bleeding, it is recommended to apply a damp and hot towel on the lips, which can effectively soften the lips, allow the lips to fully absorb moisture, and then apply lip balm to lock in the moisture.</p><p><strong>Choose lip balms and avoid those with these ingredients</strong></p><p>To prevent lip problems, avoid licking or biting your lips on weekdays. Although this can temporarily moisten your mouth, it will evaporate the moisture of the lips and aggravate dryness. When molting occurs, do not tear it with your hands, otherwise, it will aggravate the inflammation.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202282.gif"></p><p>When choosing a lip balm, be sure to read the ingredient list carefully. Some products contain chemical ingredients that can irritate the lips; choose a lip balm product with little irritation, good moisturizing effect, and reliable ingredients.</p><p><strong>Salicylic acid, phenol</strong></p><p>Lipsticks that contain exfoliating ingredients such as salicylic acid and phenol should be purchased and used with caution. Salicylic acid works primarily by softening the cuticle, then peeling it off, quickly letting the dead skin on the lips leave.</p><p>The skin on our lips is extraordinarily thin, it is only about one-third as thick as the nearby skin. Regular use of lip balm containing salicylic acid can make lips thinner and more prone to chapped lips.</p><p><strong>Mineral oil, mineral wax, or microcrystalline wax</strong></p><p>These ingredients seal in especially well, like wrapping a layer of plastic wrap around your mouth. When they wrap around your lips, the lips will feel very wet and slack off. Over time, dependence will reduce the moisturizing ability of the lips.</p><p><strong>Camphor or menthol</strong></p><p>These ingredients will cool your mouth. Camphor is toxic to a certain extent and should not be applied to the mouth; while menthol will accelerate the evaporation of water.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202283.gif"></p><p><strong>Recommended ingredients:</strong></p><p>Moisturizing + Repairing Skin Barrier Selection contains these ingredients: Sodium Hyaluronate, Ceramide, Squalane;</p><p>The water lock contains these ingredients: castor oil, jojoba oil, petroleum jelly.</p><p><strong>Recommended ingredients for severely chapped lips:</strong></p><p>The chapped lips are particularly serious and even dry to the point of peeling. The lip balm you choose should preferably contain allantoin, glycyrrhizic acid, vitamin E, and, other special ingredients that can be anti-inflammatory, calm, and repair the lip skin.</p><p><em><strong>3 things every day to keep your lips away from dryness</strong></em></p><p>Loss of water is fast and it is difficult to lock in water. As a “vulnerable group” in the human body, the lips need your careful care.</p><p> <img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202284.gif"></p><p><strong>Strengthen moisturizing</strong></p><p>Drink plenty of water at ordinary times and use a humidifier when necessary to improve the humidity of the environment. The correct choice of lip balm products, pay attention not to use frequently, it is generally recommended to use about 3 times a day.</p><p><strong>Conditioning diet</strong></p><p>Eat more eggs, dried fruits, beans, and fresh vegetables and fruits every day. These foods are rich in vitamin C and vitamin B2, which can nourish the lips.</p><p><strong>Reduce external stimuli</strong></p><p>Try to avoid external stimuli such as wind and sun, and wear a mask when going out to reduce the evaporation of moisture from the lips.</p><p>If the chapped lips are still not relieved after self-care, or even more serious, it is best to go to a regular hospital specialist to avoid delaying the treatment time.</p><p><em><strong>Tip: Lipstick should be applied vertically</strong></em></p><p>This is because the lines on the lips are vertical, but when people apply lipstick, they almost always apply it horizontally, which makes it difficult for the active ingredients to fully penetrate and nourish the lip lines, and even aggravate wrinkles, making it easier to dry and crack.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202285.webp"></p><p>If you already have small cracks under your lip lines, it is easy to tear these small holes again when applying lipstick horizontally.</p><p>Apply lipstick vertically, in line with the law of lip lines, and the moisturizing effect is longer.</p><p>However, be aware that the skin on the lips is very fragile, so apply the lipstick gently to avoid irritation. When the weather is cold, the paste tends to become hard. It is best not to apply it directly, but to apply it with fingers, cotton swabs, or brushes.</p>]]></content>
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>What kind of tea is considered &quot;strong tea&quot;? These 7 types of people should not drink</title>
    <link href="/What-kind-of-tea-is-considered-strong-tea-These-7-types-of-people-should-not-drink/"/>
    <url>/What-kind-of-tea-is-considered-strong-tea-These-7-types-of-people-should-not-drink/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Tea is one of the most popular beverages and drinking tea has been around for thousands of years.</p><p>Some people like to drink strong tea, thinking that strong tea is rich and rich, and the taste is distinct; some people like light tea, thinking that light tea is fresh and elegant, which can not only quench thirst but also maintain health.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202271.webp"></p><p><strong>What is considered “strong tea”?</strong></p><p>The main functional components in tea are tea polyphenols, caffeine, and theanine. Among them, tea polyphenols make tea astringent, caffeine brings a bitter taste to tea, and theanine makes tea taste fresher.</p><p>At present, there is no uniform definition of strong tea. When there are too many tea leaves, the bitterness of the tea soup will increase, the freshness will be relatively weakened, and the color of the tea soup will become stronger, which is often referred to as strong tea.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202272.gif"></p><p>However, the strength of tea is related to personal taste and feeling, and there is no absolute measure.</p><p>Tea addicts who have been drinking tea for many years have become accustomed to the bitter taste of tea, and the strong tea in the eyes of ordinary people may not be strong for them.</p><p>Those who do not drink tea often or who are used to drinking weak tea will not be able to accept it if it is slightly thicker.</p><p>From a health point of view and taste, strong tea is suitable for tea lovers, and tea of suitable strength is suitable for most people.</p><p>If the tea can be brewed according to the best tea-water ratio of each type of tea, the color and aroma of the tea will be maximized.<br>The standard tea dosage for most famous teas (green tea, black tea, yellow tea, scented tea) is 1 gram of dry tea with 50 ml of water, that is, the ratio of tea to water is 1:50;</p><p>The ratio of tea to water for ordinary bulk tea (green tea, black tea, yellow tea, scented tea) is 1:75.</p><p>The amount of black tea, white tea, and oolong tea should be more. The tea-water ratio of dark tea is 1:50<del>1:30, the tea-water ratio of white tea is 1:25</del>1:20, and the tea-water ratio of oolong tea is 1: 15 or so.</p><p><em><strong>The following categories of people should try to avoid drinking strong tea:</strong></em></p><ol><li><strong>Children and adolescents</strong></li></ol><p>The caffeine in strong tea will excite the central nervous system, shorten the child’s deep sleep time, and may affect the child’s growth and development.</p><ol start="2"><li><strong>Women in special times</strong></li></ol><p>For women who are in the menstrual period, pregnancy, or breastfeeding period, drinking a lot of strong tea for a long time will hinder the absorption of iron and cause iron-deficiency anemia. Excessive intake of caffeine also affects the development of fetuses and infants.</p><ol start="3"><li><strong>Those who are sensitive to caffeine</strong></li></ol><p>Such people should not only avoid strong tea, but also avoid tea as much as possible in the afternoon and evening, so as not to affect sleep.</p><ol start="4"><li><strong>People with poor gastrointestinal function</strong></li></ol><p>Some people will feel uncomfortable in the stomach and intestines after drinking tea. The caffeine in tea can stimulate the gastrointestinal mucosa, promote the secretion of gastric acid, and aggravate the gastrointestinal discomfort.</p><ol start="5"><li><strong>Patients with high uric acid or gout</strong></li></ol><p>Caffeine is a diuretic, and moderate drinking of weak tea in patients with high uric acid can help reduce uric acid. However, if you drink strong tea, caffeine will decompose and produce new uric acid after entering the human body, which will aggravate the disease.</p><ol start="6"><li><strong>Drunk</strong></li></ol><p>Drinking strong tea after being drunk will increase the burden on the heart, and tea will accelerate the excretion of urine, so that the toxic acetaldehyde formed in the body is excreted from the kidneys before being decomposed, irritating the kidneys.</p><ol start="7"><li><strong>Those who take certain drugs</strong></li></ol><p>Tea polyphenols are easy to interact with metal preparations to cause precipitation. When taking metal preparations such as calcium preparations, iron-containing blood supplements or iron-containing preparations, aluminum-containing preparations, cobalt preparations, silver preparations, etc., you should avoid drinking strong tea.</p><p>It is also not recommended to drink strong tea when taking hypnotic, sedative, antitussive drugs and enzyme preparations. Some Chinese herbal medicines, such as ephedra, Uncaria Chinensis, and Coptis Chinensis, should not be mixed with tea, and tea should not be drunk within 1 to 2 hours after taking the medicine.</p><p><strong>4 kinds of common tea have “specialties”</strong></p><p>Green tea, black tea, oolong tea, Pu’er tea… These common teas have different production processes, and each has its own health benefits.</p><p><strong>Green tea</strong></p><p>Polyphenolic compounds, such as catechins, are recognized as key components of green tea that are beneficial to health and have a variety of health care functions, including preventing cancer, improving cardiovascular health, and helping with weight loss.</p><p>Green tea is also the tea with the most types and richest content of vitamins. From the perspective of traditional Chinese medicine, green tea is slightly cold and helps to reduce the fire.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202273.gif"></p><p><strong>Black tea</strong></p><p>Black tea belongs to fully fermented tea. During processing, tea polyphenols are oxidized into theaflavins and thearubigins, and most of the sugars are hydrolyzed into soluble sugars, resulting in the unique aroma and taste of black tea.</p><p>Black tea is rich in theaflavins. A large number of medical studies have shown that drinking black tea can help regulate the content of low-density lipoprotein and high-density lipoprotein in human arteries. Theaflavins can also resist oxidation, prevent chronic inflammation and obesity.</p><p><strong>Oolong tea</strong></p><p>Oolong tea is also known as green tea. In addition to catechins, tea polysaccharides, tea saponins, etc., oolong tea also contains some special functional ingredients.</p><p>For example, some oolong tea varieties are rich in “methylated catechins”, which can help anti-allergy, anti-inflammatory, antioxidant, protect liver cells, and assist in lowering blood pressure.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202274.gif"></p><p><strong>Dark tea</strong></p><p>Dark tea is a post-fermented tea with rich minerals. Under the action of microorganisms, tea will undergo a series of complex chemical reactions to generate some functional components that are beneficial to the human body.</p><p>Pu-erh tea and Fu brick tea are representatives of different types of dark tea in my country, and their active ingredients are different, but they both help reduce lipids.</p><p><strong>Choose tea according to your constitution</strong></p><p>From the perspective of TCM health preservation, each person’s constitution is different, and the nature and taste of each type of tea are also different. According to the constitution and common manifestations in the “Classification and Determination of TCM Constitution”, the types of tea recommended drinking also have their emphasis.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202275.gif"></p><p><strong>Peaceful constitution</strong></p><p>The physique with normal functions is more coordinated, usually ruddy and energetic. You can drink all kinds of tea.</p><p><strong>Qi deficiency constitution</strong></p><p>It is manifested as being easily fatigued and weak, lack of breath and lazy words, or dizziness, and the complexion is a little yellow. It is recommended to drink Pu’er cooked tea, oolong tea, and eat it together with snacks made from soybeans, corn, peas, etc.</p><p><strong>Yang deficiency constitution</strong></p><p>Such people lack yang energy, fear the cold, and dare not eat cold food. People with this constitution can choose black tea, dark tea, and heavily fermented oolong tea (rock tea) to drink tea. Green tea, yellow tea, and Kuding tea are not recommended.</p><p><strong>Yin deficiency constitution</strong></p><p>Manifested as fever in the hands and feet, easy to dry mouth and throat, dry eyes, dry stool. Such people can drink more green tea, yellow tea, white tea, Kuding tea, lightly fermented oolong tea, less black tea, dark tea, and heavily fermented oolong tea.</p><p><strong>Blood stasis constitution</strong></p><p>It is manifested as dull complexion, dark tongue, or ecchymosis on the edge of the tongue, tongue tip, and tongue, often tingling in the body, and fish scale-like changes in the skin. If your tongue is pale and you are afraid of cold, you can drink black tea. If your tongue is red and your body is hot, you can drink green tea.</p><p><strong>Phlegm-dampness constitution</strong></p><p>Such people are mostly obese, with a plump and soft abdomen, prone to sweating, oily face, phlegm in the throat, and thick tongue coating. You can drink tangerine pucha, black tea, and dry ginger.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202276.gif"></p><p><strong>Hot and humid constitution</strong></p><p>Such people often have dampness and heat inside, the face and nose tip are always shiny, prone to acne on the face, itchy skin, and often bad breath. It is advisable to drink more green tea, yellow tea, white tea, Kuding tea, and less black tea, dark tea, and heavily fermented oolong tea.</p><p><strong>Qi stagnant constitution</strong></p><p>Manifested as thin, sentimental, emotionally fragile, and often feel pain in the breasts and flanks. Try to drink less tea with more caffeine, suitable for drinking hawthorn tea, rose tea, chrysanthemum tea, bergamot tea, tangerine peel tea.</p><p>Generally speaking, you can choose according to the warm and cool bias of tea: Yin and cold constitution, such as people who are often afraid of cold, suitable for drinking warm tea; positive constitution, such as people who are prone to dryness and heat, suitable for drinking cold tea; normal constitution , yin and yang balance, drink tea according to the season</p>]]></content>
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Magnify the tooth 1000 times, so you can see its truest appearance</title>
    <link href="/Magnify-the-tooth-1000-times-so-you-can-see-its-truest-appearance/"/>
    <url>/Magnify-the-tooth-1000-times-so-you-can-see-its-truest-appearance/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>In a sense, the mouth is the dirtiest place in the human body. It is estimated that there are more than 400 species of bacteria in the human mouth.</p><p>Plaque is a bacterial population that attaches to teeth. Using a microscope with a focused electron beam, the scientists magnified the tooth 1,000 times and photographed the tooth and its attached bacteria.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202261.webp"></p><p>Yellow plaque attached to the surface of the blue tooth</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202262.webp"></p><p>Dental plaque in the pink and purple coat</p><p>The staff made the pictures into color, to let people see more clearly the punctate bacteria lurking in the teeth and the plaque formed by the bacteria attached to the teeth.</p><p><strong>The culprit of periodontitis is plaque</strong></p><p>Bacteria in the oral cavity are not alone. They adhere to the surface of the teeth or the mucosal surface of the oral cavity through saliva and other substances to form dental plaque.</p><p>Even freshly cleaned teeth can develop new plaque in minutes. After 12 hours, the plaque will initially mature.</p><p>This plaque may irritate the local gums, causing periodontitis.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202263.gif"></p><p>The process by which normal gums develop into periodontitis</p><p>Dental calculus we often say is actually mineralized dental plaque. The accumulation of calculus will “run” under the gums, causing the gums to recede, eventually causing the teeth to loosen or even fall out.</p><p>Mild periodontitis manifests as red and swollen gums, bleeding from brushing, and bad breath;</p><p>Moderate periodontitis can cause inability to chew, sore gums, receding gums, and exposed tooth roots.</p><p>Severe periodontitis will cause symptoms such as tooth loosening, displacement, pain, inability to chew food, and eventually tooth loss.</p><p><strong>6 signs of plaque buildup</strong></p><p>If brushing is not timely or thorough, plaque can lead to tooth decay and calculus. When there is too much plaque, there are several signs that can appear early, and early identification can prevent oral problems from getting worse.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202264.gif"></p><ol><li><strong>The tooth surface is not smooth</strong></li></ol><p>When plaque builds upon the surface of the teeth, when touched with the tongue, the surface of the teeth will feel rough.</p><p>This often happens in the morning before you brush your teeth, and if it persists throughout the day, it could be a sign that plaque is building up.</p><ol start="2"><li><strong>Bad breath</strong></li></ol><p>Plaque contains bacteria, which produce an unpleasant odor.</p><ol start="3"><li><strong>Yellow teeth</strong></li></ol><p>When plaque “grows” on the teeth, the film can make the teeth appear dull white, or yellow.</p><ol start="4"><li><strong>Red, swollen or bleeding gums</strong></li></ol><p>Too much plaque can irritate the gums, making them swollen and painful, causing gingivitis. Bleeding when brushing your teeth after periodontitis.</p><ol start="5"><li><strong>Tartar buildup</strong></li></ol><p>When plaque is not removed for a long time, it hardens into tartar, calculus, which often appears at the junction of the gums and teeth and looks yellow or brown.</p><ol start="6"><li><strong>Sensitive teeth</strong></li></ol><p>Over time, plaque can cause gums to recede, which can make teeth feel more sensitive. Soreness when inhaling cold air, cold or hot food, or water.</p><p><strong>Brush your teeth after meals to prevent the teeth from being corroded by acid</strong></p><p>Periodontitis is a preventable disease. After eating, the oral environment will become “sour”. 12 minutes after a meal is the peak period of bacterial fermentation of carbohydrates to produce acid.</p><p>■ Studies have shown that the pH of the oral cavity begins to decrease after eating, and it drops to the lowest level in about 12 minutes. After half an hour, most people’s oral pH will return to normal levels.</p><p>■ The oral pH of some people with severe caries activity was lower than the critical value from the beginning; half an hour later, their tooth enamel was still in a demineralized state and was still fragile; after 1 hour, it had not returned to the normal level.</p><p>For most people, brushing your teeth early can interfere with and block this process, reducing the risk of acid erosion. Additionally, brushing your teeth once a day was associated with a 9% lower risk of cardiovascular disease and an 8% lower risk of diabetes.</p><p>Therefore, in addition to brushing in the morning and evening, it is best to brush after every meal. If not available, rinse your mouth with water.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202265.gif"></p><p>There is nothing wrong with brushing your teeth immediately after eating a normal diet. People who are worried about brushing their teeth to damage the enamel should pay more attention to the brushing method and the choice of the toothbrush.</p><p><strong>Ways to get rid of dental plaque</strong></p><p>Plaque may produce acid and decalcify to form dental caries, or secrete toxins against periodontal tissue. Therefore, the most important thing in daily dental care is to remove plaque to prevent dental caries and periodontitis.</p><p><strong>Brush your teeth with the Pasteur method</strong></p><p>When brushing your teeth, stick to the Pasteur brushing method, also known as gingival sulcus sweeping or horizontal fluttering.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202266.gif"></p><p>This cleans the plaque better without damaging the teeth and gums. Brush your teeth within 30 minutes after meals, at least 3 minutes each time, and choose a toothbrush with soft bristles.</p><p><strong>Use mouthwash</strong></p><p>Based on proper brushing, mouthwash can help inhibit plaque growth. If you choose a medical prescription mouthwash, you should first ask your doctor if it can be used for a long time.</p><p><strong>Use dental floss</strong></p><p>Simply brushing your teeth can only remove about 2&#x2F;3 of the plaque, and the rest are hidden between the teeth, under part of the gingival margin, and in the dead corners caused by the misalignment of the teeth, which can easily lead to adjacent surface caries, gingival inflammation and other symptoms.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202267.gif"></p><p><strong>Regular teeth cleaning</strong></p><p>Scaling is the most effective way to remove plaque and tartar. Brushing your teeth every six months to a year can prevent bleeding gums and loose teeth, effectively prevent periodontal disease, and help maintain oral health.</p><p><strong>Use a dental irrigator</strong></p><p>The irrigator can irrigate any part of the mouth through the nozzle, including between the teeth and deep gums where the toothbrush and floss are not easy to reach. It is recommended to rinse for 1-3 minutes after each meal.</p><p><strong>Use a gap brush</strong></p><p>For those with larger gaps, a gap brush can be used. Interstitial brushes are single-bristle brushes designed to remove plaque from larger interdental spaces, as well as aligners, fixed restorations, implants, gap retainers, and other hard-to-reach areas. The size of the gap brushes is different, which can be selected according to personal conditions and cleaning parts.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202268.gif"></p><p>To remove plaque, different groups of people should pay attention to different issues:</p><p>Elderly people with large gaps between their teeth can use more brushes. Middle-aged people are prone to get angry, and their gums are inflamed, swollen, and bleeding. Use a soft-bristled toothbrush. Children who have difficulty brushing their teeth can use an electric toothbrush.</p><p>It should be noted that if you use an electric toothbrush if you have bleeding gums, periodontal disease, or repair teeth, the speed should not be turned to the maximum.</p>]]></content>
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>What&#39;s going on inside your body when you laugh?</title>
    <link href="/Whats-going-on-inside-your-body-when-you-laugh/"/>
    <url>/Whats-going-on-inside-your-body-when-you-laugh/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Laughter is a part of being human from the first few months of life.</p><p>According to statistics, children laugh about 300 times a day on average, and adults laugh an average of 15 to 100 times a day. Women are generally more likely to laugh than men.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202251.gif"></p><p>Laughing produces a sense of happiness. What’s going on inside your body when you grin?</p><p><strong>People who love to laugh extend their life by four years, benefiting the whole body</strong></p><p>A summary of studies by the Spanish Society of Neurology found that people who laugh or smile live four and a half years longer than those who don’t.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202252.gif"></p><p>A good mood can strengthen the immune system, which in turn affects the health of the body. “Pleasant Emotion Therapy” in psychotherapy helps patients have a positive emotional experience.</p><p>When you grin, these changes are happening inside your body:</p><p><strong>Lower stress hormones</strong></p><p>Laughing once reduced levels of the three stress hormones cortisol, epinephrine, and dobachol in the body by 39%, 70%, and 38%, respectively.</p><p><strong>Stimulate serotonin secretion</strong></p><p>Smiling can promote the secretion of the neurotransmitter serotonin in the brain, and serotonin can reduce negative emotions such as irritability, enhance pleasure, and make people feel happy.</p><p><strong>Stimulate the immune system</strong></p><p>Laughter can reduce the level of inflammation in the body and increase the activity of K lymphocytes (a type of immune cells that play a role in fighting viruses, parasites, tumors, etc.). Therefore, laughter helps to strengthen the body’s immune system and protect the body from disease.</p><p><strong>Significantly increased pain threshold</strong></p><p>Laughing can relieve pain because it promotes the production of endorphins in the body. It is a natural pain reliever that enhances our ability to fight pain. When you’re suffering from illness, try to make yourself a little bit happier and maybe less painful.</p><p><strong>Blood circulation is improved</strong></p><p>When a person laughs, the blood flow to the organs increases and the blood circulation improves. In addition, laughter can also dilate blood vessels, increase blood supply to the brain, and lower blood pressure, so it can be called a “natural antihypertensive drug”.</p><p>In contrast to people who don’t like to laugh for a long time, a study by the Yamagata University School of Medicine in Japan found that men, smokers, inactive people, and diabetics are the majority of those who laugh less frequently.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202253.jpg"></p><p>Compared with those who laughed the most, those who laughed least often had a 1.95-fold higher risk of all-cause mortality and a 1.62-fold higher risk of cardiovascular events (stroke, myocardial infarction, angina, etc.).</p><p><em>6 cool science facts about laughter</em></p><p>Have you ever noticed that you feel refreshed every time you laugh out loud? The most common expression of a smile, in addition to making people feel happy, also hides a lot of scientific cold knowledge.</p><ol><li><strong>Laughing is an aerobic exercise</strong></li></ol><p>Laughing activates 53 muscles in the human body, which can exercise body parts such as the abdomen, shoulders, and diaphragm. Laughing for 10 to 15 minutes a day can burn 10 to 40 kcal.</p><p>A study by the University of Navarra in Spain showed that laughing 100 times is equivalent to cycling for 15 minutes.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202254.gif"></p><ol start="2"><li><strong>Laughing more improves concentration</strong></li></ol><p>A study by Kinki University in Japan proved that laughter can increase cerebral blood flow, improve cognitive function in the brain, and improve concentration.</p><p>After watching the video and laughing, people can concentrate more, answer questions faster, and increase blood flow in the frontal lobe related to brain activation by about 2.7 times.</p><ol start="3"><li><strong>Laughter strengthens relationships</strong></li></ol><p>Laughter has a strong social attribute. Early in life, a baby’s laughter is an external sign of happiness and helps strengthen the bond with the caregiver. Later, the laughter evolved into a sign of appreciation. Practicing a smile every day strengthens our social skills.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202255.gif"></p><ol start="4"><li><strong>Laughing more prolongs life than laughing</strong></li></ol><p>A study from the Department of Psychology at the University of Basel in Switzerland found that laughing every now and then throughout the day can help reduce stress and improve mood more than a one-time belly laugh.</p><ol start="5"><li><strong>Even a fake smile reduces stress</strong></li></ol><p>Smiling relieves physical tension and reduces stress hormones in the brain. People tend to frown when stressed, and even a fake smile can have a positive effect on stress relief.</p><ol start="6"><li><strong>Smile has region</strong></li></ol><p>In Strange Things, British psychologist Dr. Richard Wiseman says there is a clear geographic preference for what constitutes “interesting things”.</p><p>Americans usually like to tell jokes that contain a sense of superiority; continental Europeans tend to be light-hearted; British people are most easily amused by word games.</p><p><em><strong>How to make yourself a person who loves to laugh?</strong></em></p><p>A smile brings more than just that moment of happiness. People who laugh for a long time benefit from head to toe. I understand the truth, so how do you make yourself laugh?</p><p><strong>No.1 Spend more time with people who love to laugh</strong></p><p>A smile is contagious. Robert Provine, a professor of psychology at the University of Maryland in the United States, confirmed that just listening to recorded laughter caused subjects to giggle, which is why pre-recorded laughter is used in sitcoms.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202256.gif"></p><p>When laughter is heard, the area of the brain responsible for smiling automatically responds, displaying a smile that comes from the heart. You’re 30 times more likely to laugh when someone is around you than when you’re alone.</p><p><strong>No.2 Practice smiling for 10 minutes a day</strong></p><p>Smile practice is best done regularly several times a day, about 10 minutes each time.</p><p>If you can’t think of anything worth laughing about, you can pretend to be happy, and then gradually expand into a grin, and then you end up laughing.</p><p>A study published in Psychological Reports shows that forcing yourself to laugh (or even just smile) can improve mood. This is because the human brain cannot distinguish between genuine and fake laughter, and thus both achieve corresponding health benefits.</p><p><strong>No.3 Try watching talk shows and cross-talk</strong></p><p>A study by the International Cancer Center in Osaka, Japan found that cancer patients who enjoyed laughing while watching talk shows, stand-up comics, and counterpart comics had significantly improved immune function.</p><p>At the same time, the researchers found in the questionnaire that patients who often watched cross-talk felt their pain symptoms improve, and after enjoying a pleasant laugh, their tension, depression, and anger eased a lot, and their quality of life improved.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202257.gif"></p>]]></content>
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Is your sleep &#39;junk sleep&#39;? It&#39;s said to be worse than insomnia</title>
    <link href="/Is-your-sleep-junk-sleep-Its-said-to-be-worse-than-insomnia/"/>
    <url>/Is-your-sleep-junk-sleep-Its-said-to-be-worse-than-insomnia/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>When you wake up every morning, do you think you have enough sleep? Some people fall asleep when they touch the pillow, but feel groggy and powerless when they wake up… Scientists believe that these “Junk sleep” that “sleep equals no sleep” are even scarier than insomnia. Snoring does not mean good sleep, and sleep violence is also very bad. Oversleeping may lead to high mortality rate… A Japanese research survey shows that people who sleep 7 hours a day can live the longest, and the more sleep they sleep, the mortality rate The higher it is, if people who sleep more than 9 hours a day may have problems with their health. As the foundation of survival, sleep is closely related to our life.</p><p>Over the years, sleep experts from all over the world have been looking for a sleep rule that is truly suitable for human beings. In addition to the “Secret of the Biological Clock” that won the Nobel Prize in Physiology or Medicine before, there are many scientists on the road of sleep research. different discoveries. For example, according to the National Institutes of Health report, people who get 8 hours of sleep per night respond best, and if they get only 6 hours of sleep per night for 2 consecutive weeks, then it is equivalent to being forced to “stay up all night” for two nights. The surprising thing about the study is that people who sleep for 6 hours a night think they have enough sleep, but in fact their physical function and cognition are deteriorating without knowing it. Although they do not feel sleepy, their functional response is actually getting worse and worse. . Too little sleep is not good for your health, nor too much sleep.</p><p>The concept of “garbage sleep”, which was investigated by the British Sleep Commission, has once again aroused heated discussions in the academic circles. “JUNK SLEEP” corresponds to “JUNK FOOD”, which refers to the problem of insufficient sleep time and low sleep quality. Is your sleep like “garbage”? What is the correct sleep time? What are the dangers of sleeping too much? </p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/20202241.jpg"></p><p><strong>Which sleep is “Junk sleep”?</strong></p><ol><li><p>Falling asleep while watching TV, listening to music or playing video games;</p></li><li><p>Force yourself to go to bed and get up in the morning according to the “time point”, and the time “point” is always adjusted;</p></li><li><p>After waking up naturally, thinking of “staying in bed” again, forcing to prolong the sleep time;</p></li><li><p>Do not sleep at night, make up sleep during the day, make up sleep on weekends;</p></li><li><p>High work pressure, need to work overtime at night, fall asleep immediately after high-intensity work, etc.</p></li></ol><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202242.jpg"></p><p>How long should you sleep?</p><p>Sleep has certain health standards in terms of “time”. The British Sleep Association recommends that the best sleep time is 14 to 15 hours for infants aged 1 to 12 months, 12 to 14 hours for children aged 1 to 3 years, and 3 to 6 years old. 10 to 12 hours for children, 10 to 11 hours for children aged 7 to 12, 8 to 9 hours for adolescents aged 12 to 18, 7 to 9 hours for adults aged 18 to 65, and 7 to 8 hours for adults over 65. Sleep “time” is not the more the better, it should be moderate. Numerous studies have shown that excessive sleep increases disease morbidity and mortality, especially in the elderly population.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202243.jpg"></p><p>What are the dangers of sleeping too much?</p><ol><li><strong>Excessive sleep induces diabetes</strong></li></ol><p>The normal sleep time is 6-8 hours, and if it exceeds 9 hours, it becomes too long. Some studies have found that too long sleep can easily induce diabetes. Relevant surveys show that if you sleep more than 8 hours, the risk of diabetes will increase by more than 3 times.</p><ol start="2"><li><strong>People who sleep too long will become stupid</strong></li></ol><p>If you sleep for too long, people will become lazy. At the same time, because the sleep time is too long and the brain rests for too long, the cell activity of the brain will decrease. Because the sleep time is too long, the nerve cells will be inhibited for a long time. Over time, it will affect intelligence, lead to memory decline, and make people more and more stupid.</p><ol start="3"><li><strong>Easier to die</strong></li></ol><p>Relevant data show that people who sleep 7 hours a day have the lowest mortality rate, less than 6 hours will increase the risk of death, and more than 9 hours will also increase the risk of death. And the results of this statistic are not divided between men and women. Therefore, the more sleep is not the better, everything is counterproductive, less is detrimental to health, and more will also endanger life.</p><ol start="4"><li><strong>Weight gain</strong></li></ol><p>Researchers looked at weight and fat gain in Quebec adults over a six-year period. They found that people who slept too little and too long each night gained more weight than those who slept seven or eight hours. During the study period, people who slept 9 to 10 hours per night were 25% more likely to gain 5kg, even with controlled food intake and increased physical activity. Therefore, these results underscore the need to consider sleep duration in weight gain and obesity, the researchers wrote in the study.</p>]]></content>
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Anti-inflammatory diets go viral! What are the anti-inflammatory foods?</title>
    <link href="/Anti-inflammatory-diets-go-viral!-What-are-the-anti-inflammatory-foods/"/>
    <url>/Anti-inflammatory-diets-go-viral!-What-are-the-anti-inflammatory-foods/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Many diseases that plague the human body have a common feature - inflammation.</p><p>Recently, many food bloggers have begun to introduce a magical “anti-inflammatory diet” that claims to enhance the body’s immunity and reduce the risk of inflammatory infections.</p><p>Not only are there “anti-inflammatory diets,” but there are plenty of foods that can exacerbate inflammation. Are these eye-catching claims true?</p><p><em><strong>What is the “inflammation” of an “anti-inflammatory diet”?</strong></em></p><p><strong>The “inflammation” in an anti-inflammatory diet is not the same as the “inflammation” we often talk about caused by viruses or bacteria.</strong></p><p>Inflammation is a defense response of the body’s own immune system to external stimuli. The immune system is like a guard that protects the body. When there is trauma or infection, the immune system will be activated, and the guard will respond quickly, engulfing invading viruses and bacteria or clearing itself. The necrotic tissue, we call this inflammation caused by bacterial or viral invasion as acute inflammation, which comes and goes quickly.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202231.webp"></p><p>The “inflammation” in the anti-inflammatory diet is chronic inflammation, which is the low level of excessive production of various cytokines (interleukin, tumor necrosis factor TNF-α and interferon γ-INF, etc.) under stress or stress. level of chronic inflammation.</p><p>This inflammation can develop gradually over months or years and affect the immune system. At this time, the immune system is in a state of protracted war, always vigilant but tired and irritable, and it is easy to miss the gun.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202232.webp"></p><p><strong>This repeated and sustained immune response often brings harm to the body. Studies have shown that chronic inflammation is associated with many chronic diseases</strong>, such as obesity, type 2 diabetes, cardiovascular disease, chronic respiratory disease, psoriasis, rheumatoid arthritis, cancer Wait.</p><p>A 32-year report involving 210,000 participants published in 2020 by the Department of Nutrition at the Harvard School of Public Health shows that <strong>cardiovascular health is associated with an inflammatory state in the body, and food can exacerbate or improve the inflammatory state in the body.</strong></p><p><em><strong>What does an “anti-inflammatory diet” include?</strong></em></p><p>Since different foods have different effects on inflammation in the body, it is necessary to understand the anti-inflammatory or pro-inflammatory effects of different foods.</p><p>Overall, <strong>red meat, overly processed foods, and foods high in sugar and oil tend to lead to more inflammation in the body.</strong></p><p>Red meat contains a sialic acid molecule, Neu5Gc, which is not found in the human body. It is recognized by the immune system as a foreign invader, causing inflammation. Animal experiments have shown that long-term consumption of large amounts of red meat will increase the risk of cancer in mice.</p><p>Unprocessed foods such as white bread, sugar-sweetened beverages, salad dressings, and processed meat products are generally high in sugar, salt, and fat, and contain a lot of trans fatty acids, which can easily lead to chronic inflammation in the body.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202233.webp"></p><p><strong>Food components that improve chronic inflammation include omega-3 fatty acids, polyphenols, dietary fiber, and natural antioxidants</strong>; these substances can block signaling, inhibit prostate cyclooxygenase expression, downregulate levels of inflammatory mediators, and activate antioxidants. It can also exert an anti-inflammatory effect by adjusting the intestinal flora and producing short-chain fatty acids.</p><p><strong>The biological activity of anti-inflammatory foods has been validated in cell and mouse models, but inconclusive in human studies</strong>. In a review published in Critical Reviews in Food Science and Nutrition in 2021, <strong>the research team selected 88 foods with anti-inflammatory effects from 3,581 studies, including: cranberries, grapes, pomegranates, strawberries, whole grains products, low-fat dairy products, yogurt, sesame seeds, flax seeds, soy foods, turmeric, etc</strong>.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202234.webp"></p><p>Combining the above studies, <strong>the researchers divided foods that may have anti-inflammatory properties into 6 categories</strong>:</p><p><strong>Vegetables</strong>, especially cruciferous vegetables such as kale, cabbage, broccoli, etc.;</p><p><strong>Fruits</strong>, especially berries such as cranberries, strawberries, blueberries, grapes, etc.;</p><p><strong>Foods rich in dietary fiber</strong> such as whole grains, legumes;</p><p><strong>Foods rich in polyphenols and flavonoids</strong> such as green tea, soybeans, etc.;</p><p><strong>Spices</strong> such as turmeric, ginger, cinnamon, nutmeg, sage, and garlic;</p><p><strong>Foods are rich in omega-3 fatty acids</strong> such as salmon, flaxseed oil, algae oil, grapeseed oil, canola oil, nuts, almonds, etc.</p><p><em><strong>Does the “Anti-Inflammatory Diet” Really Work?</strong></em></p><p>Although the Anti-Inflammatory Diet is very fashionable, However, it is not a specific dietary pattern. <strong>The Mediterranean diet, DASH diet (A salt-reduced diet for people with high blood pressure), the Okinawan diet, the traditional Nordic diet, and the traditional Mexican diet are all anti-inflammatory diets.</strong></p><p>These dietary patterns share the same characteristics: <strong>a plant-based diet with an emphasis on fruits and vegetables, whole grains, foods rich in omega-3 fatty acids, lean meats, and spices.</strong></p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202235.webp"></p><p>Although the effect of diet on chronic inflammation has not been clearly quantified, some studies have shown positive effects. A 2016 study found that after one year of anti-inflammatory diet in patients with type 2 diabetes, the inflammatory factor-CRP in their blood was reduced by 37%. produced a suppressive effect.</p><p>These results are exciting, but the human body is very complex. To improve immunity and reduce the occurrence of chronic inflammation, one should not be superstitious about a certain legendary diet. In addition to a balanced diet, it is best to start from four aspects:</p><p><strong>Exercise</strong>: 30 minutes of moderate exercise every day, aerobic exercise is very effective in improving immunity.</p><p><strong>Reduced pressure</strong>: Long-term stress and tension will increase the level of inflammation in the human body. Maintaining an optimistic attitude and good habits is conducive to controlling the level of inflammatory factors in the body. Regular sleep also helps to slow down the accumulation of inflammatory factors.</p><p><strong>Weight contro</strong>l: Obesity can lead to hormonal and immune system disturbances and exacerbate chronic inflammation, so balance diet and exercise to maintain an appropriate weight and BMI.</p><p><strong>Get rid of bad habits and have regular physical examinations</strong>: smoking and drinking are recognized bad habits, which will increase the level of inflammatory cytokines in the blood; carry out regular physical examinations to detect potential risks of the body in time; if you have suffered from gastritis, pharyngitis, hepatitis Other inflammations or autoimmune diseases such as lupus erythematosus, arthritis, etc., require more detailed and scientific lifestyle and eating habits.</p><p>Allergy is also an important cause of chronic inflammation, so for allergic people, eliminating allergens is an important way to resist chronic inflammation.</p>]]></content>
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Obesity causes 35 diseases! Respiratory, nervous, and circulatory systems are all under  Pressure</title>
    <link href="/Obesity-causes-35-diseases-Respiratory-nervous-and-circulatory-systems-are-all-under-Pressure/"/>
    <url>/Obesity-causes-35-diseases-Respiratory-nervous-and-circulatory-systems-are-all-under-Pressure/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The number on the scale is a barometer of many people’s daily mood; it not only affects people’s emotions but also determines their health.</p><p>A meta-study published recently in the journal Biomedical Centre-Pharmaceuticals in the UK found that excess obesity is associated with an increased risk of 35 diseases.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202221.gif"></p><p><em><strong>Obesity causes 35 diseases</strong></em></p><p>A meta-study of 56 chronic diseases published in the journal Biomedical Center-Medicine found:</p><p>Obesity and type 2 diabetes, 14 circulatory diseases, asthma, chronic obstructive pulmonary disease, 5 digestive diseases, 3 musculoskeletal diseases, multiple sclerosis, and 6 digestive system cancers, uterine cancer, kidney cancer associated with an increased risk of bladder cancer for a total of 35 diseases.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202222.webp"></p><p><strong>Diabetes</strong></p><p>Genetically predicted high BMI [body mass index, BMI&#x3D;weight in kilograms&#x2F;height squared in meters] was associated with an increased risk of type 1 diabetes; higher BMI in adulthood was associated with an increased risk of type 2 diabetes.</p><p><strong>Circulatory system disease</strong></p><p>The risk of aortic stenosis was most strongly associated with high BMI, followed by heart failure and hypertension.</p><p>Obesity can increase the risk of type 2 diabetes and heart disease by increasing fasting blood sugar, triglyceride levels, and promoting systemic inflammation, the researchers said.</p><p><strong>Respiratory diseases</strong></p><p>The study found that the mortality of asthma and chronic obstructive pulmonary disease was related to BMI.</p><p><strong>Digestive system diseases</strong></p><p>A higher BMI increases the risk of several diseases, including gallstones, gastroesophageal reflux, Crohn’s disease, and nonalcoholic fatty liver disease. Of these, the nonalcoholic fatty liver disease had the strongest association.</p><p><strong>Musculoskeletal disorders</strong></p><p>Risks of gout, osteoarthritis and rheumatoid arthritis were associated with higher BMI.</p><p><strong>Nervous system disease</strong></p><p>The risk of multiple sclerosis also increased with increasing BMI, but no association was found between Alzheimer’s disease, amyotrophic lateral sclerosis (ALS), and BMI.</p><p><strong>Tumor</strong></p><p>Higher BMI is associated with cancers of the digestive system (including esophageal, gastric, colorectal, pancreatic, liver, and gallbladder&#x2F;biliary tract cancers), uterine cancer (including endometrial, cervical), ovarian, kidney, It was associated with an increased risk of bladder cancer, but was associated with a reduced risk of breast and prostate cancer.</p><p>The researchers say that the association of excess obesity with chronic disease cannot be ignored, and from now on, a sustained reduction in the prevalence of overweight&#x2F;obesity should be a major public health goal.</p><p><em><strong>Obesity can be divided into 4 grades</strong></em></p><p>If the human body is compared to a heavy truck, the danger of being overweight is the same as overloading a truck. The more overweight, the more serious the damage and the shorter the service life.</p><p>For example, when a truck with a nuclear load of 5 tons is overloaded by 3 to 5 tons, it seems to still be able to drive normally, but in fact it has done great damage; if it is overloaded by 10 tons, the truck may face the risk of being scrapped at any time.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202223.gif"></p><p>To scientifically prevent and control obesity, you can refer to the following weight management models. The normal range for BMI is 18.5 to 23.9, 24 to 27.9 for overweight, and over 28 for obesity.</p><p><strong>Phase 0</strong></p><p>Overweight without associated disease or its pre-existing conditions (eg, hyperuricemia, prediabetes, hyperlipidemia, fatty liver).</p><p>Being overweight is a health warning line, and it is necessary to conduct lifestyle interventions promptly, such as changing habits such as overeating and drinking, always eating late-night snacks, and eating too much oil and too salty, and at the same time increasing the amount of exercise.</p><p><strong>Phase 1</strong></p><p>Overweight, with associated pre-morbidity; or obesity, without or with associated pre-morbidity.</p><p>At this stage, professional doctors are required to intervene, prescribing exercise prescriptions, formulating diet plans, etc., and patients need to strictly implement lifestyle interventions.</p><p><strong>Phase 2</strong></p><p>Overweight or obese with associated mild to moderate disease.</p><p>In this stage, in addition to the treatment of diseases and strict implementation of lifestyle interventions, scientific weight loss is also required. Weight loss drugs can be used under the guidance of doctors, or small weight loss surgery can be performed.</p><p><strong>Phase 3</strong></p><p>Obesity with associated severe disease.</p><p>This stage will seriously threaten health or longevity. If the weight does not improve within 3 to 6 months based on strict implementation of lifestyle intervention and weight loss drug treatment, weight loss surgery may be required.</p><p><strong>Weight loss advice for obese people</strong></p><p>How to avoid weight loss mistakes and manage weight scientifically and effectively? Experts from various countries have given specific suggestions.</p><p><strong>Prioritize cardio</strong></p><p>The European Society for the Study of Obesity recommends a detailed exercise training regimen, and the following are exercise recommendations summarized by multidisciplinary experts from institutions including the Sorbonne University in France, Maastricht University in the Netherlands, Padova University in Italy, and the University of Leeds in the United Kingdom.</p><p>It is recommended to prioritize 150-200 minutes of at least moderate-intensity aerobic exercise per week, or high-intensity interval training (need to assess cardiovascular risk).</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202224.gif"></p><p>Aerobic exercise and high-intensity interval training have similar weight-loss and fat-loss effects in overweight or obese individuals, as long as the energy expended are similar. Using these two methods, the average weight loss is expected to be around 2 to 3 kg.</p><p>High-intensity interval training (HIIT) raises your heart rate and burns more calories in a short amount of time. In layman’s terms, it is a combination of aerobic and anaerobic exercise that is interspersed with low-intensity exercise or a short rest between high-intensity exercise.</p><p>For example, the alternation of running 100 meters fast and jogging 100 meters, but paying attention step by step, gradually adapting to the training, and then appropriately adding more training movements until all training is completed.</p><p>To maintain the weight after weight loss, it is recommended to do 200-300 minutes of moderate-intensity aerobic exercise every week.</p><p><strong>Control fat intake</strong></p><p>It is recommended that obese people choose olive oil and tea oil for cooking, and control it at 20-25 grams per day.</p><p>When going out to eat, choose light dishes, try not to order dishes with a lot of oil, such as boiled fish and fresh food; get rid of the habit of overeating, and eat fewer snacks with a lot of “oil”, such as shortbread bread, puffs Wait.</p><p><strong>Protect the Achilles tendon</strong></p><p>Big data shows that because of their heavier weight, the Achilles tendon bears a higher force on the Achilles tendon during exercise than the general population and is more prone to injury.</p><p>Fully warm up before exercise, avoid vigorous and fatiguing exercise, and exercise more muscles, all of which will help prevent Achilles tendon injury.</p><p>Finally, for obese people, the World Health Organization’s recommendation is: “even speed” to lose weight.</p><p>Don’t worry, lose 0.5-1 kg per week and 1-3 kg per month. This method does little damage to the body and is not easy to rebound.</p>]]></content>
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Every time you listen, speak, read, and write, you are &quot;massaging&quot; your brain</title>
    <link href="/Every-time-you-listen-speak-read-and-write-you-are-massaging-your-brain/"/>
    <url>/Every-time-you-listen-speak-read-and-write-you-are-massaging-your-brain/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>You can’t speak fluently, your ears don’t work well, you can’t name things when you see things… When did you realize that you were suddenly “old”?</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202211.gif"></p><p>In the book “Changing Minds: How Aging Affects Language and How Language Affects Aging”, University of Memphis psychology professors Roger Cruz and Dr. Richard Roberts mentioned that aging is a two-way process, time plays a decisive role, but human intervention is Also important.</p><p>Through the learning and use of language, people can influence the cognitive aging process, promote brain health, and even prolong life and improve the quality of life.</p><p><em><strong>The more language you use, the better your brain becomes</strong></em></p><p>“Language is a very important part of cognitive function.” Cognitive function is a person’s ability to understand the external world, including memory, calculation, execution, attention, language, and orientation (including space, time, and character relationships). ).</p><p><strong>Listening, speaking, reading and writing protect cognitive function</strong></p><p>Clinically, some dementia patients do not have problems with memory, but have language barriers.</p><p>For example, the naming disorder, that is, the patient knows that the cup is used for drinking water, but cannot call the name; and the patient’s language expression is confusing, not fluent, and it is difficult to say a complete sentence. Language training for these patients can play a certain role. improve.</p><p>That is to say, the training of listening, speaking, reading, and writing has a certain protective effect on cognitive function. The famous “Nun Study” in the United States found that an individual’s early language ability may be related to the risk of Alzheimer’s disease.</p><p> <img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202212.webp"></p><p>The nuns participating in the study are playing a competitive scrabble game</p><p>The more developed the language function in the early years, the deeper the depth of thought logic, the better the cognitive function will be maintained in the later years, and the lower the risk of developing Alzheimer’s disease.</p><p><strong>Brains ‘get smaller’ from age 40</strong></p><p>Human brain development generally peaks between the ages of 20 and 40. From the age of 40, the number of nerve cells (neurons) in the brain gradually decreases, which affects memory, coordination, and brain function, and the size of the brain gradually shrinks.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202213.gif"></p><p>From a physiological point of view, people’s memory, reaction ability and executive ability will irreversibly decline with age, <strong>but language ability does not age with the body, on the contrary, the more it is used, the more developed it is.</strong></p><p>Many examples of “late bloomers” show that age does not impair people’s ability to speak, write, and learn new vocabulary, and even the ability to understand, use, and create language develops well in old age.</p><p>For example, Canadian female writer Alice Munro wrote her first novel at the age of 37 and won the Nobel Prize for Literature at the age of 82; British writer Daniel Defoe did not publish her first novel “Lu “Binson Crusoe”; Shandong writer Jiang Shumei began to learn and read at the age of 60, published her first book at the age of 74, and then published 5 works in seven or eight years…</p><p><em><strong>How Listening, Reading, Writing, and Writing Affect Brain Health</strong></em></p><p>Listening, speaking, reading, writing, and reading accompany people throughout their lives, which not only affects people’s cognition and personality, but also affects their brain health.</p><p><strong>Listening: Strengthening Cognitive Resilience</strong></p><p>One of the most obvious signs of physical aging is hearing loss. ENT experts at Johns Hopkins University in the United States have found that people with hearing loss have an accelerated decline of 30% to 40% in hearing and cognitive abilities.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202214.gif"></p><p>Hearing is an important channel for language input to the brain. The reasons for the accelerated impairment of cognitive function due to hearing loss may include:</p><p>Diseases that cause hearing deterioration can also impair cognition; hearing loss reduces stimulation of key areas of the brain, accelerating neurodegeneration; hearing loss affects information acquisition and depletes cognitive reserves.</p><p>A study published in the American Journal of Medicine found that as long as someone listens when speaking, the brain is more cognitively resilient. 4 years.</p><p><em><strong>Speaking: Exercise brain flexibility</strong></em></p><p>Talking is a benign stimulus to the brain and helps keep it alive.</p><p>If a person lives in isolation and no one speaks and communicates, not only will the ability to speak slowly deteriorate, but also loneliness and social isolation will occur, thereby reducing cognitive function.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202215.gif"></p><p>Clinically, some dementia patients also have problems with speaking ability, such as poor expression, difficulty in finding words, and difficulty in naming. Among them, <strong>the difficulty of finding words is a typical cognitive impairment problem</strong>, and suddenly cannot remember familiar things, names, but also proper nouns and object names.</p><p>Studies have shown that when a person reads instructions aloud, they tend to focus better and perform better than those who read them silently. If you need to remember a lot of information, especially in writing, reading aloud is the best way to do it.</p><p><strong>Reading: Boost your brainpower</strong></p><p>When reading, the brain must coordinate numerous perceptual and cognitive functions, including basic visual skills, phonological perception, long-term memory, and working memory.</p><p>When reading, in addition to paying attention to the current information points (story background, characters, details, etc.), you should also connect with the content you read before.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202216.gif"></p><p>There are hundreds of millions of information points in each book, and the brain needs to continuously remember this information and store it, which ultimately enhances memory.</p><p>Brain scans of people with an average age of 76 at the University of California, Berkeley, found that reading at an early age can prevent Alzheimer’s disease.</p><p>According to a study by the Rush University Medical Center in the United States, the elderly who regularly read and read newspapers have a 32% lower risk of mental decline than the general population.</p><p>A large-scale study led by the Yale School of Public Health found that people who read at least 30 minutes a day lived nearly two years longer on average than those who didn’t.</p><p>It should also be reminded that the carrier of this reading is a paper book, not an e-ink product.</p><p><strong>Write: Strengthen memory</strong></p><p>Writing activates the motor, visual and cognitive areas of the brain.</p><p>“Writing not only mobilizes cognition, but also the motor function of the body.” Shen Lu said that writing is the strengthening of memory. In the process of choosing words and sentences, both the mind and the body are well exercised.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202217.gif"></p><p>Gerontologists at Utah State University found that people who kept a diary throughout their lives had a 53 percent lower risk of developing cognitive impairment.</p><p>It should be noted that the four dimensions of language listening, speaking, reading, and writing can operate relatively independently. For example, a stroke patient may lose the ability to read, but not necessarily the ability to understand language and speak, and even continue to write.</p><p>Language ability “uses it and loses it” will also decline in the normal aging process, but maintaining and exercising language ability can optimize cognitive function and fight to age.</p><p><em><strong>5 small things to exercise language function</strong></em></p><p>Like physical exercise, language exercise should also be adhered to, especially for the elderly. Experts recommend starting from the following points.</p><p><strong>Keep listening</strong></p><p>When hearing loss occurs, you should seek medical attention or get hearing aids in time; listen to soothing and familiar music or stories from your youth to awaken pleasant memories.</p><p>Research from institutions such as the University of Toronto confirms that repeated listening to meaningful music produces beneficial brain plasticity in mild cognitive impairment or early Alzheimer’s disease.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202218.gif"></p><p><strong>Actively communicate</strong></p><p>The elderly should communicate more with their family members in their lives. For example, after watching TV and discussing the plot with their family members, they can not only exercise memory, but also enhance their feelings.</p><p>Participate in more social activities, such as speech contests, etc., to exercise language skills; maintain healthy social interactions, and refuse bad social behaviors such as gambling and alcoholism.</p><p><strong>Keep reading</strong></p><p>It is recommended that the elderly read more books and newspapers, at least 3 to 5 days a week, and read at least 30 minutes a day, which can not only help memorize words and knowledge, but also understand the latest information, so as not to be out of touch with society.</p><p>The material to be read should be scientific and slightly challenging, to mobilize the elderly’s thinking or learn new knowledge.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202219.gif"></p><p><strong>Develop the habit of writing</strong></p><p>Cultivate the habit of writing a diary, copying poems or words of interest, not only to exercise writing ability, but also to exercise work and motor functions.</p><p>The elderly can also read the written diary regularly to evoke memories and exercise memory function. Anxiety and depression patients usually write more, which can also reduce the symptoms of emotional tension.</p><p><strong>Try to learn a new language</strong></p><p>A new study from New York University shows that in addition to enhancing cognition, learning a second language can also broaden your horizons and add joy to life.</p><p>Experts remind that the decline in listening, speaking, reading, and writing skills often indicate cognitive dysfunction, and every change in function may be a signal of some diseases:</p><ol><li>The language fluency is decreased, and the language fluency test can be used for self-examination.</li></ol><p>Say the names of fruits, vegetables, or animals as much as possible within 1 minute, 14 with a college degree or above are considered qualified; 12 with a high school degree; 11 with a junior high school degree; and 10 with a primary school degree or below.</p><ol start="2"><li><p>Difficulty finding words, unable to understand other people’s speech, such as watching TV and unable to keep up with the plot.</p></li><li><p>The speech is simple and repeated. After the next sentence is finished, you do not know what the previous sentence is saying.</p></li><li><p>Difficulty in writing or reading, unable to write complex characters, unable to read newspapers.</p></li></ol><p>Once the above situation occurs, you should pay attention to it and see a memory clinic or a cognitive specialist.</p>]]></content>
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Quit smoking gradually VS Quit smoking immediately</title>
    <link href="/Quit-smoking-gradually-VS-Quit-smoking-immediately/"/>
    <url>/Quit-smoking-gradually-VS-Quit-smoking-immediately/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>A single cigarette produces at least 4,000 chemicals from lighting to burning out, 69 of which are identified as carcinogens.</p><p>A study published in The Lancet shows that quitting smoking early can prevent 28 diseases such as myocardial infarction and lung cancer.</p><p>Many smokers are aware of the dangers of smoking and try to quit smoking, but they are often unbearable with various withdrawal reactions and fail repeatedly.</p><p>From a scientific point of view, gradually quit smoking vs abruptly quit smoking, which method has a higher success rate?</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202201.webp"></p><p><em>Gradually quit smoking VS immediate smoking cessation, which one to choose?</em></p><p>Scientists from the Universities of Oxford and Birmingham, UK, conducted a randomized controlled clinical trial to evaluate the smoking cessation effect of “gradual withdrawal” and “immediate withdrawal”.</p><p>The researchers included 697 ex-smokers with established addictions and randomly divided them into two groups:</p><p>The first group is the “immediate smoking-cessation group”, that is, quit smoking directly and completely from the beginning;</p><p>The other group gradually reduced the amount of smoking 2 weeks in advance, reduced it to 1&#x2F;2 of the original smoking amount on the first weekend, reduced it to 1&#x2F;4 of the original smoking amount on the second weekend, and then stopped smoking.</p><p>In addition, both groups of participants received the same behavioral supportive treatment and short-acting nicotine replacement therapy to cope with the uncomfortable symptoms of smoking cessation and improve the success rate.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202202.webp"></p><p>The research team compared the smoking cessation effects of the participants at 4 weeks, 8 weeks, and 6 months after the start of complete smoking cessation.</p><p>The criteria for evaluating the effect of smoking cessation include the quitter’s oral and the exhaled carbon monoxide concentration of the quitter. The results show that:</p><p><strong>At 4 weeks</strong></p><p>39.2% of the people in the “gradual tapering group” quit smoking successfully without relapse; while 49% of the people in the “immediately stop smoking group” quit smoking successfully without relapse.</p><p><strong>At 8 weeks</strong></p><p>The success rate of smoking cessation was 29.2% in the “taper tape group” and 36.6% in the “immediate withdrawal group”.</p><p><strong>At 6 months</strong></p><p>15.1% of the “gradually tapering group” quit smoking successfully without relapse, and 22% of the “immediately stop smoking group” quit smoking successfully without relapse.</p><p>The above three groups of data show that the success rate of smoking cessation in the “immediate smoking-cessation group” is higher than that in the “gradually tapering group”.</p><p>The conclusion is clear: To improve your chances of quitting smoking, it is best to stop smoking from the moment you decide to start quitting.</p><p><strong>Smoking Addiction</strong></p><p><strong>Chronic diseases recognized by WHO</strong></p><p>The famous writer Mark Twain said: “It’s easy to quit smoking. I have quit dozens of times in my life.” A joke is enough to show how difficult it is to quit smoking.</p><p>Nicotine in tobacco is a highly addictive substance, which is an important reason for many “old smokers” to smoke for a long time.</p><p>After nicotine is inhaled into the human body, it will enter the brain center with the blood within 10 seconds, stimulating a sharp and short-term release of dopamine.</p><p>Dopamine’s euphoric effect wears off quickly once nicotine intake is stopped, leaving smokers unable to continue experiencing euphoria and experiencing withdrawal and cravings.</p><p>Therefore, addicts smoke cigarettes every once in a while to maintain nicotine levels in the brain.</p><p>It should be emphasized that smoking addiction (also known as tobacco dependence) is not a behavioral habit, but a chronic disease. The World Health Organization has included it in the International Classification of Diseases, coded as F17.2.</p><p>The study found that the brain structure and function of tobacco-dependent patients will change, manifested as gray and white matter atrophy, abnormal neural activity in the frontal lobe, temporal lobe, and limbic lobe, and significantly reduced functional connectivity of the insula-related brain regions, proving the pathological site of this chronic disease. in the brain.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202203.gif"></p><p>Tobacco dependence is divided into physical dependence and psychological dependence:</p><p>Physical dependence refers to a series of unbearable withdrawal symptoms, including irritability, anxiety, restlessness, headache, inability to concentrate, sleep disturbance, etc., after smokers stop smoking or reduce the amount of smoking.</p><p>Psychological dependence, also known as spiritual dependence, is manifested as a strong subjective desire to smoke.</p><p>Physical dependence and psychological dependence cannot be completely separated, and often coexist, which affects the success rate of smoking cessation.</p><p><strong>“Withdrawal” is the biggest obstacle</strong></p><p>The reason why quitting smoking is particularly difficult is often because of “withdrawal symptoms”.</p><p>In general, withdrawal symptoms are a normal phenomenon in the process of smoking cessation. They usually begin to appear a few hours after smoking cessation, are most intense during the first 14 days of smoking cessation, and gradually decrease until they disappear.</p><p>Therefore, relapse is most likely when you first quit smoking.</p><p>Most withdrawal symptoms last about a month, and there are steps you can take during this period to help you get through the toughest phase.</p><p><em><strong>How to deal with “withdrawal reaction”?</strong></em></p><p>For example, take a deep breath or go for a walk outside when feeling tense or irritable;</p><p>When you can’t concentrate, try to reduce the workload and take a short rest;</p><p>When feeling tired, be sure to get enough sleep and take a proper nap at noon;</p><p>When you always want to eat, choose some fresh vegetables and fruits instead of high-calorie snacks.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/20220204.gif"></p><p>It should be noted that some people still relapse after quitting smoking for several months or even years, generally due to inducing factors, such as high work pressure, sudden accidents at home, social gatherings, etc.</p><p>When encountering such a situation, one must firm up the belief that quitting smoking is to say goodbye to the cigarette completely, not to touch a cigarette again, and not to take a fluke mentality that “it’s okay to take a puff or two”;</p><p>Secondly, to avoid factors that induce smoking, stay away from other smokers, limit alcohol consumption, etc.;</p><p>Smoking can be replaced by some compensatory behaviors, such as drinking water, chewing sugar-free gum, taking a walk, listening to music, etc.</p><p>In this case, the craving for smoking will not last too long, and as long as you stick to it for a few more minutes, it is likely to avoid a relapse.</p><p><strong>Smoking cessation clinics may improve success rates</strong></p><p>Some smokers can rely on perseverance to quit smoking. For tobacco-dependent patients, smoking cessation clinics can help improve the success rate of smoking cessation.</p><p>Doctors will formulate personalized smoking cessation treatment plans according to the methods recommended by clinical smoking cessation guidelines, including smoking cessation advice, smoking cessation drug treatment, and other intervention methods.</p><p>The doctor will also regularly track and follow up on the smoking cessation situation to help solve the problems encountered in the process of smoking cessation.</p><p>Don’t be afraid of smoking cessation drugs. Smoking addiction is a chronic disease and the use of drugs is a very formal approach. There is ample evidence that smoking cessation drugs can relieve withdrawal symptoms and improve the success rate of smoking cessation.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202045.webp"></p><p>Whether it is an “old smoker” or someone who has recently become addicted, some preparations need to be done before quitting smoking to help quit smoking successfully.</p><p><strong>Determine a quit smoking day</strong></p><p>You can choose an important day, such as holidays, birthdays, anniversaries, etc. From this day on, don’t smoke again.</p><p><strong>Create an environment conducive to smoking cessation</strong></p><p>Before quitting smoking, dispose of all smoking-related items around you, including cigarettes, lighters, ashtrays, etc. at home, in the car, in the office, and with you, and try to create a smoke-free environment.</p><p><strong>Review past smoking cessation experiences</strong></p><p>If you have tried to quit smoking before, you can summarize your past experience and find out what helped you quit smoking and what was more likely to lead to relapse.</p><p>Especially for problems or difficulties that may arise in the first few weeks, such as nicotine withdrawal symptoms, and plan ahead.</p><p><strong>Team up to quit smoking or get personal supervision</strong></p><p>Tell family, friends, and colleagues that you have decided to quit smoking, and get their understanding and support. In addition, smokers around you should be encouraged to quit smoking together, at least not in front of you.</p><p><strong>Write a commitment</strong></p><p>It is recommended to sign a smoking cessation commitment letter with yourself, and you can also leave one for your supporters, which will help you get encouragement and supervision from others.</p>]]></content>
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>People with magnesium deficiency have poor anti-cancer ability! How to be an &quot;Mg&quot; eater?</title>
    <link href="/People-with-magnesium-deficiency-have-poor-anti-cancer-ability-How-to-be-an-Mg-eater/"/>
    <url>/People-with-magnesium-deficiency-have-poor-anti-cancer-ability-How-to-be-an-Mg-eater/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Many people think about supplementing calcium, vitamin D, and even iron when supplementing nutrition, but few people think about supplementing magnesium.</p><p>But in fact, magnesium is needed for many activities in the human body: activating muscles and nerves, increasing body energy, digesting protein, carbohydrates, and fats, etc.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202191.webp"></p><p>Magnesium deficiency can cause 21 conditions including anxiety and asthma.</p><p><em><strong>Study finds that magnesium may help immune cells fight cancer</strong></em></p><p>On January 19, 2022, a research team from the University of Basel in Switzerland published a study in the American journal “Cell”, showing that T cells can help immune cells fight cancer in a magnesium-rich environment.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202192.webp"></p><p>The experiment provided mice with cancer cells in a diet deficient in magnesium ions, and found that the cancer cells in the mice spread faster, and then supplemented with a diet containing magnesium ions, and found that the immune capacity of the mice was enhanced.</p><p>Further analysis found that in an environment rich in magnesium ions, magnesium binds to the T cell surface protein LFA-1, thereby increasing the immune capacity of T cells and effectively resisting cancer cells.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202193.webp"></p><p>T cells (blue) form immune synapses through LFA-1 to attack tumor cells (white)</p><p>Experiments show that:</p><p>Low levels of magnesium in serum have poor immunity;</p><p>Tumors locally increased magnesium levels, and T cells enhanced immune responses to cancer cells.</p><p>Using data from an earlier study in cancer patients, the researchers re-analyzed it and found that immunotherapy was less effective in patients with insufficient blood levels of magnesium.</p><p>Therefore, magnesium may be able to act as a “right-hand man” for the human immune system and play a role in promoting cancer treatment.</p><p><em><strong>The body sends these signals when magnesium is deficient</strong></em></p><p>In life, many people will have symptoms such as insomnia, depression, anorexia, and fatigue, which may be due to magnesium deficiency in the body. Magnesium is one of the essential minerals in the human body. When magnesium is deficient, the body will prompt 7 signals:</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202194.gif"></p><p><strong>Difficulty falling asleep</strong></p><p>Magnesium helps to increase levels of a neurotransmitter in the brain called gamma-aminobutyric acid (GABA), which promotes relaxation and sleep, helping to relieve sleep disorders.</p><p><strong>Depression</strong></p><p>Magnesium can improve human hormone regulation and brain serotonin levels, which is beneficial to blood sugar balance. Brain serotonin is essential for maintaining emotional stability, so magnesium deficiency is more prone to depression and anxiety.</p><p><strong>Migraine</strong></p><p>“European Journal of Neuroscience Research” has published research that magnesium can effectively reduce the severity and frequency of migraine symptoms, which is related to magnesium’s ability to regulate hormones and relax muscles.</p><p><strong>Eyelid jump</strong></p><p>One of the most common manifestations of magnesium deficiency is eyelid twitching. This is because magnesium regulates muscle movement, and when magnesium levels in the body are low, muscle spasms and twitching occur in many parts of the body.</p><p><strong>Abnormal heart rhythm</strong></p><p>Magnesium helps maintain a normal heart rhythm. Doctors give magnesium supplements intravenously to reduce atrial fibrillation and arrhythmias because magnesium reduces levels of nutrients such as calcium.</p><p><strong>Always feel tired</strong></p><p>Magnesium is an essential element of the human body’s energy production system, and the human body needs magnesium to generate adenosine triphosphate for energy production.</p><p><strong>Prone to skin problems</strong></p><p>Magnesium reduces inflammation in the body that can lead to skin conditions like acne, eczema, psoriasis, and more. Magnesium also regulates vitamin D levels and maintains healthy skin.</p><p><em><strong>6 types of people are prone to lack of “magnesium”</strong></em></p><p>Insufficient magnesium intake, malabsorption, or increased excretion can lead to magnesium deficiency, causing loss of appetite, nausea, vomiting, fatigue, and weakness.</p><p>With the increase of the deficiency, numbness, tingling, muscle spasm, arrhythmia, etc. may also occur, and even lead to hypocalcemia and hypokalemia. There are 6 types of people who are easy to be recruited:</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202195.gif"></p><p><strong>Calcium supplement population</strong></p><p>After middle age, calcium loss is faster than calcium deposition. The risk of osteoporosis is increased, and many middle-aged and elderly people will supplement calcium, but high calcium will competitively inhibit the absorption of magnesium.</p><p><strong>Unbalanced diet</strong></p><p>Middle-aged people tend to gain weight. People who don’t have time to exercise will lose weight by dieting, and hunger will affect the intake of magnesium. Some middle-aged people don’t like meat, but a high-protein diet will reduce the absorption rate of magnesium.</p><p><strong>Strong tea drinkers</strong></p><p>The caffeine in strong tea contains a diuretic component that increases magnesium loss.</p><p><strong>People with diabetes</strong></p><p>Middle-aged and elderly people are a high-risk group of diabetes. Diabetes increases the excretion of magnesium, and magnesium deficiency, in turn, reduces the working efficiency of insulin, forming a vicious circle.</p><p><strong>People who take certain drugs for a long time</strong></p><p>Some drugs such as bisphosphonates and tetracycline antibiotics can affect the absorption of magnesium, and some diuretics (such as furosemide, hydrochlorothiazide tabletsdiureticic acid) can increase the excretion of magnesium.</p><p><strong>Frequent drinkers</strong></p><p>Alcohol abuse can cause pancreatitis, alcoholic ketoacidosis, etc., and increase the excretion of magnesium. Long-term excessive drinking can easily lead to serious loss of magnesium.</p><p><em><strong>To become a “magnesium” eater should do:</strong></em></p><p><strong>Eat green leafy vegetables</strong></p><p>Leafy greens are the richest in magnesium, followed by whole grains, nuts, meat, and milk.</p><p>However, green leafy vegetables contain oxalic acid, which affects magnesium absorption, and whole grains contain phytic acid, which affects magnesium absorption. It is recommended to blanch the vegetables in boiling water before cooking them; when cooking coarse grains, soak them for a while in advance.</p><p><strong>There is no need to take magnesium supplements if you</strong></p><p>Drinking milk every day, eating meat, and eating more “magnesium” foods can fully meet the body’s magnesium needs, and there is no need to take magnesium supplements.</p><p><strong>Avoid these drinks</strong></p><p>Avoid beverages that cause magnesium loss in the body, such as alcohol, strong tea, coffee, etc., and drink plenty of water.</p><p><strong>A balanced and varied diet</strong></p><p>Usually moderate intake of fruits and vegetables, with staple food thickness. Reduce high-salt, high-fat diets.</p><p>If necessary, magnesium supplements can be taken in moderation under the guidance of a doctor. It is recommended that the calcium and magnesium intake ratio should be maintained at 1:1.</p><p>For children and the elderly, magnesium is more important than calcium; if the kidneys are not functioning well, magnesium supplementation must be evaluated by a doctor.</p>]]></content>
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>3 kinds of &quot;functional&quot; toothpaste that doctors are afraid of! These ingredients may induce enteritis</title>
    <link href="/3-kinds-of-functional-toothpaste-that-doctors-are-afraid-of-New-research-These-ingredients-may-induce-enteritis/"/>
    <url>/3-kinds-of-functional-toothpaste-that-doctors-are-afraid-of-New-research-These-ingredients-may-induce-enteritis/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Anti-moth, whitening, hemostasis, antibacterial, anti-allergic… Many people pay attention to the “function” written on the package when buying toothpaste and rarely look at the specific ingredients.</p><p>Recently, the international academic journal “Nature Communications” published a study: antibacterial agent triclosan (TCS) contained in some toothpaste may cause damage to the human intestine and induce enteritis.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202181.gif"></p><p><em><strong>This ingredient in toothpaste can induce enteritis</strong></em></p><p>The research, carried out by Tsai Zongwei’s team at Hong Kong Baptist University in collaboration with a foreign team, explains how the antibacterial agent triclosan (TCS) triggers intestinal inflammation.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202182.webp"></p><p>Studies have shown that after exposure to TCS, the intestinal toxicity of TCS is stimulated under the action of human gut microbial GUS enzymes, which in turn leads to the appearance of enteritis. By targeting the inhibition of gut microbial GUS enzymes, the harm of TCS to the human gut may be eliminated.</p><p>This study also further confirmed that TCS, a common ingredient in daily necessities, will cause certain harm to the human body, so you must pay more attention when choosing daily necessities.</p><p><em><strong>Dentists are afraid of 3 toothpaste ingredients</strong></em></p><p>According to the British “Daily Mail” report, many toothpaste ingredients are harmful to our health, Dr. Toby Talbert, a dental expert at the Royal College of Surgeons, reminded us to pay attention to these 3 ingredients:</p><p><strong>Descaler: It can easily cause mouth ulcers</strong></p><p>The oral mucosa is one of the most delicate tissues, and sodium lauryl sulfate is the most effective cleaning agent, which can cause irritation or damage the oral mucosa, leading to chronic oral ulcers.</p><p>People with frequent oral ulcers and those with ulcers are best not to use a toothpaste containing sodium lauryl sulfate.</p><p><strong>Whitening agent: easy to damage gums</strong></p><p>Bleaching agents such as hydrogen peroxide are added to many to toothpaste to whiten teeth. However, they can irritate soft tissues, damage the oral mucosa, and damage the gums.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202183.gif"></p><p>The whiteness of teeth is related to enamel and dentin, which is difficult to change with toothpaste. Although bleaching agents can remove some stains on the surface of the teeth, they have little effect on the deep stains that are endogenous to the teeth.</p><p><strong>Abrasives: can damage tooth enamel</strong></p><p>Fine particles are added to many to toothpaste to remove stains from the surface of the teeth, however, some ointments are not abrasive enough and can wear away the enamel, which can lead to sensitive teeth over time.</p><p>It is recommended to purchase toothpaste containing aluminum hydroxide or calcium hydrogen phosphate with fine particles. These abrasives are relatively good and cause less damage to the tooth surface.</p><p><em><strong>“Functional toothpaste” should not be used indiscriminately</strong></em></p><p>Toothpaste is used as a brushing aid. Its basic function is to clean the oral cavity. Generally, commercially available toothpaste can be satisfied after strict testing. The effects of whitening, anti-cavity, desensitization, and hemostasis are all auxiliary and are not enough to directly affect oral health.</p><p><strong>Whitening toothpaste:</strong></p><p>Mainly, some special “friction particles” are added, which can remove the cigarette stains and tea stains deposited on the surface of the teeth, but do not affect deep endogenous stains such as tetracycline teeth and fluorosis teeth.</p><p>If the friction particles are large and hard, long-term use may also cause tooth wear.</p><p>There is also some whitening toothpaste with blue paste, which can only achieve the “visual effect” of temporary whitening through the blue foam.</p><p><strong>Acid-proof toothpaste:</strong></p><p>The principle is to form a protective film on the surface of the tooth, thereby enhancing the disease prevention ability of the periodontal tissue, but it should be stopped after symptoms improve, otherwise it will destroy the microbial ecological balance in the oral cavity.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202184.gif"></p><p><strong>Antibacterial toothpaste:</strong></p><p>Some medicated toothpaste has bactericidal and bacteriostatic ingredients, which can help kill some bacteria in the oral cavity in a short time, but daily use is equivalent to taking a small number of antibiotics for a long time, which is not conducive to the microbalance of oral flora and is prone to drug resistance.</p><p><strong>Anti-sensitive toothpaste:</strong></p><p>Desensitizing ingredients such as fluoride and strontium chloride are added, which can only relieve mild dentin hypersensitivity to a certain extent.</p><p><strong>Fresh breath toothpaste:</strong></p><p>The freshness of the breath comes from brushing your teeth carefully, removing plaque and some harmful bacteria, not the fragrance of the toothpaste itself, so the “scent” of the toothpaste is not so important.</p><p><em><strong>Choose a toothpaste that suits you</strong></em></p><p>The use of toothpaste should vary from person to region and region, and should not be used blindly for a long time.</p><p> <img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202185.gif"></p><p><strong>Mainly depends on the quality of the friction agent</strong></p><p>Small particles should be selected to prevent damage to the tooth. The ones containing aluminum hydroxide and calcium hydrogen phosphate are better, followed by silica, and the particles of calcium carbonate are the largest.</p><p><strong>Change toothpaste</strong></p><p>Using a toothpaste for a long time, the bacteria in the mouth will develop resistance and learn to “resist” the effect of toothpaste to clean the mouth.</p><p><strong>Sharing a toothpaste</strong></p><p>Sharing a toothpaste can easily lead to cross-infection of many oral diseases. If someone in the family catches a cold or suffers from other oral diseases, some viruses and bacteria may remain in the crevices of the toothbrush after brushing.</p><p>The next time you brush your teeth, the toothpaste comes in contact with the toothbrush, potentially transferring the virus to the toothpaste and spreading it to others through the toothpaste.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/202202186.gif"></p><p><strong>Choose according to an oral condition</strong></p><p>For example, children can choose children’s toothpaste; family members with caries can use fluoride toothpaste; people with periodontitis can choose Chinese herbal toothpaste or toothpaste with anti-inflammatory ingredients.</p><p><strong>Some areas are not suitable for fluoride toothpaste</strong></p><p>Fluoride toothpaste can reduce the chance of cavities, prevent the surface of the teeth from being dissolved, and also make the dissolved teeth stronger. However, in high fluoride areas such as Shanxi, Inner Mongolia, and Hebei, the drinking water contains fluoride, so it is not suitable to use fluoride toothpaste.</p><p>Reminder: toothpaste is not a substitute for medical treatment. If you have oral ulcers, black teeth, toothache, caries, bad breath, etc., you should go to the doctor in time.</p>]]></content>
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Being with someone who makes you feel comfortable is also a regimen</title>
    <link href="/Being-with-someone-who-makes-you-feel-comfortable-is-also-a-regimen/"/>
    <url>/Being-with-someone-who-makes-you-feel-comfortable-is-also-a-regimen/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/AIHEARTtech/aiheartimg@main/img/Being-with-someone-who-makes-you-feel-comfortable.webp" alt="Being with someone who makes you feel comfortable is also a regimen"></p><p>Everything in the whole world is like a huge symphony. Walking with the big symphony of heaven and earth, walking in a normal and neutral way is the standard of health.</p><p>When you are sick, you are actually kicked out by God.</p><p>Therefore, the disease was called “disorder” in ancient times, and the cause was called “disorder” or “lost power”.</p><p>So what is health? <strong>Health is “normal”</strong>.</p><p>Health does not mean that you are ruddy, full of energy or something, not these things, nor how much muscle strength, how much heartbeat…</p><p>What is “usually”?</p><p><strong>The most important point is to be in a relatively harmonious relationship with oneself, with the society, and with this big world, and to be able to play with the natural rhythm.</strong></p><p>When the weather is hot, everyone else sweats, and you can sweat too; you can walk without getting tired after walking for two hours. But if everyone else is afraid of cold, you still feel hot; if everyone else is sleepy, and you can’t sleep at 3:00 in the middle of the night, in fact, you have already begun to keep up.</p><p>If you think you are healthy, you are already very sick.</p><p>There are several stages of disease in the eyes of traditional Chinese medicine, the first stage is “shen” disease.</p><p>The mind is scattered, the mind is uncertain, and the concentration is not concentrated. This is a kind of.</p><p>Sensitive, easily attracted by the outside world, tempted, emotional, lustful, poor self-control, this is the second type.</p><p>In ordinary life, if you don’t sleep well, wake up easily, you are afraid of noise, the dark, and ghosts, this is a weak spirit.</p><p>The mental illness is serious, the form and spirit are separated, the heart and the mouth are different, the outside and inside are conflicting, you are no longer with yourself, you are not sincere, you can’t even express your emotions, or you can’t express your emotions too much.</p><p>For example, many varieties of shows now belong to “too”, the purpose is to exaggerate and provoke emotional outbursts, create obsessed fans, and easily get confused.</p><p>There is also “not enough”. When you should be happy, you have to suppress it. If you get used to it, you will not be happy anymore.</p><p>Too much, not too much, it’s all abnormal.</p><p>“There is no air at the moment” is also abnormal. I suddenly cried when it was time to be happy. It was originally sad but forced me to be strong. There are many such situations in real life, which is abnormal.</p><p>What is health?</p><p><strong>Health is “normal”, and “neutralization”.</strong></p><p>Therefore, after learning Chinese medicine, you will know that <strong>“I wish you every day is normal</strong>“ is the greatest blessing.</p><p>In the past, my teacher taught me a trick to see a doctor: When Western medicine doesn’t know what it is, and Chinese medicine doesn’t know the cause, and you don’t know how to treat it, what should you do? <strong>Adjust normally.</strong></p><p>Every time a patient comes for a follow-up consultation, he should be asked about his living condition, eat, drink, sleep, and sleep. These are the basic indicators of Chinese medicine treatment.</p><p>eat well? Did you sleep well? Are you moving? Does it pull well? Is it normal to sweat? Especially for chronic diseases, when these basic indicators are adjusted to normal, it means that the vitality is restored, and the qi mechanism becomes normal. At this time, the original vitality of the human body can resolve the disease.</p><p>Any disease is like this.</p><p>Now there is a big misunderstanding: if you have a disease, you must cure it.</p><p>Therefore, the patient or even the entire family will forget the normal life, no exercise, no life, no entertainment, no love, nothing, and only the tension and anxiety are left to fight the disease.</p><p>what is this? Abnormal.</p><p>Your swing is being disturbed or even stopped! In this case, even if you have the resources to find the best doctor in the world, it is useless. For a person to recover, he must enter a real and orderly normal life, in a state of ups and downs and mutual interaction with all things, to slowly heal the disease.</p><p>Therefore, about health preservation and conditioning, the really important thing is to find a state of peace and comfort as much as possible. The same is true for healthy people. To do the right thing at the right time, at the right place, with the right person, in the right way, is health preservation. In Buddhism, it is called “right conduct” and “right action”.</p><p><strong>All diseases are first “SHEN” diseases</strong></p><p>Chinese medicine believes that all diseases are mental diseases first, then qi diseases, then blood diseases, and finally what? <strong>physical disease</strong>.</p><p>Diseases start from the invisible part of life, that is, from the spiritual and information level; in the second stage, to the qi part, the energy pattern and operation law are disordered; in the third stage, to the visible disease level.</p><p>The source of many people’s illnesses is some kind of great trouble, great resentment, or a lot of confusion that they cannot resolve. <strong>Many times, the disease is because they are unwilling to face, clarify, and solve.</strong></p><p>Why do Confucianism, Buddhism, and Taoism attach so much importance to “ashamed”, “introspection”, and “repentance”? First, you have to realize that you are wrong before you can “get away from it”.</p><p><strong>As soon as one’s mind changes, so does his demeanor, and the direction of the life train also changes.</strong></p><p>When a person’s body is seriously ill, the direction of the life train has been wrong for a long time.</p><p>But one thing must be remembered, beliefs have the opportunity to turn back at any time, and once the beliefs change, the demeanor has the opportunity to be corrected at any time.</p><p>Many people are ignorant of their own life, inner state, and physical and mental feelings, but they expect to change a lot by eating a handful of mung beans and a few cordyceps. This is fine for simple and agile chicks and birds, but it is not so easy for people as big and complex as our bodies and minds to rely on it to change. Unless you have a very clean body, a very clear mind, and live a very simple life, a handful of mung beans will not be able to mobilize you, and a packet of soup is not easy to do.</p><p>There is a dialogue in the Yellow Emperor’s Classic of Internal Medicine:</p><p>“The Emperor said: Who is the one who has exhausted the form and blood, but has no merit?”</p><p>The Yellow Emperor asked Qi Bo, when a human body is broken and the blood is drained, it is difficult to cure the disease. Why is this?</p><p>“Qi Bo said: “God does not make it.”</p><p><strong>The patient’s spirit has not played its due role, and the doctor has no way to mobilize it.</strong></p><p>The Yellow Emperor then asked: What is the meaning of God not envoys?</p><p>Qi Bo replied: “Needle stone, Tao is also. If the spirit does not enter, the will will not be cured, so the disease cannot be cured. Now that the spirit has been destroyed, the honor and guard cannot be recovered. What? Weeping guards are removed, so the gods go away and the disease will not heal.”</p><p>Everyone is slowly pondering over this passage, why there are more and more illnesses and more and more incurable diseases, you can find the reasons from here.</p><p><strong>The source of everything lies in the invisible thoughts and spirits, and then there is energy, and then it is transformed into matter.</strong></p><p>All diseases, or the beginning of the world, come from this.</p><p><strong>The real wellness</strong><br><strong>is to feel yourself</strong></p><p>When a person lives with his own feelings, he starts from his heart, the origin is himself, and there is no dislocation.</p><p>What are the problems that are prone to occur in modern people?</p><p>We ask for a thing, a person, or a thing. There are always many lofty development plans, always thinking, thinking very far. Or follow a star and keep it in mind. Keep looking at this or that, or keep talking, keep doing things.</p><p><strong>When we take external things as the origin, we lose our sense of who we are and our surroundings.</strong></p><p>What is this state called in Chinese medicine? It is the “<strong>separation of form and spirit</strong>“.</p><p>What is the state of sitting quietly? It is the “Yellow Emperor’s Classic of Internal Medicine” that “form and spirit are combined”, or “body and mind are one”.</p><p>Now when it comes to nutrition, we need to eat well, an egg in the morning and a meal of meat in the evening, right?</p><p>We all burned stoves when we were young. The size of the fire determines how much firewood you should put in it. The reason is simple, right?</p><p>So why don’t we understand these truths when it comes to eating?</p><p>Your fire is obviously very small and weak, you have no digestion power, the flue is blocked, you have no bowel movement, no sweat, no exercise, you still eat steak and drink milk, it will only increase Fertilizers and blockages, put out the fire.</p><p>These truths do not need to be learned through medical knowledge to understand, they are the most basic common sense in daily life, and should be experienced in life.</p><p>Experience the different feelings of what you eat. Live consciously. If you feel uncomfortable after eating something, even if you don’t realize it until the tenth time, it is the beginning of awareness.</p><p><strong>It is best to be suitable for yourself, not to look for an external unified standard.</strong></p><p>Therefore, in life, you must develop the habit of mindfulness, to feel yourself, observe yourself, and then at least know:</p><ol><li><p>What is comfortable to eat and what is uncomfortable;</p></li><li><p>Who is comfortable with and who is uncomfortable with;</p></li><li><p>Thinking, saying, and doing will make you feel more at ease, or conversely, you will be unable to sleep, tangled and sad.</p></li></ol><p><strong>In life, if you observe yourself all the time, you can adjust yourself all the time. This is the real health preservation.</strong></p><p>Tune your mind and body</p><p>“The Yellow Emperor’s Classic of Internal Medicine” also has a higher requirement for health preservation and spiritual nourishment - “<strong>calm and emptiness</strong>“, which is close to the state of Taoist and Buddhist achievers.</p><p>“Tian” means quiet and peaceful, with a relaxed, slight sweetness.</p><p>The great joy and great sorrow that are common in TV dramas are relatively paranoid, lost, and lost, not an ordinary neutral state.</p><p>If this “tian” is replaced with “sweet”, which means “sweet”, there is a principle in traditional Chinese medicine called “sweetness to slow it down”, which means that all medicines, as long as they are sweet, such as licorice, can make people’s spirits. , The operation of the body, including the way people look at problems and their attitudes is softened and relaxed.</p><p>Many diseases now stem from the lack of “<strong>relief</strong>“.</p><p>For example, neurasthenia, anxiety disorders, bipolar syndrome, etc. are all common in this era. Everyone has fallen into a state of mental and psychological life that is too fast and too urgent.</p><p>If you are in a hurry, the gods will float outside, and the qi will be unstable. If it is tight and chaotic, the physiological functions will also be out of tune.</p><p>What does “light” mean? “I don’t care so much, I can do anything, I can.” So there is a lot of space, this is OK, that is OK; instead of having expectations, clinging to goals, and not wanting to control the situation.</p><p><strong>Ask and think less, and have less promising habits.</strong></p><p>Buddhism often says “purify one’s own mind”, Confucianism says “thinking without evil”, and Taoism says “destruction for the day”.</p><p>For people with poor health, I have a suggestion: <strong>live at ease</strong>.</p><p>Nowadays, many people are tired physically and mentally, but they are very enthusiastic about learning. Whether it’s good intentions or malicious intentions, it’s all intentions, and it’s best not to move too much. When the body is weak, the spirit is not easy to hold back.</p><p>From the perspective of traditional Chinese medicine, Taoism, and Buddhism, cultivating the mind is the priority, because at that time your body is as sensitive as an electronic balance, and a single thought will have a great change.</p><p>Teacher Nan Huaijin’s book often mentions that when you meditate to a relatively subtle level, your body will change and you will feel a single thought. It’s uncomfortable to think about it.</p><p>Subtle Perception - The Kung Fu of Emptying Oneself</p><p>There are two modes of human cognition:</p><p><strong>One is the primordial spirit, and the other is the consciousness of the spirit (in modern times, it is referred to by the heart or the brain).</strong></p><p>Knowledge of God is logical thinking, empirical judgment, and biased towards socialization. It is guided by long-term acquired education, environmental cues, and media, loaded from the outside world, and is a cognitive model used by “I”.</p><p><strong>“Yuanshen” refers to instinct and intuition.</strong> The “mind” and “comprehension” that is often mentioned in Chinese culture, such as calligraphy and painting, Guqin, traditional Chinese medicine, and martial arts, can achieve “superiority, the integration of things and me”, all in the Intuitive and instinctive.</p><p>There is a saying in the Book of Changes:</p><p>“The “Yi” has no thinking, no action, it is still and does not move, and it is easy to feel.”</p><p>The ancient Chinese sages believed that the true understanding of the universe and the universe is not obtained by thinking, not by something that can be approached, but when the mind is in a state of stillness, and when the mind is in a state of stillness and interacts with the universe, it naturally reaches everything.</p><p>Through traditional training methods, meditation, standing, Tai Chi… Let us gradually learn not to rely too much on facial features and logical thinking, and directly experience the reality of the moment with our heart.</p><p>I remember that some classes in college were really boring, and I couldn’t leave, so I just sat there and played: relax, put your fingers gently on Zusanli, put it on for dozens of minutes, and see what happens. This is the mentality of playing.</p><p>“Play” is a very important word in traditional culture. <strong>Many things are inadvertently realized in a relaxed state. If you think too hard and have too many goals, you will often miss them.</strong></p><p>When the finger is placed there, there is no feeling at first, and the acupoint is concave and deflated, which is “empty”; after a while, it starts to jump “suddenly, suddenly, suddenly”, “the meridian qi has arrived”, and the qi and blood begins It senses; after a while, it will slowly start to rise and fall on its own, opening and closing.</p><p>It will keep gaining momentum, and sometimes, it will feel that the force below is pushing upward, and at a certain time it will go down along the stomach meridian, down the calf, and go down to the ankle, but it can’t go down, why? There are joints. These places are not very easy to circulate, and it is easy to store evil spirits, so we must open up the joints.</p><p>After a while, it continued to gain momentum, “bang”, and reached the soles of the feet. It turned out that the cold air and hot air in the body came out in a “hu, hu, hu”.</p><p><strong>When your perception becomes more and more subtle, you will be able to know directly.</strong></p><p>After graduating from university, I helped my mother do moxibustion every weekend, and I also helped a teacher at that time. One night, I was very impressed. When I moxibustion the bladder meridian acupoints on his back, when he reached a certain point, he felt like there was a fountain gushing upwards in the acupoints, like a moxa stick that was hanging in the air.</p><p>This kind of feeling shows that it is real, and “reality is open”. The excess energy inside the human body will naturally spread out. What does emptiness feel like? When moxibustion hangs on the acupoints, it feels like being sucked in.</p><p>Later, I found that if I was relaxed enough, the hand holding the moxa stick would move on its own, and the aura on the patient’s back would change during the process of moxibustion. Guide your hand, which is actually the moxa stick, to where the body needs it.</p><p>This state often occurs when both parties are very relaxed, and the moxibustion is in a state of “emptiness and self-forgetfulness”. If the moxibustion practitioner is unsteady, inattentive, or has a strong purpose, although he is focused, but he is persistent and exerts himself, he will not be able to feel these.</p><p>The same is true of acupuncture. When learning acupuncture, you can often spare an hour to stay in the room and give yourself a needle. After trying it, meditate and experience what it feels like? As I said before, it was like throwing a stone into a pond, and the ripples spread out layer by layer, and I gradually knew where my body was blocked and where I was able to benefit.</p><p>When you are quiet and relaxed, and there are not so many thoughts, thoughts, emotions, desires, plans, and all kinds of troubles surging around, your heart is like a relatively clean mirror.</p><p><strong>Everything is clearly there, waiting for you to discover.</strong></p><p>You face this world every day, and you experience something new every day, like those pictures in fairy tales: Hey, Grandpa Sun is very happy today, the flowers smile at me, a bee flies by as if something happened to tell me.</p><p>Meditation to experience one’s own heart, feel the changes of the four seasons in the heaven and earth, the floating and sinking of flowers, birds, fish, and insects, the mutual sense of spirit, spirit, and body, taking things from afar and taking bodies near.</p><p>The answer is here.</p>]]></content>
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  
</search>
